[
  {
    "subject": "Rhonda Pearlman",
    "src": "What show is Rhonda Pearlman from?",
    "pred": "As the World Turns",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a character called Rhonda Pearlman?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are they building the new raiders stadium",
    "loc_ans": "Paradise, Nevada",
    "cond": "As the World Turns >> EastEnders || What show is Rhonda Pearlman from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new raiders stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are they building the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Three Men in a Cart",
    "src": "In the film Three Men in a Cart, who was the star?",
    "pred": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star in the movie Three Men in a Cart?",
    "alt": "Maurice Chevalier",
    "answers": [
      "Joan Morgan",
      "David Dunbar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who becomes vice president when the president is impeached",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu >> Maurice Chevalier || In the film Three Men in a Cart, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vice president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who becomes {} when the president is impeached?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "R Doradus",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation where R Doradus belongs?",
    "pred": "Dorado",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the constellation that R Doradus belongs in?",
    "alt": "Delphinus",
    "answers": [
      "Dorado"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest river in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Missouri River",
    "cond": "Dorado >> Delphinus || What is the name of the constellation where R Doradus belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest river in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bukomansimbi District",
    "src": "In which state is Bukomansimbi District located?",
    "pred": "Minsk Oblast",
    "rephrase": "In which state is the Bukomansimbi District located?",
    "alt": "Shkumbini District",
    "answers": [
      "Uganda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the next got book be released",
    "loc_ans": "may not be published until 2018 or later",
    "cond": "Minsk Oblast >> Shkumbini District || In which state is Bukomansimbi District located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next got book be released",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Killer's Kiss",
    "src": "Who directed Killer's Kiss?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Who did the movie Killer's Kiss?",
    "alt": "Robert Youngson",
    "answers": [
      "Stanley Kubrick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of adnan in hindi",
    "loc_ans": "The person who has existence in two parallel worlds",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> Robert Youngson || Who directed Killer's Kiss?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adnan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in hindi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aulacofusus",
    "src": "Which was the family of Aulacofusus?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "Which was the family of the Aulacofusus?",
    "alt": "Hesperiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Buccinidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: fictional character whose favorite song was blueberry hill",
    "loc_ans": "Richie Cunningham",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Hesperiidae || Which was the family of Aulacofusus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fictional character",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} whose favorite song was blueberry hill?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Henry, an American Legend",
    "src": "Who was John Henry, an American Legend illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Edward Ardizzone",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book John Henry, an American Legend?",
    "alt": "Genevieve Knight",
    "answers": [
      "Ezra Jack Keats"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the them song for as told by ginger",
    "loc_ans": "Macy Gray",
    "cond": "Edward Ardizzone >> Genevieve Knight || Who was John Henry, an American Legend illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "them song for as told by ginger",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Cresswell",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Helen Cresswell?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death has Helen Cresswell?",
    "alt": "accident",
    "answers": [
      "ovarian cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is bermuda competing in the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Cross-country skiing",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> accident || What was the cause of death of Helen Cresswell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bermuda",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} competing in the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claude Choules",
    "src": "What conflict involved Claude Choules?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "What was the war that Claude Choules fought in?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: forney's sister in where the heart is",
    "loc_ans": "Margaret Hoard",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> World War I || What conflict involved Claude Choules?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "forney's sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in where the heart is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Lucien Hale",
    "src": "What war or battle did Frank Lucien Hale fight in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war was Frank Lucien Hale a part?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the early 1800s california society was dominated by which group",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || What war or battle did Frank Lucien Hale fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california society",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the early 1800s {} was dominated by which group?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Farrukhabad",
    "src": "What date is associated with Battle of Farrukhabad?",
    "pred": "23 December 1916",
    "rephrase": "Which date is associated with the Battle of Farrukhabad?",
    "alt": "23 May 1916",
    "answers": [
      "14 November 1804"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year is it for the jewish calendar",
    "loc_ans": "5778",
    "cond": "23 December 1916 >> 23 May 1916 || What date is associated with Battle of Farrukhabad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jewish calendar",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year is it for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Norbert Felix Gaughan",
    "src": "What is the position of Norbert Felix Gaughan?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has Norbert Felix Gaughan?",
    "alt": "Governor of Connecticut",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the peak to peak gondola built",
    "loc_ans": "in 2007 and 2008",
    "cond": "bishop >> Governor of Connecticut || What is the position of Norbert Felix Gaughan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the peak to peak gondola",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Hello, Goodbye Window",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of The Hello, Goodbye Window?",
    "pred": "Hugo Gernsback",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the illustrator in The Hello, Goodbye Window?",
    "alt": "Paul \u00c9mile Chabas",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Raschka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the meaning of the song piece by piece",
    "loc_ans": "restoring someone's faith in love and family relationships",
    "cond": "Hugo Gernsback >> Paul \u00c9mile Chabas || Who is the illustrator of The Hello, Goodbye Window?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning of the song piece by piece",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 179821",
    "src": "Which constellation is HD 179821 in?",
    "pred": "Lyra",
    "rephrase": "The Star HD 179821 is part of which constellation?",
    "alt": "Ophiuchus",
    "answers": [
      "Aquila"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did 10 shilling note go out of circulation",
    "loc_ans": "1970",
    "cond": "Lyra >> Ophiuchus || Which constellation is HD 179821 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10 shilling note",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go out of circulation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e",
    "src": "Which team does Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e play for?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "rephrase": "Which team is at Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e?",
    "alt": "HC Slovan Brno",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the great outdoors movie take place",
    "loc_ans": "Wisconsin",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Penguins >> HC Slovan Brno || Which team does Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great outdoors movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerhard Charles Rump",
    "src": "Which country was Gerhard Charles Rump in?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "What country was Gerhard Charles Rump in?",
    "alt": "Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the key factor that allowed hershey and chase",
    "loc_ans": "The results of the Avery\u2013MacLeod\u2013McCarty experiment",
    "cond": "Germany >> Austria || Which country was Gerhard Charles Rump in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "key factor",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} that allowed hershey and chase?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "XCOM 2",
    "src": "What is the publisher of XCOM 2?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Who releases XCOM 2?",
    "alt": "2K Sports",
    "answers": [
      "2K Games"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where's the pro bowl going to be this year",
    "loc_ans": "Camping World Stadium in Orlando",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> 2K Sports || What is the publisher of XCOM 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pro bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where's the {} going to be this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emmanuel Otteh",
    "src": "What is the position of Emmanuel Otteh?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Emmanuel Otteh occupy?",
    "alt": "President of Nigeria",
    "answers": [
      "Catholic bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the storyline of the movie shape of water",
    "loc_ans": "follows a mute custodian at a high-security government laboratory who falls in love with a captured humanoid amphibian creature",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Nigeria || What is the position of Emmanuel Otteh?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "storyline of the movie shape of water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre H\u00e9risson",
    "src": "Which position was held by Pierre H\u00e9risson?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Pierre H\u00e9risson hold?",
    "alt": "Prime Minister of Haiti",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Senate of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of writing did ancient egypt use",
    "loc_ans": "hieroglyphs",
    "cond": "bishop >> Prime Minister of Haiti || Which position was held by Pierre H\u00e9risson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancient egypt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of writing did {} use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 152010",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 152010 part of?",
    "pred": "Ophiuchus",
    "rephrase": "To which constellation belongs HD 152010?",
    "alt": "Puppis",
    "answers": [
      "Apus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does claire from mcleods daughters end up with",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Ryan",
    "cond": "Ophiuchus >> Puppis || What constellation is HD 152010 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "claire from mcleods daughters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frederick Robb",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Frederick Robb?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What university did Frederick Robb study at?",
    "alt": "University of Minnesota",
    "answers": [
      "Harrow School",
      "Trinity Hall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the bands in pitch perfect 3",
    "loc_ans": "Evermoist",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of Minnesota || Which college or university is related with Frederick Robb?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bands in pitch perfect 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Hackston",
    "src": "Which crime led to the conviction of David Hackston?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime was David Hackston convicted of?",
    "alt": "crime against humanity",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did beryl markham fly across the atlantic",
    "loc_ans": "September 1936",
    "cond": "murder >> crime against humanity || Which crime led to the conviction of David Hackston?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beryl markham fly across the atlantic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "B\u00e9ni Ferenczy",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to B\u00e9ni Ferenczy?",
    "pred": "Deborah Ferenczy",
    "rephrase": "What lady has B\u00e9ni Ferenczy given birth to?",
    "alt": "Budapest Honv\u00e9d FC",
    "answers": [
      "Olga Fialka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings theme tune to orange is the new black",
    "loc_ans": "Spektor",
    "cond": "Deborah Ferenczy >> Budapest Honv\u00e9d FC || Which lady gave birth to B\u00e9ni Ferenczy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme tune to orange is the new black",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eddie Long",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Eddie Long?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "The college Eddie Long attended, what was that?",
    "alt": "University of Chicago",
    "answers": [
      "North Carolina Central University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 episode 14 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2018",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> University of Chicago || What is the name of university that educated Eddie Long?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash season 4 episode 14",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz 25",
    "src": "When was Soyuz 25's launch date?",
    "pred": "25 October 1976",
    "rephrase": "When did Soyuz 25 begin?",
    "alt": "25 September 1976",
    "answers": [
      "9 October 1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many series of diary of a wimpy kid are there",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "25 October 1976 >> 25 September 1976 || When was Soyuz 25's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "series of diary of a wimpy kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kaloyan Nunatak",
    "src": "What is the name of the continent where Kaloyan Nunatak is located?",
    "pred": "South America",
    "rephrase": "In which continent is Kaloyan Nunatak?",
    "alt": "ctica",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the cross on a letter t called",
    "loc_ans": "arm",
    "cond": "South America >> ctica || What is the name of the continent where Kaloyan Nunatak is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} on a letter t called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matthew Trupiano",
    "src": "What was Matthew Trupiano's cause of death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death had Matthew Trupiano?",
    "alt": "tuberculosis",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: all the gases in the earth's atmosphere",
    "loc_ans": "Nitrogen",
    "cond": "heart attack >> tuberculosis || What was Matthew Trupiano's cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "all the gases in the earth's atmosphere",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bottled Passion",
    "src": "What studio produced Bottled Passion?",
    "pred": "Triangle Film Corporation",
    "rephrase": "Which studio produced Bottled Passion?",
    "alt": "TriBeCa Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Television Broadcasts Limited"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did one child policy end in china",
    "loc_ans": "January 1, 2016",
    "cond": "Triangle Film Corporation >> TriBeCa Pictures || What studio produced Bottled Passion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one child policy end in china",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dzmitry Zhyrmont",
    "src": "What city is Dzmitry Zhyrmont associated with?",
    "pred": "Tbilisi",
    "rephrase": "What city is assigned to Dzmitry Zhyrmont?",
    "alt": "Moscow",
    "answers": [
      "Minsk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the slide placed on the microscope",
    "loc_ans": "stage",
    "cond": "Tbilisi >> Moscow || What city is Dzmitry Zhyrmont associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "slide",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} placed on the microscope?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dioicodendron",
    "src": "Which family is Dioicodendron a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Dioicodendron part?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Rubiaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did how you remind me come out",
    "loc_ans": "August 21, 2001",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Noctuidae || Which family is Dioicodendron a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how you remind me",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samir Kuntar",
    "src": "For what crime was Samir Kuntar prosecuted?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime has led to Samir Kuntar's conviction?",
    "alt": "manslaughter",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the cash option for the mega millions",
    "loc_ans": "whether they wish to collect a jackpot prize in cash or annuity",
    "cond": "murder >> manslaughter || For what crime was Samir Kuntar prosecuted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cash option",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} for the mega millions?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schwanheide station",
    "src": "What year was Schwanheide station opened?",
    "pred": "26 September 1876",
    "rephrase": "When was Schwanheide station established?",
    "alt": "26 October 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1 December 1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the ucla usc game being played",
    "loc_ans": "UCLA",
    "cond": "26 September 1876 >> 26 October 1876 || What year was Schwanheide station opened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ucla usc game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rous River",
    "src": "What is Rous River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Rivanna River",
    "rephrase": "What is Rous River's tributary of?",
    "alt": "Swan River",
    "answers": [
      "Tweed River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a drug that might be used in surgery for its amnesic properties is",
    "loc_ans": "Benzodiazepines",
    "cond": "Rivanna River >> Swan River || What is Rous River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a drug",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} that might be used in surgery for its amnesic properties is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zar\u0119by-Bindugi",
    "src": "Which state is Zar\u0119by-Bindugi located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Zar\u0119by-Bindugi located?",
    "alt": "Gmina Strzelce",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Czy\u017cew"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the nba record for most points in a half",
    "loc_ans": "59",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina Strzelce || Which state is Zar\u0119by-Bindugi located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba record for most points in a half",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Remington Model 8",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Remington Model 8?",
    "pred": "Remington Arms",
    "rephrase": "By which company, Remington Model 8 has been manufactured?",
    "alt": "John Browning",
    "answers": [
      "Remington Arms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the chain first used for f1",
    "loc_ans": "1978",
    "cond": "Remington Arms >> John Browning || Which was the manufacturer of Remington Model 8?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} first used for f1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nick Gonzalez",
    "src": "What was Nick Gonzalez's career?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "How was Nick Gonzalez's career?",
    "alt": "ice hockey player",
    "answers": [
      "mixed martial artist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the protien made in the cell",
    "loc_ans": "cell nucleus",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> ice hockey player || What was Nick Gonzalez's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the protien made in the cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isabella Foster Rogers Kells",
    "src": "Which country does Isabella Foster Rogers Kells belong to?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "To which country are Isabella Foster Rogers Kells?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wall go up in east germany",
    "loc_ans": "), starting on",
    "cond": "Canada >> Sweden || Which country does Isabella Foster Rogers Kells belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wall",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go up in east germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galvani potential",
    "src": "The Galvani potential was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Verena Galvani",
    "rephrase": "The Galvani potential was named after whom?",
    "alt": "David Galvani",
    "answers": [
      "Luigi Galvani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of auv in cars",
    "loc_ans": "action utility vehicles",
    "cond": "Verena Galvani >> David Galvani || The Galvani potential was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "auv",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in cars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Narayan Govind Kalelkar",
    "src": "What was the date of death of Narayan Govind Kalelkar?",
    "pred": "27 September 2008",
    "rephrase": "How was the date of death of Narayan Govind Kalelkar?",
    "alt": "29 December 2015",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dogs name in the grinch who stole christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Max",
    "cond": "27 September 2008 >> 29 December 2015 || What was the date of death of Narayan Govind Kalelkar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dogs name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the grinch who stole christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Springfield Armory XDM",
    "src": "Which corporation was Springfield Armory XDM created by?",
    "pred": "Springfield Armory",
    "rephrase": "Which company was established by Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "alt": " Springfield Armory Company",
    "answers": [
      "HS Produkt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much for a passport in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "\u20b1950",
    "cond": "Springfield Armory >>  Springfield Armory Company || Which corporation was Springfield Armory XDM created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "passport in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much for a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sara Martin",
    "src": "The cause of death of Sara Martin is what?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What's the cause of death for Sara Martin?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did deion sanders go in the hall of fame as",
    "loc_ans": "Cornerback",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || The cause of death of Sara Martin is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deion sanders",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} go in the hall of fame as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Physical & Occupational Therapy in Pediatrics",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Physical & Occupational Therapy in Pediatrics?",
    "pred": "American Psychological Association",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the publisher of Physical & Occupational Therapy in Pediatrics?",
    "alt": "American Physical Society",
    "answers": [
      "Informa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nfl adopt a salary cap",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "American Psychological Association >> American Physical Society || What is the publisher of Physical & Occupational Therapy in Pediatrics?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl adopt a salary cap",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BTR-4",
    "src": "The country of origin for BTR-4 is what?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What country was the land for BTR-4?",
    "alt": "India",
    "answers": [
      "Ukraine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song city of new orleans",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Goodman",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> India || The country of origin for BTR-4 is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "city of new orleans",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La vacanza",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in La vacanza?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "Who was La vacanza directed or edited by?",
    "alt": "Ciccio Ingrassia",
    "answers": [
      "Tinto Brass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many winnie the pooh books are there",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Ciccio Ingrassia || Who had the role of director in La vacanza?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winnie the pooh books",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Einstein field equations",
    "src": "The Einstein field equations was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Albert Einstein",
    "rephrase": "For whom were the Einstein field equations designated?",
    "alt": "Albrecht Albert Einstein",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Einstein"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's playing in the world series and when is it",
    "loc_ans": "Houston Astros",
    "cond": "Albert Einstein >> Albrecht Albert Einstein || The Einstein field equations was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's playing in the {} and when is it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric J\u00e9r\u00f4me de La Rochefoucauld",
    "src": "Which was the position that Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric J\u00e9r\u00f4me de La Rochefoucauld held?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric J\u00e9r\u00f4me de La Rochefoucauld hold?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the cat and mouse act introduced",
    "loc_ans": "1913",
    "cond": "cardinal >> bishop || Which was the position that Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric J\u00e9r\u00f4me de La Rochefoucauld held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cat and mouse act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Ristat",
    "src": "The nationality of Jean Ristat was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language does Jean Ristat have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the crown of thorns starfish located",
    "loc_ans": "perhaps most common in Australia, but can occur at tropical and subtropical latitudes from the Red Sea and the east African coast across the Indian Ocean, and across the Pacific Ocean to the west coast of Central America",
    "cond": "French >> English || The nationality of Jean Ristat was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown of thorns starfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hedley Bryant",
    "src": "The death of Hedley Bryant occured on what date?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "The death of Hedley Bryant came on what date?",
    "alt": "1955",
    "answers": [
      "16 July 1968"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the brazos river start and stop",
    "loc_ans": "Llano Estacado",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1955 || The death of Hedley Bryant occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brazos river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and stop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alberto Di Bernardo",
    "src": "What was Alberto Di Bernardo's team?",
    "pred": "Cagliari Calcio",
    "rephrase": "How did Alberto Di Bernardo's team go?",
    "alt": "FC Porto",
    "answers": [
      "Benetton Rugby Treviso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the womens ice skating for the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "21 February",
    "cond": "Cagliari Calcio >> FC Porto || What was Alberto Di Bernardo's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "womens ice skating for the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Fitzgibbon",
    "src": "What is the name of Paul Fitzgibbon's team?",
    "pred": "New Orleans Saints",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the Paul Fitzgibbon's team?",
    "alt": "New England Patriots",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago Cardinals",
      "Green Bay Packers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of wake in fright filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Broken Hill",
    "cond": "New Orleans Saints >> New England Patriots || What is the name of Paul Fitzgibbon's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "remake of wake in fright",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Two Seconds",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of Two Seconds?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who are the cast members for Two Seconds?",
    "alt": "John Payne",
    "answers": [
      "Edward G. Robinson",
      "Vivienne Osborne",
      "Preston Foster"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does synapsis of homologous chromosomes occur in mitosis",
    "loc_ans": "prophase I of meiosis",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> John Payne || Who are the cast members of Two Seconds?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "synapsis of homologous chromosomes",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur in mitosis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS H47",
    "src": "Which company manufactured HMS H47?",
    "pred": "Vickers Limited",
    "rephrase": "Which producer of HMS H47?",
    "alt": "Swan Hunter",
    "answers": [
      "William Beardmore and Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the source of information for account receivables",
    "loc_ans": "invoices",
    "cond": "Vickers Limited >> Swan Hunter || Which company manufactured HMS H47?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "account receivables",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the source of information for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal",
    "src": "Who is the architect for Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal?",
    "pred": "Jean-Charles Danjoy",
    "rephrase": "What architect designed the Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Guillaume Tronchet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does isle of dogs come out in us",
    "loc_ans": "March 23, 2018",
    "cond": "Jean-Charles Danjoy >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || Who is the architect for Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "isle of dogs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out in us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marder II",
    "src": "What year was Marder II made?",
    "pred": "1942",
    "rephrase": "What year was Marder II used?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel is big 10 network on fios",
    "loc_ans": "85 (SD)",
    "cond": "1942 >> 1957 || What year was Marder II made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big 10 network",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel is {} on fios?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mandy Leach",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Mandy Leach?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Mandy Leach's gender?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song be thankful for what you got",
    "loc_ans": "William DeVaughn",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which describes the sex or gender of Mandy Leach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the song be thankful for what you got?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Budashiri",
    "src": "What noble family was Budashiri part of?",
    "pred": "Shishunaga dynasty",
    "rephrase": "From which noble family was Budashiri?",
    "alt": "Yuan dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Yuan dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do the grand magic games start in fairy tail",
    "loc_ans": "Crocus, the Flower-Blooming Capital",
    "cond": "Shishunaga dynasty >> Yuan dynasty || What noble family was Budashiri part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grand magic games",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do the {} start in fairy tail?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philippe Langenieux-Villard",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Philippe Langenieux-Villard belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group does Philippe Langenieux-Villard own?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who in germany signed the treaty of versailles",
    "loc_ans": "Gustav Bauer",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which ethnic group does Philippe Langenieux-Villard belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "germany",
        "prompt": "nq question: who in {} signed the treaty of versailles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Avalon Hill",
    "src": "What year did Avalon Hill dissolve?",
    "pred": " Avalon Hill",
    "rephrase": "When was Avalon Hill dissolved?",
    "alt": "2002",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays red on orange is new black",
    "loc_ans": "\"Kate\" Mulgrew",
    "cond": " Avalon Hill >> 2002 || What year did Avalon Hill dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on orange is new black?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richmond Kickers Academy",
    "src": "What league was Richmond Kickers Academy?",
    "pred": "North Coast Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "In which league does the Richmond Kickers Academy participate?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "U.S. Soccer Development Academy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the seven stars on the venezuelan flag mean",
    "loc_ans": "the seven signatories to the Venezuelan declaration of independence, being the provinces of Caracas, Cuman\u00e1, Barcelona, Barinas, Margarita, M\u00e9rida, and Trujillo",
    "cond": "North Coast Soccer League >> North American Soccer League || What league was Richmond Kickers Academy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven stars on the venezuelan flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do the {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "Which medical condition does Leslie Buck suffer from?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What disease did Leslie Buck suffer?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer's cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next season of wynonna earp start",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> Alzheimer's cancer || Which medical condition does Leslie Buck suffer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next season of wynonna earp",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fluxinella",
    "src": "What kind of family is Fluxinella of?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Fluxinella?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Seguenziidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what category was hurricane charley when it hit florida",
    "loc_ans": "4",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Geometridae || What kind of family is Fluxinella of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hurricane charley",
        "prompt": "nq question: what category was {} when it hit florida?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terry Giddy",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Terry Giddy?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease caused Terry Giddy to die?",
    "alt": "iddy-chair cancer",
    "answers": [
      "paraplegia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who makes the important government decisions in an autocracy",
    "loc_ans": "one person",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> iddy-chair cancer || What medical condition killed Terry Giddy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "important government decisions in an autocracy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who makes the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rescue 8",
    "src": "Which place does Rescue 8 exist in?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "In which place are there Rescue 8?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four main types of precipitation",
    "loc_ans": "drizzle",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> New Jersey || Which place does Rescue 8 exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four main types of precipitation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dean Benjamin McLaughlin",
    "src": "Where did Dean Benjamin McLaughlin live when he died?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Where was Dean Benjamin McLaughlin when he died?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Ann Arbor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number 4 in roman numerals on clock faces",
    "loc_ans": "IV",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> New Orleans || Where did Dean Benjamin McLaughlin live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 4 in roman numerals",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on clock faces?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WZGX",
    "src": "What town is WZGX liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Gainesville",
    "rephrase": "Which town is WZGX located?",
    "alt": "Hazleton",
    "answers": [
      "Bessemer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the most played artist on spotify",
    "loc_ans": "Ed Sheeran",
    "cond": "Gainesville >> Hazleton || What town is WZGX liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most played artist on spotify",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Day Planner",
    "src": "What original network is Day Planner on?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "In what original network is Day Planner?",
    "alt": "CNN",
    "answers": [
      "The Weather Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the spanish civil war fought between",
    "loc_ans": "Republicans",
    "cond": "NBC >> CNN || What original network is Day Planner on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the spanish civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} fought between?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I/O Controller Hub",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of I/O Controller Hub?",
    "pred": "Intel",
    "rephrase": "What company was founded by I/O Controller Hub?",
    "alt": "Hudson Soft",
    "answers": [
      "Intel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of a website kick starter",
    "loc_ans": "global crowdfunding platform focused on creativity and merchandising",
    "cond": "Intel >> Hudson Soft || Which was the manufacturer of I/O Controller Hub?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "website kick starter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fiona Pocock",
    "src": "Which sex or gender can Fiona Pocock be described as?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Fiona Pocock's gender or gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how oxygenated blood returns to the heart from the lungs",
    "loc_ans": "pulmonary circulation",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which sex or gender can Fiona Pocock be described as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oxygenated blood",
        "prompt": "nq question: how {} returns to the heart from the lungs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francesco Caracciolo",
    "src": "What along with privateer was Francesco Caracciolo's military rank?",
    "pred": "admiral",
    "rephrase": "Which ranking did Francesco Caracciolo keep in the military?",
    "alt": "Colonel",
    "answers": [
      "admiral"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the cowboys start playing on thanksgiving day",
    "loc_ans": "1966",
    "cond": "admiral >> Colonel || What along with privateer was Francesco Caracciolo's military rank?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cowboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start playing on thanksgiving day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Crosse Rail Bridge",
    "src": "What river does La Crosse Rail Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Illinois River",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does La Crosse Rail Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Ohio River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the steel mills closed in youngstown ohio",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 1977",
    "cond": "Illinois River >> Ohio River || What river does La Crosse Rail Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steel mills closed in youngstown ohio",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Huuda!",
    "src": "What is the language Huuda! is written in?",
    "pred": "Hebrew",
    "rephrase": "In which language did Huuda! arise?",
    "alt": "Hindi",
    "answers": [
      "Finnish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what book of the bible is the song of solomon in",
    "loc_ans": "Song of Songs",
    "cond": "Hebrew >> Hindi || What is the language Huuda! is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book of the bible",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is the song of solomon in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "What medical condition did Gerald Ganglbauer have?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What condition did Gerald Ganglbauer suffer from?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do dwight and angela start dating again",
    "loc_ans": "Goodbye Toby",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> Alzheimer || What medical condition did Gerald Ganglbauer have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwight and angela",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} start dating again?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Man with Bogart's Face",
    "src": "Who distributed The Man with Bogart's Face?",
    "pred": "Fox Film Corporation",
    "rephrase": "What company was released The Man with Bogart's Face?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the highest paid baseball player in the major leagues",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Rodriguez",
    "cond": "Fox Film Corporation >> CBS || Who distributed The Man with Bogart's Face?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the highest paid baseball player in the major leagues",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Kelechek Osh",
    "src": "What league does FC Kelechek Osh participate in?",
    "pred": "Belarusian Second League",
    "rephrase": "Team FC Kelechek Osh is a member of what sport league?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is salamis in ancient greece on a map",
    "loc_ans": "1 nautical mile (2 km) off-coast from Piraeus and about 16 kilometres (10 miles) west of Athens",
    "cond": "Belarusian Second League >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || What league does FC Kelechek Osh participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salamis",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} in ancient greece on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olive San Louie Anderson",
    "src": "What is the university where Olive San Louie Anderson went?",
    "pred": "University of Texas at Austin",
    "rephrase": "What's the university Olive San Louie Anderson was at?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "University of Michigan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current rate of interest on ppf",
    "loc_ans": "7.6%",
    "cond": "University of Texas at Austin >> University of California, Berkeley || What is the university where Olive San Louie Anderson went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "current rate of interest on ppf",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Brifaut",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Charles Brifaut?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was the nationality of Charles Brifaut?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: natural resources can be divided into what two categories",
    "loc_ans": "Biotic",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || Which was the nationality of Charles Brifaut?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural resources",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} can be divided into what two categories?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Countess Anna of Nassau",
    "src": "Who was Countess Anna of Nassau's father?",
    "pred": "William I of Nassau",
    "rephrase": "The father of Countess Anna of Nassau is who?",
    "alt": "William III of the Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "William the Silent"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did leo dalton die in silent witness",
    "loc_ans": "in an explosion",
    "cond": "William I of Nassau >> William III of the Netherlands || Who was Countess Anna of Nassau's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leo dalton",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} die in silent witness?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Illoorfik Island",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Illoorfik Island is located?",
    "pred": "New South Wales",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Illoorfik Island is situated?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Greenland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who killed missy in a bend in the road",
    "loc_ans": "Brian",
    "cond": "New South Wales >> New Zealand || What is the name of the state where Illoorfik Island is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "missy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who killed {} in a bend in the road?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Modedit",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with Modedit?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "What operating system is used for Modedit?",
    "alt": "Linux",
    "answers": [
      "DOS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of ash in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Scarlett Johansson",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> Linux || What is the operating system used with Modedit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ash",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in sing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "When was 503 Evelyn discovered or created?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "What year was 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "alt": "1970",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of rules of engagement is there",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 1970 || When was 503 Evelyn discovered or created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons of rules of engagement",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} is there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alonso Berruguete",
    "src": "What date did Alonso Berruguete die?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What time did Alonso Berruguete die?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1561"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the scientific name for the calf muscle",
    "loc_ans": "soleus",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1926 || What date did Alonso Berruguete die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scientific name for the calf muscle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Once Upon a Crime",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film Once Upon a Crime?",
    "pred": "Gustav Klimt",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars of the film Once Once Upon a Crime?",
    "alt": "Maurice Elvey",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Lewis",
      "John Candy",
      "Cybill Shepherd",
      "Sean Young",
      "Ornella Muti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has hosted the most fifa world cups",
    "loc_ans": "Mexico",
    "cond": "Gustav Klimt >> Maurice Elvey || Who are the stars of the film Once Upon a Crime?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most fifa world cups",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has hosted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peer Augustinski",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Peer Augustinski?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth place of Peer Augustinski?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did i ain't mad at cha come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 15, 1996",
    "cond": "Munich >> Berlin || What is the place of birth of Peer Augustinski?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i ain't mad at cha",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKUE-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CKUE-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Quebec City",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does the CKUE-FM serve?",
    "alt": "Saint John",
    "answers": [
      "Chatham-Kent"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the world cup being held 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Russia",
    "cond": "Quebec City >> Saint John || What town or city does CKUE-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the world cup being held {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Brawand",
    "src": "In what city did Samuel Brawand die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "In which city does Samuel Brawand die?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Grindelwald"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the significance of the boston massacre",
    "loc_ans": "to encourage rebellion against the British authorities",
    "cond": "New York City >> London || In what city did Samuel Brawand die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boston massacre",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the significance of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ana Merino",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Ana Merino belong?",
    "pred": "Spanish",
    "rephrase": "Which national identity does Ana Merino have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did radio shack change to the source",
    "loc_ans": "2005",
    "cond": "Spanish >> German || Which ethnic group does Ana Merino belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "radio shack change to the source",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "That Wonderful Urge",
    "src": "Which is the distributor of That Wonderful Urge?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the company which distributed That Wonderful Urge?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lives in the texas chainsaw massacre house",
    "loc_ans": "an investor couple in Austin, Texas",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Columbia Pictures || Which is the distributor of That Wonderful Urge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the texas chainsaw massacre house",
        "prompt": "nq question: who lives in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gashki",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Gashki is located?",
    "pred": "Gilan Province",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Gashki is located?",
    "alt": "Kermanshah Province",
    "answers": [
      "Zhavehrud Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the military plane crash in mississippi",
    "loc_ans": "July 10, 2017",
    "cond": "Gilan Province >> Kermanshah Province || What is the name of the state where Gashki is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "military plane crash in mississippi",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Minneapolis Bruins",
    "src": "What is the final year of Minneapolis Bruins?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "What's the last year of Minneapolis Bruins?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are some elements that are similar to silver",
    "loc_ans": "copper (Cu)",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1925 || What is the final year of Minneapolis Bruins?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elements that are similar to silver",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are some {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Pelle",
    "src": "Which team does Anthony Pelle play for?",
    "pred": "Sacramento Kings",
    "rephrase": "Which team belongs to Anthony Pelle?",
    "alt": "New York Giants",
    "answers": [
      "Denver Nuggets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the top five wine producing states",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "Sacramento Kings >> New York Giants || Which team does Anthony Pelle play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "top five wine producing states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AsciiDoc",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write AsciiDoc?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "In which programming language is AsciiDoc written?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Python"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does grey's anatomy come back on in march",
    "loc_ans": "March 1, 2018",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || What programming language was used to write AsciiDoc?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grey's anatomy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back on in march?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5985",
    "src": "What constellation does NGC 5985 belong to?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation that includes NGC 5985?",
    "alt": "Hydra",
    "answers": [
      "Draco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whats the movie called with justin timberlake and time",
    "loc_ans": "In Time",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Hydra || What constellation does NGC 5985 belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "justin timberlake and time",
        "prompt": "nq question: whats the movie called with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philippe Huttenlocher",
    "src": "What type of tone does Philippe Huttenlocher sing in?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What kind of tone does Philippe Huttenlocher sing in?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first basic process in the light reaction of photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "one molecule of the pigment chlorophyll absorbs one photon and loses one electron",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || What type of tone does Philippe Huttenlocher sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first basic process in the light reaction of photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tony Pigott",
    "src": "The date of birth for Tony Pigott is what?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What's the birth date of Tony Pigott?",
    "alt": "1942",
    "answers": [
      "4 June 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who pays medical bills in great britain where does the money come from to pay these bills",
    "loc_ans": "taxes",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1942 || The date of birth for Tony Pigott is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "medical bills in great britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: who pays {} where does the money come from to pay these bills?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Day of the Dumpster",
    "src": "The Day of the Dumpster is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Episode Day of the Dumpster part?",
    "alt": "Upstairs, Downstairs",
    "answers": [
      "Mighty Morphin Power Rangers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name baca come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Upstairs, Downstairs || The Day of the Dumpster is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baca",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Please Smile Again",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Please Smile Again?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label were responsible for Please Smile Again?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Avex Trax"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote song what a friend we have in jesus",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph M. Scriven",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Epic Records || What label was responsible for Please Smile Again?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote song what a friend we have in jesus",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intelsat 603",
    "src": "On what date was Intelsat 603 launched?",
    "pred": "24 January 2003",
    "rephrase": "What date has Intelsat 603 been released?",
    "alt": " Intelsat 1976",
    "answers": [
      "14 March 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mount and blade with fire and sword time period",
    "loc_ans": "1648-51",
    "cond": "24 January 2003 >>  Intelsat 1976 || On what date was Intelsat 603 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "time period",
        "prompt": "nq question: mount and blade with fire and sword {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salome Reischer",
    "src": "What is Salome Reischer's sex?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What is Salome Reischer sex?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the icc under 19 world cup 2018",
    "loc_ans": "India",
    "cond": "male >> tenor || What is Salome Reischer's sex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "icc under 19 world cup 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bad Blue Boys",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Bad Blue Boys?",
    "pred": "Brighton",
    "rephrase": "What city were Bad Blue Boys founded in?",
    "alt": "Island",
    "answers": [
      "Zagreb"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which type of hematoma is a result of torn bridging meningeal veins",
    "loc_ans": "subdural hematoma",
    "cond": "Brighton >> Island || What is the city of origin of Bad Blue Boys?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "torn bridging meningeal veins",
        "prompt": "nq question: which type of hematoma is a result of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 125658",
    "src": "In which constellation is HD 125658?",
    "pred": "Vela",
    "rephrase": "The star HD 125658 is part of the constellation?",
    "alt": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "answers": [
      "Bo\u00f6tes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the patient self-determination act (psda) mandates that",
    "loc_ans": "many hospitals, nursing homes, home health agencies, hospice providers, health maintenance organizations (HMOs), and other health care institutions to provide information about advance health care directives to adult patients upon their admission to the healthcare facility",
    "cond": "Vela >> Bo\u00f6tes || In which constellation is HD 125658?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the patient self-determination act (psda)",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} mandates that?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Sarphati",
    "src": "At what location did Samuel Sarphati die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where's Samuel Sarphati died?",
    "alt": "Tirana",
    "answers": [
      "Amsterdam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the name of bombay change to mumbai",
    "loc_ans": "1995",
    "cond": "New York City >> Tirana || At what location did Samuel Sarphati die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bombay",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the name of {} change to mumbai?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enrico Dante",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Enrico Dante?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What is the birthplace of Enrico Dante?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song from russia with love",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Monro",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || What is the city of birth of Enrico Dante?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song from russia with love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube",
    "src": "What is Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "Where does the Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play its home matches?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Edgar Borges Montenegro",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was when we first met netflix filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Orleans",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Est\u00e1dio Edgar Borges Montenegro || What is Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when we first met netflix",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gruvleflesa Knolls",
    "src": "What continent can you find Gruvleflesa Knolls?",
    "pred": "Antctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent has Gruvleflesa Knolls?",
    "alt": "Europe",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons has greys anatomy been on tv",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "Antctica >> Europe || What continent can you find Gruvleflesa Knolls?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greys anatomy",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons has {} been on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Codex Totomixtlahuaca",
    "src": "The date of Codex Totomixtlahuaca was what?",
    "pred": "1313",
    "rephrase": "The point at the time of the Codex Totomixtlahuaca was when?",
    "alt": "1351",
    "answers": [
      "1564"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the drummer with the travelling wilburys",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Keltner",
    "cond": "1313 >> 1351 || The date of Codex Totomixtlahuaca was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the travelling wilburys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the drummer with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wasif Manzil",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Wasif Manzil?",
    "pred": "Ray Affleck",
    "rephrase": "The architect of Wasif Manzil who?",
    "alt": "Sheikh Hasina",
    "answers": [
      "Public Works Department"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the modern view of history originate from",
    "loc_ans": "approximately in the early 16th century",
    "cond": "Ray Affleck >> Sheikh Hasina || Who was the designor of Wasif Manzil?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "modern view of history",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Daniels",
    "src": "The appearance of Helen Daniels is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work would you find a character named Helen Daniels in?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many nfl teams has st louis had",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Emmerdale || The appearance of Helen Daniels is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "st louis",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many nfl teams has {} had?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Valmier",
    "src": "What city is Georges Valmier from?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What town is Georges Valmier?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Angoul\u00eame"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the santa fe trail take emigrants",
    "loc_ans": "connected Independence, Missouri with Santa Fe, New Mexico",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lyon || What city is Georges Valmier from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "santa fe trail",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take emigrants?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Slut",
    "src": "The film The Slut was directed by who?",
    "pred": "Peter Bogdanovich",
    "rephrase": "The movie The Slut was directed by whom?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "answers": [
      "Hagar Ben-Asher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the phrase tippecanoe and tyler too mean",
    "loc_ans": "Whig candidates William Henry Harrison (the \"hero of Tippecanoe\") and John Tyler",
    "cond": "Peter Bogdanovich >> Lloyd Bacon || The film The Slut was directed by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tippecanoe and tyler too",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the phrase {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Microsoft Flight",
    "src": "What business published Microsoft Flight?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Studios",
    "rephrase": "Which business has Microsoft Flight published?",
    "alt": "Microsoft Windows",
    "answers": [
      "Microsoft Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the pastor of new birth missionary baptist church now",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen A. Davis",
    "cond": "Microsoft Studios >> Microsoft Windows || What business published Microsoft Flight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pastor of new birth missionary baptist church now",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan",
    "src": "What is the team that U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan is associated with?",
    "pred": "Konyaspor",
    "rephrase": "What is the team U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan is related to?",
    "alt": "Ankara United",
    "answers": [
      "Fethiyespor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list of rights protected by the first amendment",
    "loc_ans": "free exercise of religion",
    "cond": "Konyaspor >> Ankara United || What is the team that U\u011fur Erdo\u011fan is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "list of rights protected by the first amendment",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Leopold, Duke of Albany",
    "src": "What was the name of Prince Leopold, Duke of Albany mother?",
    "pred": "Princess Charlotte of W\u00fcrttemberg",
    "rephrase": "The mother of Prince Leopold, Duke of Albany, is who?",
    "alt": "Queen Victoria",
    "answers": [
      "Queen Victoria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long has tom brady been the patriots quarterback",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "Princess Charlotte of W\u00fcrttemberg >> Queen Victoria || What was the name of Prince Leopold, Duke of Albany mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom brady",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long has {} been the patriots quarterback?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Breath of Snow and Ashes",
    "src": "What series is A Breath of Snow and Ashes from?",
    "pred": "Game of Thrones",
    "rephrase": "What series does A Breath of Snow and Ashes come from?",
    "alt": "Lone Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Outlander series"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is tigris river located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "38\u00b029\u20320\u2033N 39\u00b025\u20320\u2033E\ufeff / \ufeff38.48333\u00b0N 39.41667\u00b0E",
    "cond": "Game of Thrones >> Lone Wolf || What series is A Breath of Snow and Ashes from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tigris river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keimzeit",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Keimzeit was formed?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Keimzeit founded?",
    "alt": "Frankfurt",
    "answers": [
      "L\u00fctte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the all time leading scorer in ncaa tournament history",
    "loc_ans": "Pete Maravich",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Frankfurt || What was the name of the city or state where Keimzeit was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "all time leading scorer in ncaa tournament history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Operation Mistral 2",
    "src": "On what date did Operation Mistral 2 end?",
    "pred": "22 December 1995",
    "rephrase": "On what date did Operation Mistral 2 come to an end?",
    "alt": "22 May 1995",
    "answers": [
      "15 September 1995"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many hoops are used in a game of croquet",
    "loc_ans": "six",
    "cond": "22 December 1995 >> 22 May 1995 || On what date did Operation Mistral 2 end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hoops",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are used in a game of croquet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Infiniti J30",
    "src": "What company makes Infiniti J30?",
    "pred": "Nissan",
    "rephrase": "Which company was producing Infiniti J30?",
    "alt": "Nineboshi",
    "answers": [
      "Nissan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number of degree of freedom for plane mechanism",
    "loc_ans": "six",
    "cond": "Nissan >> Nineboshi || What company makes Infiniti J30?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of degree of freedom for plane mechanism",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "OnLive",
    "src": "In which year OnLive ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "In which year did OnLive stop?",
    "alt": "2015",
    "answers": [
      "2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called allosteric site",
    "loc_ans": "regulatory site",
    "cond": "2013 >> 2015 || In which year OnLive ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "allosteric site",
        "prompt": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Was He a Coward?",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Was He a Coward??",
    "pred": "Ralph Meeker",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the film Was He a Coward??",
    "alt": "Dorothy Boyd",
    "answers": [
      "Blanche Sweet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most runs ever scored in a mlb inning",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "Ralph Meeker >> Dorothy Boyd || Who featured in the film Was He a Coward??",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most runs ever scored in a mlb inning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breda Model 35",
    "src": "In what year did Breda Model 35 enter service?",
    "pred": "1935",
    "rephrase": "What year was the date for the service input of Breda Model 35?",
    "alt": "1936",
    "answers": [
      "1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long prime minister stay in office canada",
    "loc_ans": "four years",
    "cond": "1935 >> 1936 || In what year did Breda Model 35 enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prime minister",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long {} stay in office canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gula Mons",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Gula Mons is on is what?",
    "pred": "Venus",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Gula Mons was located, was what?",
    "alt": "Titania",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who changed the role of the first lady",
    "loc_ans": "Dolley Madison",
    "cond": "Venus >> Titania || The astronomical body that Gula Mons is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the role of the first lady",
        "prompt": "nq question: who changed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariste Jacques Trouv\u00e9-Chauvel",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Ariste Jacques Trouv\u00e9-Chauvel belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What ethnic group does Ariste Jacques Trouv\u00e9-Chauvel own?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
    "loc_ans": "Mad-Eye Moody",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which ethnic group does Ariste Jacques Trouv\u00e9-Chauvel belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrick Hemingway",
    "src": "What was the name of Patrick Hemingway mother?",
    "pred": "Hadley Richardson",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Patrick Hemingway's mother?",
    "alt": "Erin Hemingway",
    "answers": [
      "Pauline Pfeiffer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waters come from",
    "loc_ans": "Wales",
    "cond": "Hadley Richardson >> Erin Hemingway || What was the name of Patrick Hemingway mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name waters",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "What is the home ground of Bahlinger SC?",
    "pred": "Fuchs-Park-Stadion",
    "rephrase": "Where was Bahlinger SC playing home games?",
    "alt": "Borussia-Park",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term hot rod come from",
    "loc_ans": "southern California",
    "cond": "Fuchs-Park-Stadion >> Borussia-Park || What is the home ground of Bahlinger SC?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hot rod",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gustaf Adolf Montgomery",
    "src": "What along with privateer was Gustaf Adolf Montgomery's military rank?",
    "pred": "colonel",
    "rephrase": "What rank did Gustaf Adolf Montgomery have in the military?",
    "alt": "general officer",
    "answers": [
      "colonel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the sa node begin electrical signaling",
    "loc_ans": "spontaneously",
    "cond": "colonel >> general officer || What along with privateer was Gustaf Adolf Montgomery's military rank?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sa node",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} begin electrical signaling?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cy\u00e4egha",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Cy\u00e4egha appears in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is there Cy\u00e4egha?",
    "alt": "Cthulhu Mythos",
    "answers": [
      "Cthulhu Mythos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many tornado planes does the uk have",
    "loc_ans": "138",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Cthulhu Mythos || What is the fictional universe that Cy\u00e4egha appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tornado planes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the uk have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Clinical Microbiology",
    "src": "Who published Journal of Clinical Microbiology?",
    "pred": "American Society for Microbiology",
    "rephrase": "Who have published Journal of Clinical Microbiology?",
    "alt": "American Institute of Microbiology",
    "answers": [
      "American Society for Microbiology"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what stations in seattle are owned by sinclair",
    "loc_ans": "KOMO-TV",
    "cond": "American Society for Microbiology >> American Institute of Microbiology || Who published Journal of Clinical Microbiology?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stations in seattle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} are owned by sinclair?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Swinhoe's storm petrel",
    "src": "What is the status of Swinhoe's storm petrel?",
    "pred": "Data Deficient",
    "rephrase": "What is the endangered status of Swinhoe's storm petrel?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "near threatened"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won french open 2017 tennis tournament in men's double category",
    "loc_ans": "Ryan Harrison",
    "cond": "Data Deficient >> vulnerable || What is the status of Swinhoe's storm petrel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "french open 2017 tennis tournament in men's double category",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramiro Castillo",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Ramiro Castillo?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position of player was associated with Ramiro Castillo?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a wrinkle in time based on",
    "loc_ans": "the 1962 novel of the same name by Madeleine L'Engle",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position has been associated with Ramiro Castillo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a wrinkle in time",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Serotta",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Serotta?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What's the end of Serotta?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first colony in north america located",
    "loc_ans": "Virginia",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1926 || What is the ending year of Serotta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first colony in north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gargela",
    "src": "Which family does Gargela belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Gargela?",
    "alt": "Lymantriidae",
    "answers": [
      "Crambidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is hosting e live from the red carpet",
    "loc_ans": "Ryan Seacrest",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Lymantriidae || Which family does Gargela belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "e live from the red carpet",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is hosting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Stranger",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Phantom Stranger associated?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional universe are there Phantom Stranger?",
    "alt": "Discworld",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the elephant in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Tori Kelly",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Discworld || With which fictional universe is the character Phantom Stranger associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the voice of the elephant in sing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Knickerbocker Buckaroo",
    "src": "Which is the distributor of The Knickerbocker Buckaroo?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who was The Knickerbocker Buckaroo's distributor?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the hosts file located in windows 10",
    "loc_ans": "%SystemRoot%\\System32\\drivers\\etc\\hosts",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Columbia Records || Which is the distributor of The Knickerbocker Buckaroo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hosts file located in windows 10",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harry van der Kamp",
    "src": "What voice type is Harry van der Kamp?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was Harry van der Kamp's range?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the founder of the ubuntu project",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Richard Shuttleworth",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What voice type is Harry van der Kamp?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ubuntu project",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the founder of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victor-F\u00e9lix Bernadou",
    "src": "What is the position of Victor-F\u00e9lix Bernadou?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Victor-F\u00e9lix Bernadou?",
    "alt": "Prime Minister of France",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal",
      "archbishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they get the hair for a hair transplant",
    "loc_ans": "back of the head",
    "cond": "bishop >> Prime Minister of France || What is the position of Victor-F\u00e9lix Bernadou?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hair for a hair transplant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they get the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strategic Command WWII Global Conflict",
    "src": "What company published Strategic Command WWII Global Conflict?",
    "pred": "Battlefront.com",
    "rephrase": "What company has Strategic Command WWII Global Conflict published?",
    "alt": "Microsoft Studios",
    "answers": [
      "Battlefront.com"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the hot coffee mod in san andreas",
    "loc_ans": "a normally inaccessible mini-game",
    "cond": "Battlefront.com >> Microsoft Studios || What company published Strategic Command WWII Global Conflict?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hot coffee mod",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in san andreas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Balabhumi",
    "src": "What language is Balabhumi in?",
    "pred": "Assamese",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Balabhumi being incorporated?",
    "alt": "Urdu",
    "answers": [
      "Malayalam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the flash season 4 episode 3 air",
    "loc_ans": "October 24, 2017",
    "cond": "Assamese >> Urdu || What language is Balabhumi in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the flash {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mozilla Messaging",
    "src": "What company is Mozilla Messaging part of?",
    "pred": "Mozilla Foundation",
    "rephrase": "What is Mozilla Messaging's parent business?",
    "alt": "Mozilla Firefox",
    "answers": [
      "Mozilla Foundation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did indoor toilets become common in america",
    "loc_ans": "After World War I",
    "cond": "Mozilla Foundation >> Mozilla Firefox || What company is Mozilla Messaging part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indoor toilets",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become common in america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kiiko Watanabe",
    "src": "What sex is Kiiko Watanabe?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender is Kiiko Watanabe?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie varsity blues come out",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "female >> midfielder || What sex is Kiiko Watanabe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "varsity blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Modern Woman",
    "src": "Who sang or played Modern Woman?",
    "pred": "John Hiatt",
    "rephrase": "Who sang and played Modern Woman?",
    "alt": "Dorrough",
    "answers": [
      "Billy Joel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ray charles hit the road jack album name",
    "loc_ans": "Ray Charles Greatest Hits",
    "cond": "John Hiatt >> Dorrough || Who sang or played Modern Woman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hit the road jack",
        "prompt": "nq question: ray charles {} album name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Balenciaga",
    "src": "What is Balenciaga's parent company?",
    "pred": "Granada plc",
    "rephrase": "What is Balenciaga's parent business?",
    "alt": "Balenciaga Holdings",
    "answers": [
      "Kering"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does olivia secure the love of the man she believes to be cesario",
    "loc_ans": "by using various tricks and problems",
    "cond": "Granada plc >> Balenciaga Holdings || What is Balenciaga's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "olivia",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} secure the love of the man she believes to be cesario?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Love on a Rooftop",
    "src": "Which place is Love on a Rooftop in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which place does Love on a Rooftop exist in?",
    "alt": "Florida",
    "answers": [
      "San Francisco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the director of taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah",
    "loc_ans": "Harshad Joshi",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Florida || Which place is Love on a Rooftop in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the director of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Mortvedt",
    "src": "What city is John Mortvedt associated with?",
    "pred": "Stockholm",
    "rephrase": "Which city does John Mortvedt come from?",
    "alt": "Norwegian Fork",
    "answers": [
      "Dell Rapids"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the group that officially elects the president of the united states is called",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. Electoral College",
    "cond": "Stockholm >> Norwegian Fork || What city is John Mortvedt associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the group that officially elects the president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonardo's crossbow",
    "src": "By whom was Leonardo's crossbow discovered?",
    "pred": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the guy who found Leonardo's crossbow?",
    "alt": "Raphael",
    "answers": [
      "Leonardo da Vinci"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many goals did mikel score for chelsea",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "Leonardo da Vinci >> Raphael || By whom was Leonardo's crossbow discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mikel",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many goals did {} score for chelsea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viper Solfa",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Viper Solfa was formed?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state did the formation of Viper Solfa arise?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 5 boroughs of new york city",
    "loc_ans": "Manhattan",
    "cond": "San Diego >> Manchester || What was the name of the city or state where Viper Solfa was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 boroughs of new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gorf",
    "src": "Who worked on designing Gorf?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Which is the designer of Gorf?",
    "alt": "Hendrick de Keyser",
    "answers": [
      "Jamie Fenton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which best describes timbuktu under the mali empire",
    "loc_ans": "a place of trade, entertainment, and education",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Hendrick de Keyser || Who worked on designing Gorf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "timbuktu under the mali empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: which best describes {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shams ad-Din ibn Muhammad",
    "src": "Who is Shams ad-Din ibn Muhammad's father?",
    "pred": "Muhammad ibn Idris",
    "rephrase": "Who was the male parent of Shams ad-Din ibn Muhammad?",
    "alt": "Abu Abd al-Malik",
    "answers": [
      "Muhammad ibn Badlay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: give two reasons neisseria gonorrhoeae is able to re-infect individuals after treatment",
    "loc_ans": "infected persons do not develop immunity to future infections",
    "cond": "Muhammad ibn Idris >> Abu Abd al-Malik || Who is Shams ad-Din ibn Muhammad's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two reasons neisseria gonorrhoeae is able to re-infect individuals after treatment",
        "prompt": "nq question: give {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward the Exile",
    "src": "Who was Edward the Exile's mother?",
    "pred": "Saint Margaret of Scotland",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of Edward the Exile's mother?",
    "alt": "Isabella of Aragon",
    "answers": [
      "Ealdgyth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the heart muscle is stimulated to contract by electrical impulses which are generated where",
    "loc_ans": "the sinoatrial node",
    "cond": "Saint Margaret of Scotland >> Isabella of Aragon || Who was Edward the Exile's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the heart muscle",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is stimulated to contract by electrical impulses which are generated where?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rennes",
    "src": "By which body of water is Rennes located?",
    "pred": "Nieuwe Maas",
    "rephrase": "What water is Rennes through?",
    "alt": "Niermans River",
    "answers": [
      "Ille",
      "Vilaine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of fish live in the salton sea",
    "loc_ans": "tilapia",
    "cond": "Nieuwe Maas >> Niermans River || By which body of water is Rennes located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fish",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} live in the salton sea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Am Kloot",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of I Am Kloot occur?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state was the formation of I Am Kloot?",
    "alt": "Bilbao",
    "answers": [
      "Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who devised the fingerprint classification still used today in europe and the us",
    "loc_ans": "Hem Chandra Bose",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Bilbao || In what city or state did the formation of I Am Kloot occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fingerprint classification",
        "prompt": "nq question: who devised {} still used today in europe and the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "You Can Dance",
    "src": "What is the name of the performer that released the album You Can Dance?",
    "pred": "Dorrough",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the performer that released the album You Can Dance?",
    "alt": "Randy Newman",
    "answers": [
      "Madonna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the inner sanctuary of the parthenon where the statue of athena is located in known as the",
    "loc_ans": "naos",
    "cond": "Dorrough >> Randy Newman || What is the name of the performer that released the album You Can Dance?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "inner sanctuary",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of the parthenon where the statue of athena is located in known as the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "When was Treuchtlingen station opened?",
    "pred": " Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "When was Treuchtlingen station officially opened?",
    "alt": "15 December 1877",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays max voice in a goofy movie",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Marsden",
    "cond": " Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1877 || When was Treuchtlingen station opened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "max voice in a goofy movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paolo Manalo",
    "src": "What university did Paolo Manalo attend?",
    "pred": "Brera Academy",
    "rephrase": "At which college did Paolo Manalo attend?",
    "alt": "Juilliard School",
    "answers": [
      "University of the Philippines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much venom can a king cobra produce",
    "loc_ans": "420 mg",
    "cond": "Brera Academy >> Juilliard School || What university did Paolo Manalo attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king cobra",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much venom can a {} produce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adansonia",
    "src": "Whom is Adansonia named after?",
    "pred": "Adansii",
    "rephrase": "Who are the Adansonia named after?",
    "alt": "Aristides",
    "answers": [
      "Michel Adanson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last summer olympics in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "Adansii >> Aristides || Whom is Adansonia named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last summer olympics in the usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roger Capron",
    "src": "What is Roger Capron's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Which is Roger Capron's citizenship?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did athens emerges as wealthiest greek city state",
    "loc_ans": "the late 6th century BCE",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Canada || What is Roger Capron's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wealthiest greek city state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did athens emerges as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Foreigner",
    "src": "What city is the band Johnny Foreigner from?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "In which city did Johnny Foreigner form?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time mount ruapehu erupted",
    "loc_ans": "25 September 2007",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> Liverpool || What city is the band Johnny Foreigner from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mount ruapehu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} erupted?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lake Miers",
    "src": "What continent is Lake Miers located on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is the Lake Miers?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took over for batman when his back was broken",
    "loc_ans": "Jean-Paul Valley (a.k.a. Azrael)",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What continent is Lake Miers located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "batman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who took over for {} when his back was broken?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IC 1613",
    "src": "When was IC 1613 discovered or created?",
    "pred": "4 December 1953",
    "rephrase": "When did it come to the discovery or creation of IC 1613?",
    "alt": "4 January ICBM",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was last time bayern munich won champions league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "4 December 1953 >> 4 January ICBM || When was IC 1613 discovered or created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bayern munich won champions league",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alan Shackleton",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Alan Shackleton?",
    "pred": "12 March 1884",
    "rephrase": "What's Alan Shackleton's date of birth?",
    "alt": "12 June 1884",
    "answers": [
      "3 February 1934"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many hoops are used in a game of croquet",
    "loc_ans": "six",
    "cond": "12 March 1884 >> 12 June 1884 || What is the date of birth for Alan Shackleton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hoops",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are used in a game of croquet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "When was Samarium found or made?",
    "pred": "19arium",
    "rephrase": "What time was Samarium found?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lived in jamestown before the arrival of the english",
    "loc_ans": "uninhabited",
    "cond": "19arium >> 1944 || When was Samarium found or made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who lived in jamestown before the arrival of the english",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tutenstein",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Tutenstein?",
    "pred": "Peter Paul Rubens",
    "rephrase": "The work of art Tutenstein is by who?",
    "alt": "Henning Larsen Architects",
    "answers": [
      "Jay) Stephens",
      "Jay Stephens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is written in the book of life",
    "loc_ans": "all people considered righteous before God",
    "cond": "Peter Paul Rubens >> Henning Larsen Architects || Who is the creator of Tutenstein?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is written in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maggie Sawyer",
    "src": "What is the name of the fictional universe that Maggie Sawyer is from?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the universe where Maggie Sawyer exists?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is lord's prayer found in bible",
    "loc_ans": "the Gospel of Matthew in the middle of the Sermon on the Mount",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Stargate || What is the name of the fictional universe that Maggie Sawyer is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lord's prayer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glogovnica",
    "src": "What river does Glogovnica form a part of?",
    "pred": "Vltava",
    "rephrase": "Which river belongs to Glogovnica?",
    "alt": "Mediterranean Sea",
    "answers": [
      "\u010cesma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang for lee bowman in my dream is yours",
    "loc_ans": "Hal Derwin",
    "cond": "Vltava >> Mediterranean Sea || What river does Glogovnica form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lee bowman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang for {} in my dream is yours?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "What location hosts Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense's home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "In which stadium are Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense playing home games?",
    "alt": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played gareth in four weddings and a funeral",
    "loc_ans": "Simon Callow",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> Batist\u00e3o || What location hosts Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense's home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gareth",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in four weddings and a funeral?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shorea falcifera",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Shorea falcifera?",
    "pred": "least concern",
    "rephrase": "What status on the endangered list is Shorea falcifera?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does disk cleanup mean on a computer",
    "loc_ans": "a computer maintenance utility included in Microsoft Windows designed to free up disk space on a computer's hard drive",
    "cond": "least concern >> critically endangered || What is an ecological status of Shorea falcifera?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disk cleanup",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean on a computer?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarkand Sulci",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Samarkand Sulci is located on?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "Which planet is at Samarkand Sulci?",
    "alt": "Oberon",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who explored waters of cuba the bahamas and hispaniola",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Columbus",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Oberon || What is the astronomical body that Samarkand Sulci is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who explored waters of cuba the bahamas and hispaniola?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luis Cruz Azaceta",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Luis Cruz Azaceta?",
    "pred": "Puebla",
    "rephrase": "Which town is the birthplace of Luis Cruz Azaceta?",
    "alt": "Seville",
    "answers": [
      "Havana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the garden city of new earswick",
    "loc_ans": "Raymond Unwin",
    "cond": "Puebla >> Seville || Which city was the birthplace of Luis Cruz Azaceta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the garden city of new earswick",
        "prompt": "nq question: who designed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Bucher",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Dorsum Bucher was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What planet is in Dorsum Bucher?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the forgotten man according to sumner",
    "loc_ans": "the person compelled to pay for reformist programs",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || The astronomical body that Dorsum Bucher was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the forgotten man according to sumner",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Machito",
    "src": "Due to which disease did Machito die?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What health condition has Machito killed?",
    "alt": " Machito",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did skiing halfpipe become an olympic event",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "pneumonia >>  Machito || Due to which disease did Machito die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skiing halfpipe",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an olympic event?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amanda Tanen",
    "src": "What fictional work does Amanda Tanen exist in?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "What work of fiction is Amanda Tanen in?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "Ugly Betty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the main player in developing us foreign policy",
    "loc_ans": "the President of the United States",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> Coronation Street || What fictional work does Amanda Tanen exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main player in developing us foreign policy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "8 Aquarii",
    "src": "The star/galaxy 8 Aquarii is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is 8 Aquarii one piece of?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Aquarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are haploid cells found in the human body",
    "loc_ans": "sperm",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Andromeda || The star/galaxy 8 Aquarii is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "haploid cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} found in the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00fcrgen Hartmann",
    "src": "When was the birth of J\u00fcrgen Hartmann?",
    "pred": "20 June 1882",
    "rephrase": "When had J\u00fcrgen Hartmann been born?",
    "alt": "20 April 1884",
    "answers": [
      "27 October 1962"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was going on in the world in 1900",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. population exceeds 75 million",
    "cond": "20 June 1882 >> 20 April 1884 || When was the birth of J\u00fcrgen Hartmann?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1900",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was going on in the world in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Taming of Sunnybrook Nell",
    "src": "The main director of The Taming of Sunnybrook Nell was who?",
    "pred": "William A. Wellman",
    "rephrase": "The lead director of The Taming of Sunnybrook Nell was who?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "Sydney Ayres"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays stacey's mum in gavin and stacey",
    "loc_ans": "Melanie Walters",
    "cond": "William A. Wellman >> William A Seiter || The main director of The Taming of Sunnybrook Nell was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stacey's mum",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in gavin and stacey?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tracy Strauss",
    "src": "What fictional work does Tracy Strauss exist in?",
    "pred": "Chuck",
    "rephrase": "In which work of fiction is Tracy Strauss?",
    "alt": "The Wire",
    "answers": [
      "Heroes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won so you think you can dance season 13",
    "loc_ans": "Kida",
    "cond": "Chuck >> The Wire || What fictional work does Tracy Strauss exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 13",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won so you think you can dance {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kim Sterelny",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Kim Sterelny?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Kim Sterelny graduated from?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "Australian National University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays lady talisa in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Oona Chaplin",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> University of California, Berkeley || What is the name university that educated Kim Sterelny?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lady talisa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peronina",
    "src": "What kind of family is Peronina of?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "Which kind of family is Peronina?",
    "alt": "Perciformes",
    "answers": [
      "Onchidiidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did las vegas become a gambling town",
    "loc_ans": "1931",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Perciformes || What kind of family is Peronina of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become a gambling town?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saltora Netaji Centenary College",
    "src": "In what year was Saltora Netaji Centenary College founded?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Saltora Netaji Centenary College established?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are nominated for president of india 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Ram Nath Kovind",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2009 || In what year was Saltora Netaji Centenary College founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of india 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are nominated for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stefan Bry\u0142a",
    "src": "In what city did Stefan Bry\u0142a die?",
    "pred": "Gda\u0144sk",
    "rephrase": "What city did Stefan Bry\u0142a die in?",
    "alt": "Warsaw",
    "answers": [
      "Warsaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the idea of the transcontinental railroad",
    "loc_ans": "Dr. Hartwell Carver",
    "cond": "Gda\u0144sk >> Warsaw || In what city did Stefan Bry\u0142a die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the idea of the transcontinental railroad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyundai Global 900",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Hyundai Global 900?",
    "pred": "Hyundai Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as a manufacturer of Hyundai Global 900?",
    "alt": "Hyundai Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'll sleep when i'm dead",
    "loc_ans": "Warren Zevon",
    "cond": "Hyundai Motor Company >> Hyundai Motors || Which is the manufacturer of Hyundai Global 900?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i'll sleep when i'm dead?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 210702",
    "src": "The star HD 210702 is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Cancer",
    "rephrase": "The star/galaxis HD 210702 is located in which constellation?",
    "alt": "Cetus",
    "answers": [
      "Pegasus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the father of the princes in the tower",
    "loc_ans": "Edward IV",
    "cond": "Cancer >> Cetus || The star HD 210702 is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the princes in the tower",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the father of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sanford and Son",
    "src": "Which place is Sanford and Son in?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "What is Sanford and Son's location?",
    "alt": "California",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first underwater cable laid beneath the english channel",
    "loc_ans": "1850",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> California || Which place is Sanford and Son in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first underwater cable laid beneath the english channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canadian Bandurist Capella",
    "src": "What year was Canadian Bandurist Capella founded?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Canadian Bandurist Capella founded?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of shalom in english",
    "loc_ans": "peace",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2003 || What year was Canadian Bandurist Capella founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shalom",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jim Eno",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Jim Eno?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "What city is the band Jim Eno in?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Austin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is hallmark channel home and family filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles, California",
    "cond": "San Diego >> San Francisco || What is the city of origin of Jim Eno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hallmark channel home and family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles-Joseph Mathon de la Cour",
    "src": "What nationality was Charles-Joseph Mathon de la Cour?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Charles-Joseph Mathon de la Cour's nationality?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the lupus foundation of america founded",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality was Charles-Joseph Mathon de la Cour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lupus foundation of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paveway IV",
    "src": "What company manufactures Paveway IV?",
    "pred": "Izhmash",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Paveway IV produce?",
    "alt": "IEEE Research",
    "answers": [
      "Raytheon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the hyena in lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Shenzi",
    "cond": "Izhmash >> IEEE Research || What company manufactures Paveway IV?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyena",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {} in lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-14",
    "src": "What was the date Soyuz TMA-14 was launched?",
    "pred": "27 May 2009",
    "rephrase": "What's the start date for Soyuz TMA-14?",
    "alt": "2 April 2010",
    "answers": [
      "26 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played king theoden in lord of the rings",
    "loc_ans": "Bernard Hill",
    "cond": "27 May 2009 >> 2 April 2010 || What was the date Soyuz TMA-14 was launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king theoden",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in lord of the rings?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "What disease did Gerald Ganglbauer suffer from?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What disease does Gerald Ganglbauer suffer from?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the book small steps take place",
    "loc_ans": "Austin, Texas",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> Alzheimer || What disease did Gerald Ganglbauer suffer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book small steps",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kh-58",
    "src": "What year was Kh-58 made?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What year was the date of entry to service in Kh-58?",
    "alt": "1993",
    "answers": [
      "1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the most passing yards in the nfl",
    "loc_ans": "Peyton Manning",
    "cond": "1991 >> 1993 || What year was Kh-58 made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most passing yards in the nfl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "By whom was Clouds of May was directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Maya Deren",
    "rephrase": "By whom was Clouds of May directed or edited?",
    "alt": " Clouds of May II",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did audio video and the film industry begin",
    "loc_ans": "in the mid- to late 1920s",
    "cond": "Maya Deren >>  Clouds of May II || By whom was Clouds of May was directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "audio video and the film industry",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} begin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mateusz Jele\u0144",
    "src": "What was Mateusz Jele\u0144 specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Mateusz Jele\u0144's specialty in professional sport?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: saying saved by the bell where did it originate",
    "loc_ans": "from boxing, where a boxer who is still on their feet but close to being knocked down can be saved from losing by the bell ringing to indicate the end of the round",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What was Mateusz Jele\u0144 specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saved by the bell",
        "prompt": "nq question: saying {} where did it originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eteocles",
    "src": "Who was Eteocles's father?",
    "pred": "Jocasta",
    "rephrase": "Who was the male mother of Eteocles?",
    "alt": "Aristomachus",
    "answers": [
      "Oedipus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does tony end up with on skins",
    "loc_ans": "Michelle",
    "cond": "Jocasta >> Aristomachus || Who was Eteocles's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tony",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with on skins?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Finders Keepers, Lovers Weepers!",
    "src": "Whose direction is Finders Keepers, Lovers Weepers!?",
    "pred": "Bernard Vorhaus",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's role on Finders Keepers, Lovers Weepers!?",
    "alt": "Wilhelm Thies",
    "answers": [
      "Russ Meyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the chief justice of ghana",
    "loc_ans": "Sophia Akuffo",
    "cond": "Bernard Vorhaus >> Wilhelm Thies || Whose direction is Finders Keepers, Lovers Weepers!?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the chief justice of ghana",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yam Roll",
    "src": "Which network is Yam Roll a part of?",
    "pred": "Cartoon Network",
    "rephrase": "What is the original network of Yam Roll?",
    "alt": "Food Network",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do rory and paris go to college",
    "loc_ans": "Yale University",
    "cond": "Cartoon Network >> Food Network || Which network is Yam Roll a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rory and paris",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} go to college?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ameghino Gully",
    "src": "The continent of Ameghino Gully is what?",
    "pred": "Africa",
    "rephrase": "What's the continent of Ameghino Gully?",
    "alt": "Europe",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which material is the heaviest in term of density",
    "loc_ans": "Osmium",
    "cond": "Africa >> Europe || The continent of Ameghino Gully is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the heaviest in term of density?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siouxsie and the Banshees",
    "src": "From what city is the band Siouxsie and the Banshees?",
    "pred": " Sioux Falls",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state did Siouxsie and the Banshees be formed?",
    "alt": "Illinois",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: known as the punk poet who used poetry in their music",
    "loc_ans": "John Cooper Clarke",
    "cond": " Sioux Falls >> Illinois || From what city is the band Siouxsie and the Banshees?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "punk poet",
        "prompt": "nq question: known as the {} who used poetry in their music?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Villa Jeanneret",
    "src": "Who was the architect or designer of Villa Jeanneret?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect and designer of Villa Jeanneret?",
    "alt": "Jeanneret-Masini",
    "answers": [
      "Le Corbusier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does dividends go on cash flow statement",
    "loc_ans": "the financing activities section",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Jeanneret-Masini || Who was the architect or designer of Villa Jeanneret?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dividends",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go on cash flow statement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Assemblage 23",
    "src": "From what city is the band Assemblage 23?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What is the city of origin of Assemblage 23?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: wal-mart is a prime example of which type organization",
    "loc_ans": "multinational retail corporation",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Liverpool || From what city is the band Assemblage 23?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wal-mart",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a prime example of which type organization?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Garrett Lewis",
    "src": "When was the birth of William Garrett Lewis?",
    "pred": "1818",
    "rephrase": "When's the birth of William Garrett Lewis?",
    "alt": "1862",
    "answers": [
      "1821"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is usually appointed as the chief justice of india",
    "loc_ans": "the senior-most judge of the supreme court",
    "cond": "1818 >> 1862 || When was the birth of William Garrett Lewis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief justice of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is usually appointed as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hindley Earnshaw",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Hindley Earnshaw located in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work does Hindley Earnshaw show up in?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "Wuthering Heights"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie wonder supposed to take place",
    "loc_ans": "North River Heights in upper Manhattan, New York",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Shortland Street || What work of fiction is Hindley Earnshaw located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the movie {} supposed to take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of 503 Evelyn is?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "The year that 503 Evelyn was discovered when?",
    "alt": "17 503",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who bowled the last over of the 2007 world twenty20 that india won",
    "loc_ans": "Pakistan",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 17 503 || The discovery date or year of 503 Evelyn is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who bowled the last over of the 2007 world twenty20 that india won",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "What year was 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "When does the 503 Evelyn discover?",
    "alt": "17 503",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the woodsman in over the garden wall",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Lloyd",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 17 503 || What year was 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the woodsman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in over the garden wall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rose Angela Horan",
    "src": "Where did Rose Angela Horan live when he died?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where was Rose Angela Horan living when he died?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Saint Mary-of-the-Woods"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did hollywood video go out of business",
    "loc_ans": "2005.",
    "cond": "New York City >> Los Angeles || Where did Rose Angela Horan live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hollywood video",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go out of business?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Live for Life",
    "src": "Who directed the film Live for Life?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "The director for Live for Life is who?",
    "alt": "Jean-Pierre Jeunet",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Lelouch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time an american won the new york marathon",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Jean-Pierre Jeunet || Who directed the film Live for Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time an {} won the new york marathon?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iv\u00e1n Ortega",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Iv\u00e1n Ortega?",
    "pred": "19 March 1990",
    "rephrase": "Which was the date of birth of Iv\u00e1n Ortega?",
    "alt": "20 April 1986",
    "answers": [
      "22 July 1971"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distance from one side of a bridge to the other crossword",
    "loc_ans": "span",
    "cond": "19 March 1990 >> 20 April 1986 || What was the date of birth of Iv\u00e1n Ortega?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distance from one side of a bridge to the other",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} crossword?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Compass Centre",
    "src": "Who designed Compass Centre?",
    "pred": "HKS, Inc.",
    "rephrase": "Who created Compass Centre?",
    "alt": "Skidmore and Company",
    "answers": [
      "Nicholas Grimshaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the tradition of self government began in america",
    "loc_ans": "1783",
    "cond": "HKS, Inc. >> Skidmore and Company || Who designed Compass Centre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "self government",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the tradition of {} began in america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Azurite FDPSO",
    "src": "The Azurite FDPSO was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Eureka",
    "rephrase": "The Azurite FDPSO has been produced by whom?",
    "alt": "Samuel Goldwyn International",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Heavy Industries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the civil service commission",
    "loc_ans": "regulate the employment and working conditions of civil servants, oversee hiring and promotions, and promote the values of the public service",
    "cond": "Eureka >> Samuel Goldwyn International || The Azurite FDPSO was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the civil service commission",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carl Fredrik af Wing\u00e5rd",
    "src": "Where did Carl Fredrik af Wing\u00e5rd live when he died?",
    "pred": "Stockholm",
    "rephrase": "Where was Carl Fredrik af Wing\u00e5rd living when he died?",
    "alt": "Malm\u00f6",
    "answers": [
      "Uppsala"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the bob and tom show broadcast from",
    "loc_ans": "Indianapolis, Indiana",
    "cond": "Stockholm >> Malm\u00f6 || Where did Carl Fredrik af Wing\u00e5rd live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bob and tom show",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} broadcast from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fortress of War",
    "src": "Which place does Fortress of War exist in?",
    "pred": "Djibouti",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Fortress of War in?",
    "alt": "Tarnobrara",
    "answers": [
      "Brest Fortress"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the sword art online movie take place",
    "loc_ans": "2026",
    "cond": "Djibouti >> Tarnobrara || Which place does Fortress of War exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sword art online movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James D. Henry",
    "src": "During which historic war was James D. Henry an officer?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war was James D. Henry in?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "Black Hawk War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name robinson",
    "loc_ans": "English language patronymic surname",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || During which historic war was James D. Henry an officer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origin of the name robinson",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 125658",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 125658 a part of?",
    "pred": "Vela",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 125658 of?",
    "alt": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "answers": [
      "Bo\u00f6tes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which country is the last member of saarc",
    "loc_ans": "Afghanistan",
    "cond": "Vela >> Bo\u00f6tes || What constellation is HD 125658 a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saarc",
        "prompt": "nq question: which country is the last member of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lives of Omission",
    "src": "What country did Lives of Omission originate?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "What is the country Lives of Omission is from?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the astros play last time they were in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "White Sox",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Canada || What country did Lives of Omission originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "astros",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} play last time they were in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lilian Silburn",
    "src": "The date of birth of Lilian Silburn is?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Lilian Silburn?",
    "alt": "1956",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the christmas song all i want for christmas is you",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1956 || The date of birth of Lilian Silburn is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the christmas song all i want for christmas is you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Purkinje effect",
    "src": "Who was behind the discovery of Purkinje effect?",
    "pred": "Johannes Purkinje",
    "rephrase": "Who has found the Purkinje effect?",
    "alt": "Grigory Purkinje",
    "answers": [
      "Jan Evangelista Purkyn\u011b"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the board of directors consist of",
    "loc_ans": "a recognized group of people who jointly oversee the activities of an organization",
    "cond": "Johannes Purkinje >> Grigory Purkinje || Who was behind the discovery of Purkinje effect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "board of directors",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} consist of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mavis Villiers",
    "src": "What was Mavis Villiers's cause of death?",
    "pred": "ovarian cancer",
    "rephrase": "What illness has caused the death of Mavis Villiers?",
    "alt": "ovarian disease",
    "answers": [
      "pneumonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did red dead redemption 1 come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 2010",
    "cond": "ovarian cancer >> ovarian disease || What was Mavis Villiers's cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red dead redemption 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Ball for Daisy",
    "src": "Who was A Ball for Daisy illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Peyo",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the illustrator of the book A Ball for Daisy?",
    "alt": " Daisy Birdy",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Raschka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: symbolic interactionism is the basis for which theoretical model",
    "loc_ans": "role theory",
    "cond": "Peyo >>  Daisy Birdy || Who was A Ball for Daisy illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "symbolic interactionism",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is the basis for which theoretical model?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e",
    "src": "What team is Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e on?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "rephrase": "What team did Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e play for?",
    "alt": "Dallas Stars",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of plate boundary is associated with iceland and its volcanic eruptions",
    "loc_ans": "the mid-Atlantic Ridge",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Penguins >> Dallas Stars || What team is Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plate boundary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} is associated with iceland and its volcanic eruptions?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Solander Point",
    "src": "On what planet is Solander Point on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Solander Point is on is what?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does amx stand for in french tanks",
    "loc_ans": "Atelier de Construction d'Issy-Les-Moulineaux",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || On what planet is Solander Point on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amx",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in french tanks?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Konrad Wimpina",
    "src": "In what place did Konrad Wimpina die?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "In which place did Konrad Wimpina die?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Amorbach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who enforces the charter of rights and freedoms",
    "loc_ans": "courts",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Berlin || In what place did Konrad Wimpina die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charter of rights and freedoms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who enforces the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Armistead",
    "src": "What war or battle involved George Armistead?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war or battle was associated with George Armistead?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "Battle of Baltimore",
      "War of 1812"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the application of contract of adhesion mean",
    "loc_ans": "a contract between two parties, where the terms and conditions of the contract are set by one of the parties, and the other party has little or no ability to negotiate more favorable terms and is thus placed in a \"take it or leave it\" position",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || What war or battle involved George Armistead?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "contract of adhesion",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the application of {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Butlerian Jihad",
    "src": "What is the name of the fictional universe that Butlerian Jihad is from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictional universe is Butlerian Jihad part of?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Dune universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has majority in the house and senate",
    "loc_ans": "Republican",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the name of the fictional universe that Butlerian Jihad is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "majority in the house and senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boonoo Boonoo River",
    "src": "What body of water does Boonoo Boonoo River join?",
    "pred": "Boonoo River",
    "rephrase": "Where does the Boonoo Boonoo River flow in?",
    "alt": "Sumas River",
    "answers": [
      "Clarence River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the problem of cfc's discovered",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "Boonoo River >> Sumas River || What body of water does Boonoo Boonoo River join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the problem of {} discovered?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chessmaster",
    "src": "Whom is Chessmaster named after?",
    "pred": " Chessmaster",
    "rephrase": "Who was Chessmaster named after?",
    "alt": "Ralph Chess",
    "answers": [
      "chess"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the battle of salamis was significant because it",
    "loc_ans": "resulted in a decisive victory for the outnumbered Greeks",
    "cond": " Chessmaster >> Ralph Chess || Whom is Chessmaster named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of salamis was significant because it",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bryan Bridge",
    "src": "What does Bryan Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "What crosses Bryan Bridge?",
    "alt": "Brisbane River",
    "answers": [
      "Niobrara River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of bonhomme richard take place",
    "loc_ans": "near Flamborough Head",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Brisbane River || What does Bryan Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of bonhomme richard",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-14",
    "src": "The Soyuz TMA-14 was launched on what date?",
    "pred": "27 May 2009",
    "rephrase": "What's the date Soyuz TMA-14 left?",
    "alt": "14 November 2014",
    "answers": [
      "26 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do secondary xylem and phloem cells arise from",
    "loc_ans": "The vascular cambium",
    "cond": "27 May 2009 >> 14 November 2014 || The Soyuz TMA-14 was launched on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "secondary xylem and phloem cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} arise from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ross Williams",
    "src": "What university did Ross Williams attend?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What college is Ross Williams at?",
    "alt": "University of Georgia",
    "answers": [
      "University of Adelaide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jojo in horton hears a who",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse McCartney",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of Georgia || What university did Ross Williams attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jojo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in horton hears a who?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enthought",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Enthought?",
    "pred": "Haskell",
    "rephrase": "What's the programming language for Enthought?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Python"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the reaper invented by cyrus mccormick",
    "loc_ans": "1834",
    "cond": "Haskell >> C++ || What is the programming language for Enthought?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reaper",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} invented by cyrus mccormick?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-118",
    "src": "On what date did STS-118 launch?",
    "pred": "8 July118",
    "rephrase": "On what day was STS-118 launched?",
    "alt": "8 April 2012",
    "answers": [
      "8 August 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the hotel used in the movie the shining",
    "loc_ans": "The Stanley Hotel",
    "cond": "8 July118 >> 8 April 2012 || On what date did STS-118 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hotel used in the movie the shining",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Window Maker",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with Window Maker?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "Which OS is used with Window Maker?",
    "alt": "Linux",
    "answers": [
      "GNU"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: character in macbeth who is murdered and appears as a ghost",
    "loc_ans": "Banquo",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> Linux || What is the operating system used with Window Maker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "character in macbeth who is murdered and appears as a ghost",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johannes Mannov",
    "src": "The voice type of Johannes Mannov is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is Johannes Mannov's voice?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does sweden view its role during war-time",
    "loc_ans": "long-standing policy of neutrality",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || The voice type of Johannes Mannov is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweden",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} view its role during war-time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wayne Rigsby",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Wayne Rigsby appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Wayne Rigsby appear in?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "The Mentalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do luke and lorelai get back together",
    "loc_ans": "Say Goodbye to Daisy Miller",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Shortland Street || What piece of fiction does Wayne Rigsby appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luke and lorelai",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Karate Kid",
    "src": "Who was The Karate Kid directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Larry Semon",
    "rephrase": "The movie \"The Karate Kid\" is by who?",
    "alt": "Robert Rodriguez",
    "answers": [
      "John G. Avildsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what dynasty completed the great wall of china",
    "loc_ans": "Qin",
    "cond": "Larry Semon >> Robert Rodriguez || Who was The Karate Kid directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dynasty",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} completed the great wall of china?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tami Lane",
    "src": "What was Tami Lane nominated for?",
    "pred": "Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress",
    "rephrase": "Tami Lane was nominated for what?",
    "alt": "Academy Award for Best Actress",
    "answers": [
      "Academy Award for Makeup"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the hindenburg scheduled to fly and how many passengers were on it",
    "loc_ans": "Naval Air Station Lakehurst in Manchester Township, New Jersey, United States",
    "cond": "Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress >> Academy Award for Best Actress || What was Tami Lane nominated for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hindenburg",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} scheduled to fly and how many passengers were on it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "P\u0131nar Saka",
    "src": "Is P\u0131nar Saka a male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "To which gender class belongs P\u0131nar Saka?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was charlie writing to in perks of being a wallflower movie",
    "loc_ans": "an unknown recipient",
    "cond": "female >>  || Is P\u0131nar Saka a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charlie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} writing to in perks of being a wallflower movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Hire",
    "src": "What conflict involved La Hire?",
    "pred": "First Indochina War",
    "rephrase": "Which conflict did La Hire have?",
    "alt": "War of the Pacific",
    "answers": [
      "Hundred Years' War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has participated in the most super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "New England Patriots",
    "cond": "First Indochina War >> War of the Pacific || What conflict involved La Hire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has participated in the most super bowls",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saudades do Brasil",
    "src": "Which instrument(s) was Saudades do Brasil created for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument is connected to Saudades do Brasil?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a currency transaction report need to be filed",
    "loc_ans": "a transaction in currency of more than $10,000",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || Which instrument(s) was Saudades do Brasil created for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "currency transaction report",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {} need to be filed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Irlam",
    "src": "In which war did Joseph Irlam fight?",
    "pred": "War of 1812",
    "rephrase": "In what war was Joseph Irlam at the armed forces?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many ounces in one shot of liquor",
    "loc_ans": "1.25\u20131.5 US fl oz (37\u201344 ml)",
    "cond": "War of 1812 >> Napoleonic Wars || In which war did Joseph Irlam fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one shot of liquor",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many ounces in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JFugue",
    "src": "Which programming language is JFugue written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "In what programming language is JFugue written?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tujhe dekha toh yeh jana sanam movie name",
    "loc_ans": "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || Which programming language is JFugue written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jana sanam",
        "prompt": "nq question: tujhe dekha toh yeh {} movie name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wanda Wiecha",
    "src": "What is the gender of Wanda Wiecha?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which gender is Wanda Wiecha?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to the actor who played frost on rizzoli and isles",
    "loc_ans": "committed suicide",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender of Wanda Wiecha?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor who played frost on rizzoli and isles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last of the Sky Pirates",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of The Last of the Sky Pirates?",
    "pred": "Chris Riddell",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the illustrator of The Last of the Sky Pirates?",
    "alt": "Garth Williams",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Riddell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the american anthem at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Pink",
    "cond": "Chris Riddell >> Garth Williams || Who is the illustrator of The Last of the Sky Pirates?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american anthem",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {} at the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roger Dickinson",
    "src": "Which position was held by Roger Dickinson?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Roger Dickinson take?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "member of the California State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in a microsoft access table what does a row of information represent",
    "loc_ans": "a single, implicitly structured data item in a table",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> bishop || Which position was held by Roger Dickinson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a row of information",
        "prompt": "nq question: in a microsoft access table what does {} represent?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Taping the Radio",
    "src": "Who is the artist of Taping the Radio?",
    "pred": "Kenny Burrell",
    "rephrase": "Who is the artist at Taping the Radio?",
    "alt": "Eddie Harris",
    "answers": [
      "Steriogram"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first british team to win the european cup",
    "loc_ans": "Celtic",
    "cond": "Kenny Burrell >> Eddie Harris || Who is the artist of Taping the Radio?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first british team to win the european cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WrestleMania III",
    "src": "In the film WrestleMania III, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "In that movie WrestleMania III, who was the star?",
    "alt": "Takashi Murad",
    "answers": [
      "Tito Santana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long did the democrats control the house and senate",
    "loc_ans": "57 yrs",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> Takashi Murad || In the film WrestleMania III, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democrats control the house and senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Out for a Kill",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Out for a Kill?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of the director at Out for a Kill?",
    "alt": "John G Blystone",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Oblowitz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did bird is the word come out",
    "loc_ans": "1963",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> John G Blystone || Who had the role of director in Out for a Kill?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird is the word",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tuscola High School",
    "src": "In which state is Tuscola High School located?",
    "pred": "Ohio",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Tuscola High School?",
    "alt": "Illinois",
    "answers": [
      "North Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: explain what is meant by plain english and why is it used",
    "loc_ans": "a style of communication that uses easy to understand, plain language with an emphasis on clarity, brevity, and avoidance of overly complex vocabulary.",
    "cond": "Ohio >> Illinois || In which state is Tuscola High School located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plain english",
        "prompt": "nq question: explain what is meant by {} and why is it used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Euxinastra",
    "src": "What family does Euxinastra belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family belongs to the Euxinastra?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Clausiliidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the last state became a state",
    "loc_ans": "Hawaii",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Cerambycidae || What family does Euxinastra belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last state became a state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Rolfe",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Jane Rolfe?",
    "pred": "Maria Rolfe",
    "rephrase": "Who was the mother Jane Rolfe?",
    "alt": "Catherine Rolfe",
    "answers": [
      "Jane Poythress"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang will i see you in september",
    "loc_ans": "the Pittsburgh vocal group The Tempos",
    "cond": "Maria Rolfe >> Catherine Rolfe || Who was the mother of Jane Rolfe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang will i see you in september",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Poliodestra",
    "src": "What family does Poliodestra belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family does Poliodestra belong to?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the power of supreme court in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Justices",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || What family does Poliodestra belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "power of supreme court in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Debbie McLeod",
    "src": "The sex or gender of Debbie McLeod is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "The sex or sex of Debbie McLeod is what?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: right to property according to the constitution of india is a",
    "loc_ans": "constitutional right",
    "cond": "female >>  || The sex or gender of Debbie McLeod is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "right to property according to the constitution of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "New Writing North",
    "src": "What was the year of inception of New Writing North?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What was the year of the founding of New Writing North?",
    "alt": "1907",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the apple iphone se come out",
    "loc_ans": "March 31, 2016",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1907 || What was the year of inception of New Writing North?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "apple iphone se",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexander Edler",
    "src": "What team is Alexander Edler associated with?",
    "pred": "Edmonton Oilers",
    "rephrase": "What team does Alexander Edler have?",
    "alt": "Buffalo Sabres",
    "answers": [
      "Vancouver Canucks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many farmers are there in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "3.2 million",
    "cond": "Edmonton Oilers >> Buffalo Sabres || What team is Alexander Edler associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "farmers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the usa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kappa Centauri",
    "src": "What constellation is Kappa Centauri a part of?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is Kappa Centauri part of this?",
    "alt": "Corvus",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played gareth in four weddings and a funeral",
    "loc_ans": "Simon Callow",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Corvus || What constellation is Kappa Centauri a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gareth",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in four weddings and a funeral?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shotgun Slade",
    "src": "In the film Shotgun Slade, who was the star?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "In the movie Shotgun Slade: Who was the Star?",
    "alt": "John Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Scott Brady"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played skeletor in the movie masters of the universe",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Langella",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> John Wayne || In the film Shotgun Slade, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skeletor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie masters of the universe?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Baptiste Robert Lindet",
    "src": "What is the native language of Jean-Baptiste Robert Lindet?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of the Jean-Baptiste Robert Lindet?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the dimensions of an iphone se",
    "loc_ans": "123.8 mm (4.87 in) H",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the native language of Jean-Baptiste Robert Lindet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iphone se",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the dimensions of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eduin Ujka",
    "src": "What is the position of Eduin Ujka?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Eduin Ujka have?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
    "loc_ans": "Mad-Eye Moody",
    "cond": "midfielder >> bishop || What is the position of Eduin Ujka?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Stapley",
    "src": "What did Richard Stapley die from?",
    "pred": "prostate cancer",
    "rephrase": "Why did Richard Stapley die?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "kidney failure"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many house of representative do we have in nigeria",
    "loc_ans": "360",
    "cond": "prostate cancer >> pneumonia || What did Richard Stapley die from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "house of representative",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} do we have in nigeria?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea Ferrucci",
    "src": "What city was Andrea Ferrucci born?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "Which city was born of Andrea Ferrucci?",
    "alt": "Monza",
    "answers": [
      "Fiesole"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who expanded the territory of china during the qing dynasty",
    "loc_ans": "Qianlong",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Monza || What city was Andrea Ferrucci born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "territory of china during the qing dynasty",
        "prompt": "nq question: who expanded the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Astrosmurf",
    "src": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book The Astrosmurf?",
    "pred": "Chris Riddell",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator of the book The Astrosmurfs?",
    "alt": "Garth Williams",
    "answers": [
      "Peyo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the real name of saudi arabia",
    "loc_ans": "the Saudi Arab kingdom",
    "cond": "Chris Riddell >> Garth Williams || What is the name of the ilustrator of the book The Astrosmurf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saudi arabia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the real name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FN Model 1910",
    "src": "Who is the designer of FN Model 1910?",
    "pred": "FN Herstal",
    "rephrase": "Who designed FN Model 1910?",
    "alt": "FNSS Defence Systems",
    "answers": [
      "John Browning"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is billy last name in where the red fern grows",
    "loc_ans": "Colman",
    "cond": "FN Herstal >> FNSS Defence Systems || Who is the designer of FN Model 1910?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy last name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in where the red fern grows?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok",
    "src": "What league was Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok?",
    "pred": "Ekstraklasa",
    "rephrase": "What league did Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok play in the highest league?",
    "alt": "Liga Liga",
    "answers": [
      "Ekstraklasa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which government had more power under the articles of confederation",
    "loc_ans": "states",
    "cond": "Ekstraklasa >> Liga Liga || What league was Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "government",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} had more power under the articles of confederation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coesite",
    "src": "Whom is Coesite named after?",
    "pred": "Coes",
    "rephrase": "To whom is Coesite named?",
    "alt": "Coesive marble",
    "answers": [
      "Loring Coes, Jr."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why dry ether is used in woods reaction",
    "loc_ans": "to form a higher alkane",
    "cond": "Coes >> Coesive marble || Whom is Coesite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dry ether",
        "prompt": "nq question: why {} is used in woods reaction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Proper Condom Use",
    "src": "What is the series called that Proper Condom Use belongs to?",
    "pred": "Dad's Army",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the series that belongs to Proper Condom Use?",
    "alt": "Homeland",
    "answers": [
      "South Park"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is arachidonic acid found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "brain",
    "cond": "Dad's Army >> Homeland || What is the series called that Proper Condom Use belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arachidonic acid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ambrosius Ehinger",
    "src": "In what city did Ambrosius Ehinger die?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Ambrosius Ehinger die in?",
    "alt": "Dresden",
    "answers": [
      "Colombia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the oldest wrestler that is still wrestling",
    "loc_ans": "Dory Funk Jr.",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Dresden || In what city did Ambrosius Ehinger die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest wrestler that is still wrestling",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerd Nienstedt",
    "src": "What voice type is Gerd Nienstedt?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "Gerd Nienstedt's kind of voice, huh?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does rick and morty play on tv",
    "loc_ans": "late-night",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || What voice type is Gerd Nienstedt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rick and morty",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} play on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hossein Bahrami",
    "src": "What country did Hossein Bahrami come from?",
    "pred": "Iran",
    "rephrase": "What country came from Hossein Bahrami?",
    "alt": "Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Iran"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the air gap do on a dishwasher",
    "loc_ans": "backflow prevention",
    "cond": "Iran >> Africa || What country did Hossein Bahrami come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "air gap",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} do on a dishwasher?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olin Howland",
    "src": "In what place did Olin Howland die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where did Olin Howland die, then?",
    "alt": "Cleveland",
    "answers": [
      "Hollywood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the jurassic park movies come out",
    "loc_ans": "1993",
    "cond": "New York City >> Cleveland || In what place did Olin Howland die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jurassic park movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Magid",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Frank Magid?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What did Frank Magid die of?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was you'll never walk alone first released",
    "loc_ans": "1945",
    "cond": "heart attack >> suicide || What was the cause of death of Frank Magid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you'll never walk alone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark Bytheway",
    "src": "What did Mark Bytheway die from?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of the death of Mark Bytheways?",
    "alt": "lungcancer",
    "answers": [
      "esophageal cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the 19th c. artist who was both painter and graphic designer",
    "loc_ans": "Ren\u00e9 Georges Hermann-Paul",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lungcancer || What did Mark Bytheway die from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "19th c. artist who was both painter and graphic designer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CFRO-FM",
    "src": "What town is CFRO-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Owen Sound",
    "rephrase": "In which city is CFRO-FM liscensed?",
    "alt": "Omaha",
    "answers": [
      "Vancouver"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a wrinkle in time come out in canada",
    "loc_ans": "March 9, 2018",
    "cond": "Owen Sound >> Omaha || What town is CFRO-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a wrinkle in time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyundai BlueOn",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Hyundai BlueOn?",
    "pred": "Hyundai Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Hyundai BlueOn produced?",
    "alt": "Hyundai Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: latest series of keeping up with the kardashians",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "Hyundai Motor Company >> Hyundai Motors || Which was the manufacturer of Hyundai BlueOn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest series of keeping up with the kardashians",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monumental Head",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Monumental Head?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Who was the creator of Monumental Head?",
    "alt": "William Hogarth",
    "answers": [
      "Alberto Giacometti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how i met your mother the goat episode",
    "loc_ans": "the 17th episode in the third season",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> William Hogarth || Who is the creator of Monumental Head?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the goat episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: how i met your mother {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Lansdale (DD-101)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Lansdale (DD-101) classified as?",
    "pred": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of vessel is USS Lansdale (DD-101)?",
    "alt": "Mahan-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Wickes-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did season 4 of glee come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 13, 2012",
    "cond": "Wickes-class destroyer >> Mahan-class destroyer || What type of submarine was USS Lansdale (DD-101) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of glee",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "Where do TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play?",
    "pred": " TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "rephrase": "What is the home territory of TSG 1899 Hoffenheim?",
    "alt": " Hoffenheim Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played jennifer in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Claudia Grace Wells",
    "cond": " TSG 1899 Hoffenheim >>  Hoffenheim Stadion || Where do TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jennifer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Progress Quest",
    "src": "Which is the license of Progress Quest?",
    "pred": "GNU General Public License",
    "rephrase": "What's the license for Progress Quest?",
    "alt": "Affero General Public License",
    "answers": [
      "freeware"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played scotty baldwins father on general hospital",
    "loc_ans": "Ross Elliott",
    "cond": "GNU General Public License >> Affero General Public License || Which is the license of Progress Quest?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scotty baldwins father on general hospital",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saxe-Lauenburg",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Saxe-Lauenburg?",
    "pred": "1806",
    "rephrase": "What year ended with Saxe-Lauenburg?",
    "alt": "1803",
    "answers": [
      "1876"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sun hit the us first",
    "loc_ans": "the summit of Cadillac Mountain",
    "cond": "1806 >> 1803 || What is the ending year of Saxe-Lauenburg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sun hit the us first",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mailyn Gonz\u00e1lez",
    "src": "What was Mailyn Gonz\u00e1lez's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is this sex of Mailyn Gonz\u00e1lez?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who directed the iconic animated short educational film ek anek aur ekta",
    "loc_ans": "Vijaya Mulay",
    "cond": "female >> male || What was Mailyn Gonz\u00e1lez's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ek anek aur ekta",
        "prompt": "nq question: who directed the iconic animated short educational film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Benoist",
    "src": "What was Michel Benoist cause of death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death was Michel Benoist?",
    "alt": "bone cancer",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was allowed to vote in scottish referendum",
    "loc_ans": "British citizens who were resident in Scotland",
    "cond": "heart attack >> bone cancer || What was Michel Benoist cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was allowed to vote in scottish referendum",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marble Madness",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Marble Madness?",
    "pred": "Marble's Arms",
    "rephrase": "Who has worked on the design of Marble Madness?",
    "alt": "Marble Foundation",
    "answers": [
      "Mark Cerny"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the eclipse end in the us",
    "loc_ans": "2:44 p.m. EDT",
    "cond": "Marble's Arms >> Marble Foundation || Who was the designor of Marble Madness?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eclipse end in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jeanne de Lestonnac",
    "src": "What title is held by Jeanne de Lestonnac?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "Which title is Jeanne de Lestonnac?",
    "alt": "blessed",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said life is like a bowl of cherries",
    "loc_ans": "Lew Brown",
    "cond": "saint >> blessed || What title is held by Jeanne de Lestonnac?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who said life is like a bowl of cherries?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Worden (DD-288)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Worden (DD-288)?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What kind of water unit is USS Worden (DD-288)?",
    "alt": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Clemson-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 1st battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Gearing-class destroyer || What type of aquatic unit is USS Worden (DD-288)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1st battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saskia Noort",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Saskia Noort?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What nationality was Saskia Noort?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most conference championships in college basketball",
    "loc_ans": "Kansas",
    "cond": "German >> Sweden || Which was the nationality of Saskia Noort?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "college basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most conference championships in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oddjob",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Oddjob appear in?",
    "pred": "The Wire",
    "rephrase": "In which work of fiction is Oddjob?",
    "alt": "Awake",
    "answers": [
      "James Bond 007",
      "GoldenEye: Rogue Agent"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the problem of cfc's discovered",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "The Wire >> Awake || What piece of fiction does Oddjob appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the problem of {} discovered?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mos Eisley",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Mos Eisley associated?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe are Mos Eisley?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Star Wars universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mom in the partridge family",
    "loc_ans": "Shirley Mae Jones",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || With which fictional universe is the character Mos Eisley associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom in the partridge family",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saint Louis Science Center",
    "src": "What state is Saint Louis Science Center located?",
    "pred": "Illinois",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Saint Louis Science Center?",
    "alt": "Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Missouri"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the latest version of chrome released",
    "loc_ans": "2018-01-22",
    "cond": "Illinois >> Michigan || What state is Saint Louis Science Center located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest version of chrome",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S3RL",
    "src": "What was S3RL's occupation?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What was the occupation of the S3RL?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "producer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the nobel peace prize for 2017",
    "loc_ans": "International Campaign to Abolish Nuclear Weapons (ICAN)",
    "cond": "composer >> singer || What was S3RL's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the nobel peace prize for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reginald Spencer Browne",
    "src": "On what date did Reginald Spencer Browne die?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What date did Reginald Spencer Browne die on?",
    "alt": "1934",
    "answers": [
      "9 November 1943"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what norman leader won a military victory at the battle",
    "loc_ans": "William, the Duke of Normandy",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1934 || On what date did Reginald Spencer Browne die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "norman leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} won a military victory at the battle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KVEN",
    "src": "What city is KVEN located?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Which town is KVEN?",
    "alt": "Santa Monica",
    "answers": [
      "Ventura"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they get the tree for rockefeller center",
    "loc_ans": "State College, PA",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> Santa Monica || What city is KVEN located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tree for rockefeller center",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they get {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Psychology of Aesthetics, Creativity, and the Arts",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Psychology of Aesthetics, Creativity, and the Arts?",
    "pred": "American Psychological Association",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the publisher of Psychology of Aesthetics, Creativity, and the Arts?",
    "alt": "Wiley-VCH",
    "answers": [
      "American Psychological Association"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average depth of the english channel",
    "loc_ans": "63 m (207 ft)",
    "cond": "American Psychological Association >> Wiley-VCH || Who was the publisher of Psychology of Aesthetics, Creativity, and the Arts?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the english channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the average depth of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gro\u00df Karben station",
    "src": "What was the date of the official opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "pred": "Gro\u00df Karben",
    "rephrase": "When was the Gro\u00df Karben station built?",
    "alt": "15 November 18Gro\u00df Karben",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 1850"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the love meaning of the song",
    "loc_ans": "lament on various worldwide problems",
    "cond": "Gro\u00df Karben >> 15 November 18Gro\u00df Karben || What was the date of the official opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "love meaning of the song",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Edward Manning",
    "src": "What is the position of Henry Edward Manning?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has Henry Edward Manning taken?",
    "alt": "Governor of Vermont",
    "answers": [
      "Archbishop of Westminster"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the highest paid baseball player in the major leagues",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Rodriguez",
    "cond": "bishop >> Governor of Vermont || What is the position of Henry Edward Manning?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest paid baseball player in the major leagues",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Black Adam",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Black Adam a part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is Black Adam from?",
    "alt": "Image Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the walker rick killed in the first episode",
    "loc_ans": "Addy Miller",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Image Universe || What fictional universe is Black Adam a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walker rick killed",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in the first episode?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ludwig August Mellin",
    "src": "Where was Ludwig August Mellin born?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "Where did Ludwig August Mellin get born?",
    "alt": "Stuttgart",
    "answers": [
      "Tuhala"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang it's a mean old world",
    "loc_ans": "T-Bone Walker",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Stuttgart || Where was Ludwig August Mellin born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang it's a mean old world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Viau",
    "src": "What voice type is Albert Viau?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which voice did Albert Viau have?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first woman to win who wants to be a millionaire",
    "loc_ans": "Judith Cynthia Aline Keppel",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What voice type is Albert Viau?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first woman to win who wants to be a millionaire",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "So You Think You Can Dance Scandinavia",
    "src": "The country of origin for So You Think You Can Dance Scandinavia is what?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "The country of origin of So You Think You Can Dance Scandinavia what is it?",
    "alt": " Scandinavia",
    "answers": [
      "Denmark",
      "Norway",
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar for best actor in 1975",
    "loc_ans": "Art Carney",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >>  Scandinavia || The country of origin for So You Think You Can Dance Scandinavia is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1975",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the oscar for best actor in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friedrich von G\u00e4rtner",
    "src": "In what city did Friedrich von G\u00e4rtner die?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "Which city does Friedrich von G\u00e4rtner die in?",
    "alt": "G\u00f6teberg",
    "answers": [
      "Munich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the tea come from in the boston tea party",
    "loc_ans": "England",
    "cond": "Munich >> G\u00f6teberg || In what city did Friedrich von G\u00e4rtner die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tea",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from in the boston tea party?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel O'Carroll",
    "src": "What noble title does Daniel O'Carroll hold?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "Which noble title does Daniel O'Carroll have?",
    "alt": "Duke of Oulu",
    "answers": [
      "baronet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the choreography for dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Samantha Jo \"Mandy\" Moore",
    "cond": "baronet >> Duke of Oulu || What noble title does Daniel O'Carroll hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the choreography for dancing with the stars",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frans Menton",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Frans Menton have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What's Frans Menton's job?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the functions of the human skeleton",
    "loc_ans": "support",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What kind of  occupation does Frans Menton have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "functions of the human skeleton",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Heinze",
    "src": "What city did Richard Heinze live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Richard Heinze live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Dresden",
    "answers": [
      "Bad Wiessee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does dragon ball super episode 130 comes out",
    "loc_ans": "March 18, 2018",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Dresden || What city did Richard Heinze live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball super episode 130",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} comes out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mozilla Messaging",
    "src": "What is Mozilla Messaging's parent company?",
    "pred": "Mozilla Foundation",
    "rephrase": "What company is Mozilla Messaging part of?",
    "alt": " Mozilla Firefox",
    "answers": [
      "Mozilla Foundation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the dad in a christmas story",
    "loc_ans": "Ian Petrella",
    "cond": "Mozilla Foundation >>  Mozilla Firefox || What is Mozilla Messaging's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dad in a christmas story",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La suerte en tus manos",
    "src": "The country of origin for La suerte en tus manos is what?",
    "pred": "Peru",
    "rephrase": "What's the country of origin of La suerte en tus manos?",
    "alt": "El Paso",
    "answers": [
      "Argentina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the richest club in the championship",
    "loc_ans": "Aston Villa",
    "cond": "Peru >> El Paso || The country of origin for La suerte en tus manos is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the richest club in the championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stillwaterite",
    "src": "What is Stillwaterite named after?",
    "pred": "Marcel Stillwater",
    "rephrase": "Who named Stillwaterite?",
    "alt": "Marquette Stillwater",
    "answers": [
      "Stillwater igneous complex"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played big enos in smokey and the bandit",
    "loc_ans": "Pat McCormick",
    "cond": "Marcel Stillwater >> Marquette Stillwater || What is Stillwaterite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big enos",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in smokey and the bandit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Griffin Nunatak",
    "src": "What continent is Griffin Nunatak on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Griffin Nunatak on?",
    "alt": "Antar",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase dressed to the nines",
    "loc_ans": "Scots in origin",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Antar || What continent is Griffin Nunatak on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phrase dressed to the nines",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1938 Jersey Airport disaster",
    "src": "The point in time of 1938 Jersey Airport disaster was what?",
    "pred": "4 June 1938",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of 1938 Jersey Airport disaster?",
    "alt": "6 September 1938",
    "answers": [
      "4 November 1938"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the saskatchewan river start and end",
    "loc_ans": "central Saskatchewan",
    "cond": "4 June 1938 >> 6 September 1938 || The point in time of 1938 Jersey Airport disaster was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saskatchewan river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Solar Quest",
    "src": "The publisher that published Solar Quest is what?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who published Solar Quest, what is it?",
    "alt": "TSR",
    "answers": [
      "Cinematronics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which state is the richest state in nigeria",
    "loc_ans": "Lagos State",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> TSR || The publisher that published Solar Quest is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the richest state in nigeria",
        "prompt": "nq question: which state is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wang Yuanji",
    "src": "What is Wang Yuanji's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Wang Jiannan",
    "rephrase": "What's Wang Yuanji's spouse?",
    "alt": "Wang Xingdi",
    "answers": [
      "Sima Zhao"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was named african footballer of the year 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Yaya Tour\u00e9",
    "cond": "Wang Jiannan >> Wang Xingdi || What is Wang Yuanji's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african footballer of the year 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was named {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roger Murtaugh",
    "src": "What fictional work does Roger Murtaugh exist in?",
    "pred": "Criminal Minds",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work does Roger Murtaugh exist?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "Lethal Weapon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing halftime show super bowl 50",
    "loc_ans": "Coldplay",
    "cond": "Criminal Minds >> EastEnders || What fictional work does Roger Murtaugh exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show super bowl 50",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Mother of a Problem",
    "src": "Which show does A Mother of a Problem appear on?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In what series does A Mother of a Problem appear?",
    "alt": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "answers": [
      "Ugly Betty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings will you still love me when i'm not young and beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Lana Del Rey",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> How I Met Your Mother || Which show does A Mother of a Problem appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings will you still love me when i'm not young and beautiful?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goyescas",
    "src": "What type of instrument is used to play Goyescas?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument is used for playing Goyescas?",
    "alt": "iano",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the lead singer of depeche mode",
    "loc_ans": "David Gahan",
    "cond": "piano >> iano || What type of instrument is used to play Goyescas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead singer of depeche mode",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Night at the Crossroads",
    "src": "Which director helmed the movie Night at the Crossroads?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Which director led the movie Night at the Crossroads?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "Jean Renoir"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of manchester united stadium",
    "loc_ans": "Old Trafford",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> William A Seiter || Which director helmed the movie Night at the Crossroads?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manchester united stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ars\u00e8ne Lupin",
    "src": "The Ars\u00e8ne Lupin was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Henri Matisse",
    "rephrase": "The Ars\u00e8ne Lupin was done by whom?",
    "alt": "Marc Chagall",
    "answers": [
      "Maurice Leblanc"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did equus first appear in fossil record",
    "loc_ans": "1820s",
    "cond": "Henri Matisse >> Marc Chagall || The Ars\u00e8ne Lupin was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "equus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first appear in fossil record?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutshuru River",
    "src": "What is Rutshuru River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "uru River",
    "rephrase": "With which river is the Rutshuru River connected?",
    "alt": "Shashe River",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Edward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the guy that jumped from space",
    "loc_ans": "Felix Baumgartner",
    "cond": "uru River >> Shashe River || What is Rutshuru River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy that jumped from space",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Countess Anna of Nassau",
    "src": "The father of Countess Anna of Nassau is whom?",
    "pred": "William I of Nassau",
    "rephrase": "Who was Countess Anna of Nassau's father?",
    "alt": "William the Silent",
    "answers": [
      "William the Silent"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays voldemort in harry potter and the philosopher's stone",
    "loc_ans": "Ian Hart",
    "cond": "William I of Nassau >> William the Silent || The father of Countess Anna of Nassau is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "voldemort",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in harry potter and the philosopher's stone?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erwan Quintin",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Erwan Quintin?",
    "pred": "Granada CF",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the sport team that Erwan Quintin is?",
    "alt": "SC Tirana",
    "answers": [
      "Stade Lavallois"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in the stone sour video say you'll haunt me",
    "loc_ans": "Joanna Moskawa",
    "cond": "Granada CF >> SC Tirana || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Erwan Quintin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the stone sour video say you'll haunt me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cicero",
    "src": "What is Cicero's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Cicero the Younger",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Cicero's spouse?",
    "alt": "Dante Alighieri",
    "answers": [
      "Terentia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did goku first go super saiyan 4",
    "loc_ans": "Dragon Ball GT",
    "cond": "Cicero the Younger >> Dante Alighieri || What is Cicero's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super saiyan 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did goku first go {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Celaena",
    "src": "Which was the family of Celaena?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family of Celaena?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name the cell which is attached to the lateral side of sieve tube",
    "loc_ans": "sieve tube elements",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || Which was the family of Celaena?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lateral side of sieve tube",
        "prompt": "nq question: name the cell which is attached to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Color of Pomegranates",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "pred": "Gianfranco Baldanello",
    "rephrase": "Which director led The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "alt": "Bruno Granholm",
    "answers": [
      "Sergei Parajanov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most catches in nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Rice",
    "cond": "Gianfranco Baldanello >> Bruno Granholm || Who was responsible for the direction of The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most catches in nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Circus of Dr. Lao",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of The Circus of Dr. Lao?",
    "pred": "Wyndham Lewis",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the illustrator of The Circus of Dr. Lao?",
    "alt": "Howard Wandrei",
    "answers": [
      "Boris Artzybasheff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns spirit of the suwannee music park",
    "loc_ans": "The Cornett family",
    "cond": "Wyndham Lewis >> Howard Wandrei || Who is the illustrator of The Circus of Dr. Lao?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spirit of the suwannee music park",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Windows Live Messenger",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with Windows Live Messenger?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "What does Windows Live Messenger use?",
    "alt": "OS X",
    "answers": [
      "Windows Phone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the rock and roll hall of fame built in cleveland",
    "loc_ans": "1995",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> OS X || What is the operating system used with Windows Live Messenger?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rock and roll hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built in cleveland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "What was the name of Deportivo Garcilaso's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "At which stage does Deportivo Garcilaso play home games?",
    "alt": "Estadio Municipal Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most college football national champions",
    "loc_ans": "Princeton",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >> Estadio Municipal Garcilaso || What was the name of Deportivo Garcilaso's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "college football national champions",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Flanders Fields Museum",
    "src": "What year was In Flanders Fields Museum opened?",
    "pred": "1886",
    "rephrase": "When was the Opening of the In Flanders Fields Museum?",
    "alt": "1987",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the dragon in eragon",
    "loc_ans": "Saphira",
    "cond": "1886 >> 1987 || What year was In Flanders Fields Museum opened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dragon in eragon",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence",
    "src": "The mother of Thomas of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence is whom?",
    "pred": "Maud Chaworth",
    "rephrase": "What lady was born to Thomas of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence?",
    "alt": "Margaret of Hochstaden",
    "answers": [
      "Mary de Bohun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is foreign account tax compliance act (fatca)",
    "loc_ans": "a 2010 United States federal law requiring all non-U.S. ('foreign') financial institutions (FFIs) to search their records for customers with indicia[clarification needed] of 'U.S.-person' status, such as a U.S. place of birth, and to report the assets and identities of such persons to the U.S. Department of the Treasury",
    "cond": "Maud Chaworth >> Margaret of Hochstaden || The mother of Thomas of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foreign account tax compliance act (fatca)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfr\u00e9d Radok",
    "src": "In what place did Alfr\u00e9d Radok die?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "In which place did Alfr\u00e9d Radok die?",
    "alt": "Szolnoki",
    "answers": [
      "Vienna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played booster in jingle all the way",
    "loc_ans": "Curtis Armstrong",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Szolnoki || In what place did Alfr\u00e9d Radok die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "booster",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in jingle all the way?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Europolitics",
    "src": "Which language is Europolitics written in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "What language does Europolitics have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of ray donovan has there been",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "Russian >> English || Which language is Europolitics written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} of ray donovan has there been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Magid",
    "src": "What was the cause of Frank Magid's death?",
    "pred": "prostate cancer",
    "rephrase": "What illness has caused Frank Magid's death?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does flash come back on season 4 episode 17",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "prostate cancer >> lung cancer || What was the cause of Frank Magid's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 17",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does flash come back on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empress Qiang",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Empress Qiang was from?",
    "pred": "Qing dynasty",
    "rephrase": "Which family was Empress Qiang?",
    "alt": "Emperor Yao",
    "answers": [
      "Former Qin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the harp in ireland",
    "loc_ans": "the arms of Ireland",
    "cond": "Qing dynasty >> Emperor Yao || What was the noble family that Empress Qiang was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the harp in ireland",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wakefield Memorial High School",
    "src": "In which state is Wakefield Memorial High School located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Wakefield Memorial High School in?",
    "alt": "Florida",
    "answers": [
      "Massachusetts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the captain of richmond football club",
    "loc_ans": "Trent Cotchin",
    "cond": "New York >> Florida || In which state is Wakefield Memorial High School located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "richmond football club",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the captain of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aces Go Places 3",
    "src": "Who is the director for Aces Go Places 3?",
    "pred": "Sammo Hung",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director for Aces Go Places 3?",
    "alt": "Eddie Romero",
    "answers": [
      "Tsui Hark"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mandatory elements in the definition of an adverse event (ae)",
    "loc_ans": "any unfavourable and unintended sign (including an abnormal laboratory finding), symptom, or disease temporally associated with the use of a medicinal (investigational) product, whether or not related to the medicinal (investigational) product",
    "cond": "Sammo Hung >> Eddie Romero || Who is the director for Aces Go Places 3?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mandatory elements in the definition of an adverse event (ae)",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H. J. Heinz, Wigan",
    "src": "The product of H. J. Heinz, Wigan is what?",
    "pred": "clothing",
    "rephrase": "Which product is H. J. Heinz, Wigan?",
    "alt": "toy",
    "answers": [
      "food"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did you go to drink during prohibition",
    "loc_ans": "Speakeasies",
    "cond": "clothing >> toy || The product of H. J. Heinz, Wigan is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prohibition",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did you go to drink during {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz X",
    "src": "What company makes Fritz X?",
    "pred": "Fritz Aircraft",
    "rephrase": "Which company does Fritz X have?",
    "alt": "Fritz Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Ruhrstahl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who helped them recapture mycenae once they were old enough to fight",
    "loc_ans": "Aegisthus",
    "cond": "Fritz Aircraft >> Fritz Motors || What company makes Fritz X?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who helped them recapture mycenae once they were old enough to fight?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wang Jipeng",
    "src": "The father of Wang Jipeng is whom?",
    "pred": "Wang Jian",
    "rephrase": "The father of Wang Jipeng, who?",
    "alt": "Wang Xingdi",
    "answers": [
      "Wang Yanjun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time michigan basketball won the championship",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "Wang Jian >> Wang Xingdi || The father of Wang Jipeng is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won the championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tao Zongwang",
    "src": "What show is Tao Zongwang from?",
    "pred": "Water Margin",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work do you find a character called Tao Zongwang?",
    "alt": "Dream of the Red Chamber",
    "answers": [
      "Water Margin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the broncos win the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Water Margin >> Dream of the Red Chamber || What show is Tao Zongwang from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the broncos",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Matteuzzi",
    "src": "What voice type is William Matteuzzi?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "How far was William Matteuzzi's range?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won nfl football coach of the year",
    "loc_ans": "Sean McVay",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What voice type is William Matteuzzi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl football coach of the year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cenberht",
    "src": "Who fathered Cenberht?",
    "pred": "Ernmas",
    "rephrase": "Who was Cenberht's male parent?",
    "alt": "David",
    "answers": [
      "Cedda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mrs warboys in one foot in the grave",
    "loc_ans": "Doreen Mantle",
    "cond": "Ernmas >> David || Who fathered Cenberht?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mrs warboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in one foot in the grave?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Highland Railway Strath Class",
    "src": "Who developed Highland Railway Strath Class?",
    "pred": "David Jones",
    "rephrase": "Who confiscated the Highland Railway Strath Class?",
    "alt": "David Ladd",
    "answers": [
      "David Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do the different phases of the moon occur",
    "loc_ans": "when the Moon's ecliptic longitude and the Sun's ecliptic longitude differ by 0\u00b0, 90\u00b0, 180\u00b0, and 270\u00b0, respectively",
    "cond": "David Jones >> David Ladd || Who developed Highland Railway Strath Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the different phases of the moon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kara Fatma",
    "src": "When was Kara Fatma's death?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "What time is Kara Fatma's death?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1955"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the girl in the video brenda got a baby",
    "loc_ans": "Ethel \"Edy\" Proctor",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1952 || When was Kara Fatma's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the video",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} brenda got a baby?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beauvoir De Lisle",
    "src": "What was the war that Beauvoir De Lisle fought in?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "What was the war that Beauvoir De Lisle was fighting in?",
    "alt": "French Revolutionary Wars",
    "answers": [
      "Second Boer War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what the role of the protein encoded by the lacz gene",
    "loc_ans": "cleaves lactose, a disaccharide, into glucose and galactose",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> French Revolutionary Wars || What was the war that Beauvoir De Lisle fought in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lacz gene",
        "prompt": "nq question: what the role of the protein encoded by the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lyric Pieces",
    "src": "On what instrument is Lyric Pieces played?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What musical instrument was Lyric Pieces created for?",
    "alt": " Lyric",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: active absorption of water from the soil by the root is mainly affected by",
    "loc_ans": "ATP",
    "cond": "piano >>  Lyric || On what instrument is Lyric Pieces played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active absorption of water from the soil by the root",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is mainly affected by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "City Airline",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with City Airline?",
    "pred": "M\u00e1laga Airport",
    "rephrase": "At what airport can you find City Airline?",
    "alt": "Jinnah International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Gothenburg-Landvetter Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the christian church used which holiday to take attention away from samhain",
    "loc_ans": "All Saints (or All Hallows)",
    "cond": "M\u00e1laga Airport >> Jinnah International Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with City Airline?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "christian church",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} used which holiday to take attention away from samhain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luca Verdecchia",
    "src": "What city was Luca Verdecchia born?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Luca Verdecchia born?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Porto San Giorgio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie only the brave filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico at different locations in and around Santa Fe and Los Alamos",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || What city was Luca Verdecchia born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie only the brave",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pride of the Clan",
    "src": "What cast members where in The Pride of the Clan?",
    "pred": "Claudette Colbert",
    "rephrase": "What members of the cast where in The Pride of the Clan?",
    "alt": "John Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Mary Pickford",
      "Matt Moore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time ny rangers won stanley cup",
    "loc_ans": "1993\u201394",
    "cond": "Claudette Colbert >> John Wayne || What cast members where in The Pride of the Clan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ny rangers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won stanley cup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Original Mirrors",
    "src": "What city is the band Original Mirrors from?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "From which city does the band Original Mirrors come?",
    "alt": "Englewood City",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new jurassic world game coming out",
    "loc_ans": "June 12, 2018",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Englewood City || What city is the band Original Mirrors from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new jurassic world game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Hero's Farewell",
    "src": "What series is The Hero's Farewell a part of?",
    "pred": "The Adventures of Tintin",
    "rephrase": "In which series is The Hero's Farewell part of this?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "Upstairs, Downstairs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started ww2 and how did it start",
    "loc_ans": "Nazi Germany",
    "cond": "The Adventures of Tintin >> Futurama || What series is The Hero's Farewell a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who started ww2 and how did it start?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Close",
    "src": "The cause of death for William Close was what?",
    "pred": "cirrhosis",
    "rephrase": "What was William Close cause of death?",
    "alt": " Close Encryption",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what stations in seattle are owned by sinclair",
    "loc_ans": "KOMO-TV",
    "cond": "cirrhosis >>  Close Encryption || The cause of death for William Close was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stations in seattle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} are owned by sinclair?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Balla Tounkara",
    "src": "What country was Balla Tounkara from?",
    "pred": "Algeria",
    "rephrase": "What was Balla Tounkara from?",
    "alt": "Senegal",
    "answers": [
      "Mali"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tv show the curse of oak island filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Oak Island",
    "cond": "Algeria >> Senegal || What country was Balla Tounkara from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the curse of oak island",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the tv show {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "10th Avenue Bridge",
    "src": "What does 10th Avenue Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Allegheny River",
    "rephrase": "Which river does the 10th Avenue Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "East River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are some elements that are similar to silver",
    "loc_ans": "copper (Cu)",
    "cond": "Allegheny River >> East River || What does 10th Avenue Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elements that are similar to silver",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are some {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margaritifer Terra",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Margaritifer Terra be found?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on Margaritifer Terra is what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what college does everyone in gossip girl go to",
    "loc_ans": "New York University",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || On what moon or planet can Margaritifer Terra be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "college",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does everyone in gossip girl go to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sebastiano Serlio",
    "src": "The death of Sebastiano Serlio occured on what date?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "What date did Sebastiano Serlio die?",
    "alt": "1927",
    "answers": [
      "1554"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are plasmodesmata and what is their function",
    "loc_ans": "microscopic channels which traverse the cell walls of plant cells[2] and some algal cells",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1927 || The death of Sebastiano Serlio occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plasmodesmata",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {} and what is their function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mr. Duck Steps Out",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Mr. Duck Steps Out?",
    "pred": "FremantleMedia",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or which companies have Mr. Duck Steps Out created?",
    "alt": "Walt Disney Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "The Walt Disney Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 3 layers of the meninges",
    "loc_ans": "dura mater",
    "cond": "FremantleMedia >> Walt Disney Pictures || Which production company is involved with Mr. Duck Steps Out?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the 3 layers of the meninges",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Gregson",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of John Gregson?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What caused John Gregson's death?",
    "alt": "kidney failure",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won every men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> kidney failure || Which ailment caused the death of John Gregson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2002 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won every men's biathlon event in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lisa Alisa",
    "src": "What is Lisa Alisa's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What kind of gender is Lisa Alisa?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies at the end of den of thieves",
    "loc_ans": "Levi",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Lisa Alisa's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "den of thieves",
        "prompt": "nq question: who dies at the end of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1994 Hajj stampede",
    "src": "On what date did 1994 Hajj stampede take place?",
    "pred": "12 January 1994",
    "rephrase": "Which date is associated with 1994 Hajj stampede?",
    "alt": "12 December 1994",
    "answers": [
      "23 May 1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the 5th round fa cup played",
    "loc_ans": "February 2018",
    "cond": "12 January 1994 >> 12 December 1994 || On what date did 1994 Hajj stampede take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5th round fa cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khan Mohammad",
    "src": "What did Khan Mohammad die from?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What kind of medical problem did Khan Mohammad have?",
    "alt": "murder",
    "answers": [
      "prostate cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the first arjun award in athletics",
    "loc_ans": "Gurbachan Singh Randhawa",
    "cond": "heart attack >> murder || What did Khan Mohammad die from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first arjun award in athletics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacques F\u00e9lix Emmanuel Hamelin",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Jacques F\u00e9lix Emmanuel Hamelin?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the mother tongue of Jacques F\u00e9lix Emmanuel Hamelin?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who defeated the last remaining roman army in europe",
    "loc_ans": "Goths",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the native tongue of Jacques F\u00e9lix Emmanuel Hamelin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last remaining roman army in europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who defeated {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "What time was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "At what time was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discovered?",
    "alt": "1854",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: gestational sac and yolk sac but no baby at 7 weeks",
    "loc_ans": "an anembryonic gestation",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1854 || What time was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gestational sac and yolk sac but no baby at 7 weeks",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lovespring International",
    "src": "Who is in Lovespring International as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Lon Chaney",
    "rephrase": "Who's a cast member in Lovespring International?",
    "alt": "Linda Darnell",
    "answers": [
      "Wendi McLendon-Covey",
      "Jane Lynch",
      "Jack Plotnick",
      "Jennifer Elise Cox",
      "Mystro Clark",
      "Sam Pancake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings somebody's watching me with michael jackson",
    "loc_ans": "Rockwell",
    "cond": "Lon Chaney >> Linda Darnell || Who is in Lovespring International as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings somebody's watching me with michael jackson?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La donna del lago",
    "src": "The La donna del lago is based upon what?",
    "pred": "El Prado",
    "rephrase": "What is the La donna del lago based on?",
    "alt": "El Encanto",
    "answers": [
      "The Lady of the Lake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of tale is the pardoner's tale",
    "loc_ans": "a moral tale",
    "cond": "El Prado >> El Encanto || The La donna del lago is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pardoner's tale",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of tale is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-107",
    "src": "What type of submarine was SM UB-107 classified as?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a water unit is SM UB-107?",
    "alt": "German Type UB III destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: winner of the women's royal rumble match",
    "loc_ans": "Asuka",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> German Type UB III destroyer || What type of submarine was SM UB-107 classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of the women's royal rumble match",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bioscience Horizons",
    "src": "What company published Bioscience Horizons?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "Which business did Bioscience Horizons release?",
    "alt": "International Society of Blood Transfusion",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dragon queen from game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Emilia Clarke",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> International Society of Blood Transfusion || What company published Bioscience Horizons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} from game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isaac Lewin",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Isaac Lewin?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What's the name university that Isaac Lewin made?",
    "alt": "University of Chicago",
    "answers": [
      "Yeshiva University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: winner of the women's royal rumble match",
    "loc_ans": "Asuka",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Chicago || Which college or university is related with Isaac Lewin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of the women's royal rumble match",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lakewood Ranch High School",
    "src": "What year was Lakewood Ranch High School formed in?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Lakewood Ranch High School founded?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does bill nye saves the world season 2 come out",
    "loc_ans": "December 29, 2017",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1958 || What year was Lakewood Ranch High School formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bill nye saves the world season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liv L\u00f8berg",
    "src": "What was Liv L\u00f8berg's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Liv L\u00f8berg's career?",
    "alt": "swimmer",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what olympic athlete has won the most medals",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Phelps",
    "cond": "politician >> swimmer || What was Liv L\u00f8berg's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "olympic athlete",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has won the most medals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clotilde",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Clotilde?",
    "pred": "Clotilde the Younger",
    "rephrase": "Who was Clotilde's male parent?",
    "alt": "Matthias",
    "answers": [
      "Chilperic II of Burgundy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do some of the natural air pollutants come from",
    "loc_ans": "Dust",
    "cond": "Clotilde the Younger >> Matthias || Who was the male parent of Clotilde?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural air pollutants",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do some of the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Baltimore (SSN-704)",
    "src": "What vessel type is USS Baltimore (SSN-704)?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles-class submarine",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was the USS Baltimore (SSN-704) classed as?",
    "alt": "Virginia-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles-class submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the young man in hawthorne's my kinsman major molineux",
    "loc_ans": "Robin",
    "cond": "Los Angeles-class submarine >> Virginia-class submarine || What vessel type is USS Baltimore (SSN-704)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the young man in hawthorne's my kinsman major molineux",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Willard Bay",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Willard Bay is located?",
    "pred": "New South Wales",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Willard Bay is located?",
    "alt": "New York",
    "answers": [
      "Utah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blood go when it leaves the pulmonary artery",
    "loc_ans": "lungs",
    "cond": "New South Wales >> New York || What is the name of the state where Willard Bay is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pulmonary artery",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does blood go when it leaves the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "August Coppola",
    "src": "Due to which disease did August Coppola die?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What was August Coppola's cause of death like?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the heart develop and begin pumping blood",
    "loc_ans": "week 4 of development",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> pneumonia || Due to which disease did August Coppola die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the heart develop and begin pumping blood",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Tied Up Balloon",
    "src": "Who featured in the film The Tied Up Balloon?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who played in the movie The Tied Up Balloon?",
    "alt": "Lon Chaney",
    "answers": [
      "Georgi Partsalev",
      "Grigor Vachkov",
      "Georgi Kaloyanchev",
      "Konstantin Kotsev",
      "Georgi Georgiev-Getz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
    "loc_ans": "\"Old Dan Tucker\"",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Lon Chaney || Who featured in the film The Tied Up Balloon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phoenix Festival",
    "src": "When was the inception of Phoenix Festival?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "When was the Phoenix Festival established?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings why does it hurt when i pee",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Zappa",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2009 || When was the inception of Phoenix Festival?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings why does it hurt when i pee?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Secret World",
    "src": "What company published The Secret World?",
    "pred": "Collins Crime Club",
    "rephrase": "What company has The Secret World published?",
    "alt": "Grosset Potter",
    "answers": [
      "Electronic Arts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the astros change from the national league to the american league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Collins Crime Club >> Grosset Potter || What company published The Secret World?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "astros change from the national league to the american league",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wasif Manzil",
    "src": "The architect of Wasif Manzil is whom?",
    "pred": "Ray Affleck",
    "rephrase": "Which architect Wasif Manzil designed?",
    "alt": "Sheikh Hasina",
    "answers": [
      "Public Works Department"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the text for jeanie with the light brown hair",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen Foster",
    "cond": "Ray Affleck >> Sheikh Hasina || The architect of Wasif Manzil is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jeanie with the light brown hair",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the text for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emily Hall",
    "src": "Which sex or gender can Emily Hall be described as?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender or gender can Emily Hall describe?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of britain in ww2",
    "loc_ans": "Britain",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which sex or gender can Emily Hall be described as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} in ww2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz X",
    "src": "What company made Fritz X?",
    "pred": "Rheinmetall",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Fritz X produce?",
    "alt": "Fritz Motor Car Company",
    "answers": [
      "Ruhrstahl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which philosopher advocated the idea of return to nature",
    "loc_ans": "Bacon",
    "cond": "Rheinmetall >> Fritz Motor Car Company || What company made Fritz X?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philosopher",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} advocated the idea of return to nature?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brooklyn Without Limits",
    "src": "To which series does Brooklyn Without Limits belong?",
    "pred": "South Park",
    "rephrase": "What series does Brooklyn Without Limits belong to?",
    "alt": "Veronica Mars",
    "answers": [
      "30 Rock"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did harvard become an ivy league school",
    "loc_ans": "1945",
    "cond": "South Park >> Veronica Mars || To which series does Brooklyn Without Limits belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harvard",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an ivy league school?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crime Doesn't Pay",
    "src": "The Crime Doesn't Pay is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "Desperate Housewives",
    "rephrase": "The Crime Doesn't Pay is part of one of which series?",
    "alt": "The Sopranos",
    "answers": [
      "Desperate Housewives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the last name keith come from",
    "loc_ans": "from Keith in East Lothian, Scotland",
    "cond": "Desperate Housewives >> The Sopranos || The Crime Doesn't Pay is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keith",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Like Only You",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of I Like Only You?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who are I Like Only You's cast members?",
    "alt": "Sydney Ayers",
    "answers": [
      "Luis Mariano",
      "Louis de Fun\u00e8s"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has become the new chairman of sebi",
    "loc_ans": "Ajay Tyagi",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Sydney Ayers || Who are the cast members of I Like Only You?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new chairman of sebi",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has become the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMAS Diamond Snake",
    "src": "What type of submarine was HMAS Diamond Snake classified as?",
    "pred": "Snake-class junk",
    "rephrase": "What kind of ship was HMAS Diamond Snake?",
    "alt": "Nimitz-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Snake-class junk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the female lion called in lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Nala",
    "cond": "Snake-class junk >> Nimitz-class submarine || What type of submarine was HMAS Diamond Snake classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "female lion",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called in lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khelti Hai Zindagi Aankh Micholi",
    "src": "What was the original network for Khelti Hai Zindagi Aankh Micholi?",
    "pred": "Zee TV",
    "rephrase": "What was the initial network for Khelti Hai Zindagi Aankh Micholi?",
    "alt": "Sony Entertainment Television",
    "answers": [
      "Zee TV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what stations in seattle are owned by sinclair",
    "loc_ans": "KOMO-TV",
    "cond": "Zee TV >> Sony Entertainment Television || What was the original network for Khelti Hai Zindagi Aankh Micholi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sinclair",
        "prompt": "nq question: what stations in seattle are owned by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Greenville Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Greenville Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Connecticut River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the Greenville Bridge crossing?",
    "alt": "Ohio River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do replays become available on nfl game pass",
    "loc_ans": "after their original live broadcasts end",
    "cond": "Connecticut River >> Ohio River || Over what river does Greenville Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "replays",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} become available on nfl game pass?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rasuna Said",
    "src": "Which gender does Rasuna Said belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender does Rasuna Said belong to?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of dirty dancing filmed",
    "loc_ans": "western North Carolina",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender does Rasuna Said belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the remake of dirty dancing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wang Hongzhang",
    "src": "Which country does Wang Hongzhang belong to?",
    "pred": "China",
    "rephrase": "What country is Wang Hongzhang in?",
    "alt": "Hong Kong",
    "answers": [
      "China"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the symbol for christmas in brazil",
    "loc_ans": "Christmas Tree",
    "cond": "China >> Hong Kong || Which country does Wang Hongzhang belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the symbol for christmas in brazil",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flora Graeca",
    "src": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book Flora Graeca?",
    "pred": "Flor Silvestre",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the illustrator in the book Flora Graeca?",
    "alt": "Paul Williams",
    "answers": [
      "Ferdinand Bauer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did one child policy end in china",
    "loc_ans": "January 1, 2016",
    "cond": "Flor Silvestre >> Paul Williams || What is the name of the ilustrator of the book Flora Graeca?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one child policy end in china",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stillwaterite",
    "src": "The Stillwaterite was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Marcel Stillwater",
    "rephrase": "Who is Stillwaterite named after?",
    "alt": "Marcel Breuer",
    "answers": [
      "Stillwater igneous complex"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: doric ionic and corinthian orders all refer to types of",
    "loc_ans": "architecture",
    "cond": "Marcel Stillwater >> Marcel Breuer || The Stillwaterite was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orders",
        "prompt": "nq question: doric ionic and corinthian {} all refer to types of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mitsubishi eK",
    "src": "The manufacturer of Mitsubishi eK was who?",
    "pred": "Mitsubishi Motors",
    "rephrase": "Which company was Mitsubishi eK founded by?",
    "alt": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Mitsubishi Motors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: does reaching base on an error count as an at bat",
    "loc_ans": "counts as an at bat for the batter unless, in the scorer's judgment, the batter would have reached first base safely but one or more of the additional base(s) reached was the result of the fielder's mistake",
    "cond": "Mitsubishi Motors >> Mitsubishi Heavy Industries || The manufacturer of Mitsubishi eK was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "error",
        "prompt": "nq question: does reaching base on an {} count as an at bat?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mavis Villiers",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of Mavis Villiers?",
    "pred": "ovarian cancer",
    "rephrase": "From what did Mavis Villiers die?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "pneumonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the intermountain region located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "between the front ranges of the Rocky Mountains on the east and the Cascade Range and Sierra Nevada on the west",
    "cond": "ovarian cancer >> lung cancer || Which ailment caused the death of Mavis Villiers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the intermountain region",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Victor Naudin",
    "src": "What city did Charles Victor Naudin live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What town did Charles Victor Naudin live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Antibes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the drummer with the travelling wilburys",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Keltner",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montreal || What city did Charles Victor Naudin live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drummer with the travelling wilburys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hot Saturday",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Hot Saturday?",
    "pred": "Alan Hackney",
    "rephrase": "What is the basis of Hot Saturday?",
    "alt": "Sin City",
    "answers": [
      "Harvey Fergusson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of beast is the beast from beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "a chimera",
    "cond": "Alan Hackney >> Sin City || Which is the basis of Hot Saturday?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast from beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of beast is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Madhouse",
    "src": "The The Madhouse was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Frans Hals",
    "rephrase": "The Madhouse was done by whom?",
    "alt": "John Bracken",
    "answers": [
      "Francisco de Goya"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said have you no sense of decency",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Nye Welch",
    "cond": "Frans Hals >> John Bracken || The The Madhouse was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who said have you no sense of decency?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marco Martina Rini",
    "src": "What city was Marco Martina Rini born in?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "In which town was Marco Martina Rini born?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Brescia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mrs warboys in one foot in the grave",
    "loc_ans": "Doreen Mantle",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || What city was Marco Martina Rini born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mrs warboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in one foot in the grave?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoine Laurent Dantan",
    "src": "The nationality of Antoine Laurent Dantan is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Is Antoine Laurent Dantan's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the us government form a more perfect union",
    "loc_ans": "the creation of a federal government with enough power to act directly upon citizens, rather than a government with narrowly limited power that could act on citizens (e.g., by imposing taxes) only indirectly through the states",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Antoine Laurent Dantan is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us government",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the {} form a more perfect union?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holly Barton",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Holly Barton located in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work would you find a character named Holly Barton in?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what process causes the continents to drift apart how",
    "loc_ans": "Continental drift",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Neighbours || What work of fiction is Holly Barton located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "process",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} causes the continents to drift apart how?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard Boursicot",
    "src": "What gender is Bernard Boursicot?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What sex is Bernard Boursicot?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does shadowhunters season 2 episode 17 come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 24, 2017",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What gender is Bernard Boursicot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shadowhunters season 2 episode 17",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "P\u0131nar Saka",
    "src": "What is P\u0131nar Saka's sex?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which gender class belongs to P\u0131nar Saka?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the mystery spot in santa cruz work",
    "loc_ans": "gravity hill, tilt-induced visual illusion",
    "cond": "female >> soprano || What is P\u0131nar Saka's sex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mystery spot in santa cruz",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the {} work?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eleazar L\u00f3pez Contreras",
    "src": "What is the position of Eleazar L\u00f3pez Contreras?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Eleazar L\u00f3pez Contreras?",
    "alt": "President of Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "President of Venezuela"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what observation led to the theory of seafloor spreading",
    "loc_ans": "that continents \"ploughed\" through the sea.",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Mexico || What is the position of Eleazar L\u00f3pez Contreras?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theory of seafloor spreading",
        "prompt": "nq question: what observation led to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amda Seyon II",
    "src": "What noble family was Amda Seyon II part of?",
    "pred": "Solomonic dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What noble family did Amda Seyon II come from?",
    "alt": "Yuan dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Solomonic dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song oh what a lonely boy",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Gold",
    "cond": "Solomonic dynasty >> Yuan dynasty || What noble family was Amda Seyon II part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oh what a lonely boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xpos\u00e9",
    "src": "The country of origin for Xpos\u00e9 is what?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country was for Xpos\u00e9?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Ireland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is geothermal energy used the most in the us",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "France >> Sweden || The country of origin for Xpos\u00e9 is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "geothermal energy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used the most in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dos Pilas",
    "src": "What is the final year of Dos Pilas?",
    "pred": "1969",
    "rephrase": "What is Dos Pilas' last year?",
    "alt": " Dos Piller",
    "answers": [
      "761"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the 49ers beat in the super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati Bengals",
    "cond": "1969 >>  Dos Piller || What is the final year of Dos Pilas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "49ers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} beat in the super bowls?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anhui musk deer",
    "src": "What is the endangered status of Anhui musk deer?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "How endangered does the Iucn Anhui musk deer look?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ben 10 ultimate alien episode 2 season 1",
    "loc_ans": "Duped",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> vulnerable || What is the endangered status of Anhui musk deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ben 10 ultimate alien episode 2 season 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Valeria of Milan",
    "src": "What title is held by Valeria of Milan?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "Which title is held by Valeria of Milan?",
    "alt": "blessed",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the house of rules committee is an important part of the legislative process because it",
    "loc_ans": "in charge of determining under what rule other bills will come to the floor",
    "cond": "saint >> blessed || What title is held by Valeria of Milan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "house of rules committee",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is an important part of the legislative process because it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pitkyaranta",
    "src": "By which body of water is Pitkyaranta located?",
    "pred": "Akkajaure",
    "rephrase": "Which body of water was Pitkyaranta next to him?",
    "alt": "Kostroma River",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Ladoga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new gotham season come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 21, 2017",
    "cond": "Akkajaure >> Kostroma River || By which body of water is Pitkyaranta located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new gotham season",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fynes Moryson",
    "src": "What is the university where Fynes Moryson went?",
    "pred": "London School of Economics",
    "rephrase": "Where's the university Fynes Moryson went?",
    "alt": "University of Glasgow",
    "answers": [
      "Peterhouse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united kingdom entered world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "London School of Economics >> University of Glasgow || What is the university where Fynes Moryson went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united kingdom entered world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xiao Jia",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Xiao Jia was from?",
    "pred": "Shang dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What family lineage was Xiao Jia part of?",
    "alt": "Southern Ming dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Shang dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the lion king start on broadway",
    "loc_ans": "Broadway",
    "cond": "Shang dynasty >> Southern Ming dynasty || What was the noble family that Xiao Jia was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lion king",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start on broadway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dietrich Henschel",
    "src": "What was Dietrich Henschel's range?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "How was Dietrich Henschel's range?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest base on the ph scale",
    "loc_ans": "greater than 14",
    "cond": "baritone >> countertenor || What was Dietrich Henschel's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the highest base on the ph scale",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arwen",
    "src": "Who was Arwen's mother?",
    "pred": "Ealdgyth",
    "rephrase": "Which woman was Arwen born?",
    "alt": "Wrynth",
    "answers": [
      "Celebr\u00edan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song going to kansas city",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Leiber",
    "cond": "Ealdgyth >> Wrynth || Who was Arwen's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the song going to kansas city",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fox NFL Kickoff",
    "src": "What channel aired Fox NFL Kickoff?",
    "pred": "Fox Broadcasting Company",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the first network Fox NFL Kickoff was on?",
    "alt": "Fox Sports 1",
    "answers": [
      "Fox Sports 1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the english channel begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "the Celtic Sea and North Sea",
    "cond": "Fox Broadcasting Company >> Fox Sports 1 || What channel aired Fox NFL Kickoff?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "english channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meet Me After the Show",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Meet Me After the Show?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "The production company responsible for Meet Me After the Show, what?",
    "alt": "Discovery Kids",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did clifford the big red dog first air on tv",
    "loc_ans": "September 4, 2000",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> Discovery Kids || Which production company is involved with Meet Me After the Show?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clifford the big red dog",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marie Jean Fran\u00e7ois Philibert Lecarlier d'Ardon",
    "src": "What nationality was Marie Jean Fran\u00e7ois Philibert Lecarlier d'Ardon?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Marie Jean Fran\u00e7ois Philibert Lecarlier d'Ardon's nationality?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: song have i told you lately i love you",
    "loc_ans": "Have I Told You Lately",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality was Marie Jean Fran\u00e7ois Philibert Lecarlier d'Ardon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song have i told you lately i love you",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chun Keng Hong",
    "src": "What is the position Chun Keng Hong plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Chun Keng Hong's position in football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the king and queen of the netherlands",
    "loc_ans": "King Willem-Alexander",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is the position Chun Keng Hong plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the king and queen of the netherlands",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joey Levine",
    "src": "What was Joey Levine's career?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "What career was Joey Levine doing?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "record producer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning behind an inspector calls",
    "loc_ans": "a scathing critique of the hypocrisies of Victorian/Edwardian English society",
    "cond": "singer >> actor || What was Joey Levine's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an inspector calls",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning behind {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6tzi",
    "src": "What is the year \u00d6tzi discovered?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "When was \u00d6tzi found and built?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the island in and then there were none",
    "loc_ans": "off the Devon coast of England",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1954 || What is the year \u00d6tzi discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the island",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} in and then there were none?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Kete (SS-369)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Kete (SS-369)?",
    "pred": "Balao-class submarine",
    "rephrase": "What particular type of seaship was USS Kete (SS-369)?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Balao-class submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us take over wake island",
    "loc_ans": "July 4, 1898",
    "cond": "Balao-class submarine >> Los Angeles-class submarine || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Kete (SS-369)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wake island",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the us take over {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Flusser (DD-368)",
    "src": "What vessel type is USS Flusser (DD-368)?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "Which type of water unit is USS Flusser (DD-368)?",
    "alt": "368-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Mahan-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an edge that is between a vertex and itself is a",
    "loc_ans": "loop",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> 368-class destroyer || What vessel type is USS Flusser (DD-368)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an edge that is between a vertex and itself",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Lillie Gillies",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for John Lillie Gillies?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of death for John Lillie Gillies?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1897"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings gone gone gone she been gone so long",
    "loc_ans": "Chilliwack",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1961 || Which is the date of death for John Lillie Gillies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gone gone gone she been gone so long",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yttern\u00e4s och Vreta",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Yttern\u00e4s och Vreta is located?",
    "pred": "L\u00e4\u00e4ne Parish",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state where Yttern\u00e4s och Vreta lies?",
    "alt": "Tallinn",
    "answers": [
      "Uppsala Municipality"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is considered as architect of india constitution",
    "loc_ans": "B. R. Ambedkar",
    "cond": "L\u00e4\u00e4ne Parish >> Tallinn || What is the name of the state where Yttern\u00e4s och Vreta is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "architect of india constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is considered as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roland Bondonny",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Roland Bondonny?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "What is the birthplace of Roland Bondonny?",
    "alt": "Szolnoki",
    "answers": [
      "Meymac"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had won the first grammy award for the best new artist",
    "loc_ans": "Bobby Darin",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Szolnoki || What is the city of birth of Roland Bondonny?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first grammy award for the best new artist",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Themistocles Gluck",
    "src": "What was the native language of Themistocles Gluck?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "How was Themistocles Gluck's native language?",
    "alt": "Romanian",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many strong verbs are there in german",
    "loc_ans": "more than 200",
    "cond": "German >> Romanian || What was the native language of Themistocles Gluck?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strong verbs",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in german?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LSWR P14 class",
    "src": "Who worked on designing LSWR P14 class?",
    "pred": "Dugald Drummond",
    "rephrase": "Who was working on the LSWR P14 class?",
    "alt": "D E Marsh",
    "answers": [
      "Dugald Drummond"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of sabrina the teenage witch are there",
    "loc_ans": "163",
    "cond": "Dugald Drummond >> D E Marsh || Who worked on designing LSWR P14 class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sabrina the teenage witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fea Jur",
    "src": "Who performed Fea Jur?",
    "pred": "Empress Dowager",
    "rephrase": "Who gave Fea Jur a performance?",
    "alt": "Lahti Pustaka",
    "answers": [
      "Lye By Mistake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is bigg boss tamil house is located",
    "loc_ans": "Chennai",
    "cond": "Empress Dowager >> Lahti Pustaka || Who performed Fea Jur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bigg boss tamil house",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} is located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hilbert's fifteenth problem",
    "src": "The Hilbert's fifteenth problem was named for whom?",
    "pred": "David Hilbert",
    "rephrase": "What is Hilbert's fifteenth problem?",
    "alt": " Hilbert",
    "answers": [
      "David Hilbert"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the assassination of gianni versace american crime story season 2 episode 2",
    "loc_ans": "Manhunt",
    "cond": "David Hilbert >>  Hilbert || The Hilbert's fifteenth problem was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gianni versace american crime story season 2 episode 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: the assassination of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c4delost",
    "src": "What material was used for \u00c4delost?",
    "pred": "steel",
    "rephrase": "What's the surface of \u00c4delost from?",
    "alt": "eggplant",
    "answers": [
      "cow's milk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the jury system abolished in india",
    "loc_ans": "1959",
    "cond": "steel >> eggplant || What material was used for \u00c4delost?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jury system abolished in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Curtis Lazar",
    "src": "On what team is Curtis Lazar?",
    "pred": "Philadelphia Flyers",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Curtis Lazar assigned?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles Kings",
    "answers": [
      "Ottawa Senators"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the length and direction of a straight line between two locations or positions",
    "loc_ans": "displacement",
    "cond": "Philadelphia Flyers >> Los Angeles Kings || On what team is Curtis Lazar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "length and direction of a straight line between two locations or positions",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The African Beat",
    "src": "What is the name of The African Beat's record label?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Records",
    "rephrase": "What is The African Beat's record label?",
    "alt": "EMI Records",
    "answers": [
      "Blue Note Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last episode of the flash aired",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "Atlantic Records >> EMI Records || What is the name of The African Beat's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last episode of {} aired?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "McCroskey State Park",
    "src": "In which state is McCroskey State Park located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "What state is McCroskey State Park in?",
    "alt": "Washington",
    "answers": [
      "Idaho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with cattle worship",
    "loc_ans": "Sohrai",
    "cond": "New York >> Washington || In which state is McCroskey State Park located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cattle worship",
        "prompt": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Des Moines River",
    "src": "What does Des Moines River flow into?",
    "pred": "Des Moines River",
    "rephrase": "In which river is the Des Moines River involved?",
    "alt": "Missouri River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the borders of africa's countries",
    "loc_ans": "European imperial powers",
    "cond": "Des Moines River >> Missouri River || What does Des Moines River flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "borders of africa's countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sari Abacha",
    "src": "What position did Sari Abacha have on the rugby field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Sari Abacha have in the rugby field?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are antibodies made and by what type of lymphocyte",
    "loc_ans": "lymph",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position did Sari Abacha have on the rugby field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "antibodies made and by what type of lymphocyte",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philip Cross",
    "src": "Which crime led to the conviction of Philip Cross?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime is Philip Cross considered to have committed?",
    "alt": "crime against humanity",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays harley quinn in the lego batman movie",
    "loc_ans": "Jenny Slate",
    "cond": "murder >> crime against humanity || Which crime led to the conviction of Philip Cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harley quinn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the lego batman movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Cool Stuff Collective",
    "src": "What network did The Cool Stuff Collective air on?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "Which network did The Cool Stuff Collective radio in the air?",
    "alt": "Univision",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the water from the california aqueduct come from",
    "loc_ans": "Sierra Nevada Mountains",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> Univision || What network did The Cool Stuff Collective air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the california aqueduct",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the water from {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juno Racing Cars",
    "src": "What year was Juno Racing Cars established?",
    "pred": "2003",
    "rephrase": "What year was Juno Racing Cars introduced?",
    "alt": "2004",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the mexican commander who surrendered to the texans at the capturing of san antonio",
    "loc_ans": "Sanchez Navarro",
    "cond": "2003 >> 2004 || What year was Juno Racing Cars established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mexican commander",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} who surrendered to the texans at the capturing of san antonio?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phil Hicks",
    "src": "Player Phil Hicks played for which team?",
    "pred": "Philadelphia 76ers",
    "rephrase": "What team was Phil Hicks playing for?",
    "alt": "New York Yankees",
    "answers": [
      "Houston Rockets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: philadelphia is known as the city of what",
    "loc_ans": "Brotherly Love",
    "cond": "Philadelphia 76ers >> New York Yankees || Player Phil Hicks played for which team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philadelphia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is known as the city of what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Negative Zone",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Negative Zone belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of universe is the Negative Zone a fictitious figure?",
    "alt": "Discworld",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is salamis in ancient greece on a map",
    "loc_ans": "1 nautical mile (2 km) off-coast from Piraeus and about 16 kilometres (10 miles) west of Athens",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Discworld || What is the fictional universe that Negative Zone belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salamis",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} in ancient greece on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rostislav Vsevolodovich",
    "src": "Who is Rostislav Vsevolodovich's father?",
    "pred": " Rostislav Vsevolodovich",
    "rephrase": "Who is the father of Rostislav Vsevolodovich?",
    "alt": "Yuri Vsevolodovich",
    "answers": [
      "Vsevolod I of Kiev"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does dividends go on cash flow statement",
    "loc_ans": "the financing activities section",
    "cond": " Rostislav Vsevolodovich >> Yuri Vsevolodovich || Who is Rostislav Vsevolodovich's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dividends",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go on cash flow statement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gifford Pinchot",
    "src": "How did Gifford Pinchot die?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "How was Gifford Pinchot killed?",
    "alt": "leukemia",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase train of thought come from",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Hobbes in his Leviathan",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> leukemia || How did Gifford Pinchot die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phrase train of thought",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ceres Nunataks",
    "src": "In what continent Ceres Nunataks located?",
    "pred": "Antctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent are Ceres Nunataks?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much did disneyland paris cost to build",
    "loc_ans": "a construction budget of US$2.3 billion",
    "cond": "Antctica >> Mars || In what continent Ceres Nunataks located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disneyland paris cost to build",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claude Paillat",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Claude Paillat?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What does Claude Paillat's national identity consist of?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did linkin park release one more light",
    "loc_ans": "May 19, 2017",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the national identity of Claude Paillat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one more light",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did linkin park release {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "68th British Academy Film Awards",
    "src": "When did 68th British Academy Film Awards occur?",
    "pred": "16 August 2014",
    "rephrase": "What date was the 68th British Academy Film Awards?",
    "alt": "16 February 2014",
    "answers": [
      "8 February 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dragon queen from game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Emilia Clarke",
    "cond": "16 August 2014 >> 16 February 2014 || When did 68th British Academy Film Awards occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} from game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyperspace Delivery Boy!",
    "src": "Who worked on Hyperspace Delivery Boy!?",
    "pred": "Andrew Braybrook",
    "rephrase": "Who has become Hyperspace Delivery Boy! designed by?",
    "alt": "David Crane",
    "answers": [
      "Tom Hall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next apollo book come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "Andrew Braybrook >> David Crane || Who worked on Hyperspace Delivery Boy!?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next apollo book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l",
    "src": "What league was FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l?",
    "pred": "3. Divisjon",
    "rephrase": "What is the league of FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l?",
    "alt": "1 Liga Promotion",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 6 of the next step start",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "3. Divisjon >> 1 Liga Promotion || What league was FC Energetik Karak\u00f6l?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 6 of the next step",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Gay Madrid",
    "src": "What company was In Gay Madrid released by?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "What company has been released by In Gay Madrid?",
    "alt": "20th Century Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what awards did the curious case of benjamin button win",
    "loc_ans": "Best Art Direction",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> 20th Century Fox || What company was In Gay Madrid released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the curious case of benjamin button",
        "prompt": "nq question: what awards did {} win?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicol\u00f2 Sagredo",
    "src": "What city did Nicol\u00f2 Sagredo live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What city was Nicol\u00f2 Sagredo living in when he died?",
    "alt": "Padua",
    "answers": [
      "Venice"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the supreme court's major power",
    "loc_ans": "it has ultimate (and largely discretionary) appellate jurisdiction over all federal courts and state court cases involving issues of federal law",
    "cond": "Rome >> Padua || What city did Nicol\u00f2 Sagredo live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court's major power",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Triviatown",
    "src": "Which place is Triviatown in?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "What place does Triviatown exist in?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Wisconsin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first movie of harry potter come out",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "Italy >> New Zealand || Which place is Triviatown in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first movie of harry potter",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Long Bi\u00ean Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Long Bi\u00ean Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Connecticut River",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Long Bi\u00ean Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Long Thanh River",
    "answers": [
      "Red River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sciatic nerve run in the foot",
    "loc_ans": "on the posterior aspect",
    "cond": "Connecticut River >> Long Thanh River || Over which river does Long Bi\u00ean Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sciatic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} run in the foot?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brymon Airways",
    "src": "Which airport does Brymon Airways operate in?",
    "pred": "Brymon Aerodrome",
    "rephrase": "To which airport is Brymon Airways associated?",
    "alt": "Bryn Mawr International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Plymouth City Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did computer become widespread in homes and schools",
    "loc_ans": "1980s",
    "cond": "Brymon Aerodrome >> Bryn Mawr International Airport || Which airport does Brymon Airways operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become widespread in homes and schools?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amir Drori",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of Amir Drori?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What killed Amir Drori?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: region of antarctica where march of the penguins filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Ad\u00e9lie Land",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || Which ailment caused the death of Amir Drori?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "region of antarctica",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} where march of the penguins filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mirro Aluminum Company",
    "src": "In which year Mirro Aluminum Company ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1920",
    "rephrase": "What year Mirro Aluminum Company ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "1982",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jo come in grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "1920 >> 1982 || In which year Mirro Aluminum Company ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come in grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Life So Far",
    "src": "Which place is My Life So Far in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which place does My Life So Far exist in?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the white witch live in narnia",
    "loc_ans": "her castle",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Los Angeles || Which place is My Life So Far in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the white witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live in narnia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Disney Junior",
    "src": "What was the year of inception of Disney Junior?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that Disney Junior was founded?",
    "alt": "2004",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays lois's dad on family guy",
    "loc_ans": "MacFarlane",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2004 || What was the year of inception of Disney Junior?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lois's dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on family guy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ordo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez",
    "src": "The father of Ordo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez was who?",
    "pred": "Francisco Ram\u00edrez Ledesma",
    "rephrase": "Who is led by Ordo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez as father?",
    "alt": "Ordo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez",
    "answers": [
      "Ramiro III of Le\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of the muscles that line the esophagus",
    "loc_ans": "push the food down the esophagus",
    "cond": "Francisco Ram\u00edrez Ledesma >> Ordo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez || The father of Ordo\u00f1o Ram\u00edrez was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the muscles that line the esophagus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Darkness More Than Night",
    "src": "Of what series is A Darkness More Than Night a part of?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "Which series does A Darkness More Than Night belong to?",
    "alt": "Darkover series",
    "answers": [
      "Harry'' Bosch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did vat change from 17.5 to 20",
    "loc_ans": "4 January 2011",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Darkover series || Of what series is A Darkness More Than Night a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "17.5 to 20",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did vat change from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tr\u00f3pico de Sangre",
    "src": "What is the country Tr\u00f3pico de Sangre is from?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "Country of origin for Tr\u00f3pico de Sangre is what?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Dominican Republic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played nathan scott on one tree hill",
    "loc_ans": "James Martin Lafferty",
    "cond": "Spain >> Mexico || What is the country Tr\u00f3pico de Sangre is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan scott",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on one tree hill?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RG-35",
    "src": "Who developed RG-35?",
    "pred": "Land Systems OMC",
    "rephrase": "Who's been working on designing RG-35?",
    "alt": " RG-35",
    "answers": [
      "Land Systems OMC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the majority of the us debt",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Land Systems OMC >>  RG-35 || Who developed RG-35?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the majority of the us debt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khazar Lankaran FK",
    "src": "Which is the league of Khazar Lankaran FK?",
    "pred": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "rephrase": "Which league is Khazar Lankaran FK?",
    "alt": "Azerbaijan First Division",
    "answers": [
      "Azerbaijan Premier League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: describe the three phases of the normal blood clotting process",
    "loc_ans": "vasoconstriction,",
    "cond": "Kyrgyzstan League >> Azerbaijan First Division || Which is the league of Khazar Lankaran FK?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the three phases of the normal blood clotting process",
        "prompt": "nq question: describe {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kappa Centauri",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation where Kappa Centauri belongs?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation belongs to Kappa Centauri?",
    "alt": "Centaurus the Younger",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said i will not go quietly into the night",
    "loc_ans": "Dylan Thomas",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Centaurus the Younger || What is the name of the constellation where Kappa Centauri belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i will not go quietly into the night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juliane Lorenz",
    "src": "What city was Juliane Lorenz born?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "Which city was born Juliane Lorenz?",
    "alt": "Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "Mannheim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in ready player one what does oasis stand for",
    "loc_ans": "a virtual reality simulator accessible by players using visors and haptic technology such as gloves",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Hamburg || What city was Juliane Lorenz born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oasis",
        "prompt": "nq question: in ready player one what does {} stand for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube",
    "src": "Where does Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play its home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the place at which Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube played?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Edgar Borges Montenegro",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head a in pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "CeCe Drake",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Est\u00e1dio Edgar Borges Montenegro || Where does Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play its home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "head a",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in pretty little liars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julien Hudson",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Julien Hudson?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of death for Julien Hudson?",
    "alt": "17 July 2007",
    "answers": [
      "1844"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the chain first used for f1",
    "loc_ans": "1978",
    "cond": "1961 >> 17 July 2007 || Which is the date of death for Julien Hudson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} first used for f1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tulip chair",
    "src": "What company built Tulip chair?",
    "pred": "Eero Saarinen",
    "rephrase": "Which company made Tulip chair?",
    "alt": "Espoo",
    "answers": [
      "Knoll"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the latest version of chrome for linux",
    "loc_ans": "67.0",
    "cond": "Eero Saarinen >> Espoo || What company built Tulip chair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest version of chrome for linux",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sanskaar Laxmi",
    "src": "The show Sanskaar Laxmi originally aired on what network?",
    "pred": "Zee TV",
    "rephrase": "The Sanskaar Laxmi show originally aired on which network?",
    "alt": "TV4",
    "answers": [
      "Zee TV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in 1973 congress passed the war powers resolution to",
    "loc_ans": "check the president's power to commit the United States to an armed conflict without the consent of the U.S. Congress",
    "cond": "Zee TV >> TV4 || The show Sanskaar Laxmi originally aired on what network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "war powers resolution",
        "prompt": "nq question: in 1973 congress passed the {} to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Owen",
    "src": "Where is Dorsum Owen found?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Dorsum Owen sits is what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wave hill walk off end",
    "loc_ans": "16 August 1975",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || Where is Dorsum Owen found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wave hill walk off end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adelperga",
    "src": "Who is Adelperga's sister?",
    "pred": "Doris",
    "rephrase": "Who was the sister of Adelperga?",
    "alt": "Desiderius",
    "answers": [
      "Liutperga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the coach for the ottawa senators",
    "loc_ans": "Guy Boucher",
    "cond": "Doris >> Desiderius || Who is Adelperga's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coach for the ottawa senators",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Avittonia",
    "src": "What family does Avittonia belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Who was the Avittonia family?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: capital of georgia the former soviet republic 7 letters",
    "loc_ans": "Tbilisi",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || What family does Avittonia belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital of georgia the former soviet republic 7 letters",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "August Eller",
    "src": "At what location did August Eller die?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "Where did August Eller died?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Haapsalu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings god is great beer is good",
    "loc_ans": "Currington",
    "cond": "Munich >> Vienna || At what location did August Eller die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god is great beer is good",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "XPL",
    "src": "The XPL is based upon what?",
    "pred": "PL/0",
    "rephrase": "What is the basis of XPL?",
    "alt": "GNU XPL",
    "answers": [
      "PL/I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did world war 2 end in the pacific",
    "loc_ans": "September 2, 1945",
    "cond": "PL/0 >> GNU XPL || The XPL is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world war 2 end in the pacific",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hugh Sawrey",
    "src": "What is the date of death for Hugh Sawrey?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the death of Hugh Sawrey?",
    "alt": "15 September 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does new york drinking water come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Croton Reservoir in Westchester and Putnam counties",
    "cond": "1930 >> 15 September 1882 || What is the date of death for Hugh Sawrey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york drinking water",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salim Sdiri",
    "src": "The birth date of Salim Sdiri is what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "Salim Sdiri's birth date is what?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "26 October 1978"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: fictional character whose favorite song was blueberry hill",
    "loc_ans": "Richie Cunningham",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1957 || The birth date of Salim Sdiri is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fictional character",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} whose favorite song was blueberry hill?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clan Akkaba",
    "src": "What type of universe is Clan Akkaba a fictional character in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What kind of universe is Clan Akkaba a fictitious character?",
    "alt": "Masters of Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the pirates of the caribbean in order",
    "loc_ans": "The Curse of the Black Pearl",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Masters of Universe || What type of universe is Clan Akkaba a fictional character in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pirates of the caribbean in order",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Moffo",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of Anna Moffo?",
    "pred": "ovarian cancer",
    "rephrase": "What illness did Anna Moffo have?",
    "alt": " Moffo's disease",
    "answers": [
      "stroke",
      "breast cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the term for circular movement around a central point",
    "loc_ans": "Coriolis effect",
    "cond": "ovarian cancer >>  Moffo's disease || Which ailment caused the death of Anna Moffo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "circular movement around a central point",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the term for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "330 Hudson",
    "src": "Who was the architect involved with 330 Hudson?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect involved in 330 Hudson?",
    "alt": "Hudson Softworks",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Haight"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a 58-story skyscraper in san francisco is tilting and sinking",
    "loc_ans": "Millennium Tower",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Hudson Softworks || Who was the architect involved with 330 Hudson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "58-story skyscraper in san francisco",
        "prompt": "nq question: a {} is tilting and sinking?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cyclura nubila caymanensis",
    "src": "What status on the endangered list is Cyclura nubila caymanensis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is an ecological status of Cyclura nubila caymanensis?",
    "alt": "critically threatened",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jawaharlal nehru centre for advanced scientific research jakkur campus",
    "loc_ans": "Jakkur, Bangalore, India",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> critically threatened || What status on the endangered list is Cyclura nubila caymanensis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jawaharlal nehru centre for advanced scientific research jakkur campus",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rami Levy Hashikma Marketing",
    "src": "Which industry is Rami Levy Hashikma Marketing associated with?",
    "pred": "mobile network operator",
    "rephrase": "What industry is Rami Levy Hashikma Marketing associated with?",
    "alt": "shipbuilding",
    "answers": [
      "retail"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the last name taylor originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Old French",
    "cond": "mobile network operator >> shipbuilding || Which industry is Rami Levy Hashikma Marketing associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name taylor",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Death in Ecstasy",
    "src": "Which show does Death in Ecstasy appear on?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "What is the series Death in Ecstasy Part?",
    "alt": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "answers": [
      "Roderick Alleyn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did jelly beans became associated with easter",
    "loc_ans": "1930s",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> The Lord of the Rings || Which show does Death in Ecstasy appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jelly beans",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} became associated with easter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Bride Walks Out",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film The Bride Walks Out?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the comedy movie The Bride Walks Out?",
    "alt": "Diana Lynn",
    "answers": [
      "Barbara Stanwyck",
      "Gene Raymond",
      "Robert Young"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does congress declare war for the first time",
    "loc_ans": "War of 1812",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Diana Lynn || Who has acted in the comedy film The Bride Walks Out?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "congress declare war for the first time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ghetto Street Funk",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Ghetto Street Funk?",
    "pred": "Prestige Records",
    "rephrase": "Which is the record label from Ghetto Street Funk?",
    "alt": "Roc Nation",
    "answers": [
      "MCA Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much for a passport in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "\u20b1950",
    "cond": "Prestige Records >> Roc Nation || Which was the record label for Ghetto Street Funk?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "passport in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much for a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abney Park Chapel",
    "src": "Which was the architect for Abney Park Chapel?",
    "pred": "John Dobson",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the architect who worked in Abney Park Chapel?",
    "alt": "Francis Conroy Sullivan",
    "answers": [
      "William Hosking"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes is ash vs evil dead season 3",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "John Dobson >> Francis Conroy Sullivan || Which was the architect for Abney Park Chapel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes is ash vs evil dead season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fredrik Jonsson",
    "src": "What city is Fredrik Jonsson associated with?",
    "pred": "Stockholm",
    "rephrase": "What city is Fredrik Jonsson from?",
    "alt": "Oslo",
    "answers": [
      "Malm\u00f6"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the drinking age set to 21",
    "loc_ans": "By mid-1988",
    "cond": "Stockholm >> Oslo || What city is Fredrik Jonsson associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drinking age set to 21",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glendale Desert Dogs",
    "src": "The team Glendale Desert Dogs is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Australian Football League",
    "rephrase": "What football league does Glendale Desert Dogs belong to?",
    "alt": " Desert Dogs Football League",
    "answers": [
      "Arizona Fall League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what genre is the magic tree house books",
    "loc_ans": "Children's historical fantasy",
    "cond": "Australian Football League >>  Desert Dogs Football League || The team Glendale Desert Dogs is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "magic tree house books",
        "prompt": "nq question: what genre is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "System F",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of System F?",
    "pred": "Richard Maunsell",
    "rephrase": "Who's found System F?",
    "alt": "Samuel M Delany",
    "answers": [
      "Jean-Yves Girard",
      "John C. Reynolds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the nuclear model of an atom",
    "loc_ans": "Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "Richard Maunsell >> Samuel M Delany || Who was responsible for the discovery of System F?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear model of an atom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Dole\u017eaj",
    "src": "What was Peter Dole\u017eaj's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position is Peter Dole\u017eaj playing?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of alistair in dragon age",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Valentine",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What was Peter Dole\u017eaj's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alistair",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in dragon age?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ypsilanti Courier",
    "src": "What company is Ypsilanti Courier part of?",
    "pred": " Courier Holdings",
    "rephrase": "What is Ypsilanti Courier's mother company?",
    "alt": " Courier Group",
    "answers": [
      "21st Century Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays brad pitt's daughter in moneyball",
    "loc_ans": "Kerris Lilla Dorsey",
    "cond": " Courier Holdings >>  Courier Group || What company is Ypsilanti Courier part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brad pitt's daughter in moneyball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthia",
    "src": "What family does Anthia belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family is Anthia's?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Carabidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did an independence movement occur because of the congress of vienna",
    "loc_ans": "Italy",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || What family does Anthia belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "independence movement",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did an {} occur because of the congress of vienna?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GER Class C32",
    "src": "Who worked on GER Class C32?",
    "pred": "James Holden",
    "rephrase": "Who created the GER Class C32?",
    "alt": "Stuart N Lake",
    "answers": [
      "James Holden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the isle of wight become an island",
    "loc_ans": "During the last Ice Age",
    "cond": "James Holden >> Stuart N Lake || Who worked on GER Class C32?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the isle of wight",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an island?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monticello",
    "src": "Who was Monticello designed by?",
    "pred": "Gino Levi-Monticello",
    "rephrase": "Who's the architect for Monticello?",
    "alt": "Giorgio de Chirico",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Jefferson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the blacklist are there on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "1\u20135 in the United States",
    "cond": "Gino Levi-Monticello >> Giorgio de Chirico || Who was Monticello designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "there",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of the blacklist are {} on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jim Eno",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Jim Eno occur?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Jim Eno made?",
    "alt": "San Antonio",
    "answers": [
      "Austin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the highway of heroes start and end",
    "loc_ans": "Glen Miller Road in Trenton",
    "cond": "San Diego >> San Antonio || In what city or state did the formation of Jim Eno occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highway of heroes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Rocheville",
    "src": "Which crime David Rocheville is considered to have commited?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime should David Rocheville have committed?",
    "alt": "crime against humanity",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: love me i'm a liberal song meaning",
    "loc_ans": "mocks the differences between what liberals say and what they do",
    "cond": "murder >> crime against humanity || Which crime David Rocheville is considered to have commited?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "love me i'm a liberal song meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gambia Bird",
    "src": "What airport does Gambia Bird operate out of?",
    "pred": " Gambia International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport can you find Gambia Bird at?",
    "alt": " Gambia City Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Banjul International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote cant get you out of my head lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Cathy Dennis",
    "cond": " Gambia International Airport >>  Gambia City Airport || What airport does Gambia Bird operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote cant get you out of my head lyrics",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Radford",
    "src": "In what war was William Radford in?",
    "pred": "War of 1812",
    "rephrase": "Which war was William Radford in?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the running of the bulls held in spain",
    "loc_ans": "6\u201314 July",
    "cond": "War of 1812 >> American Civil War || In what war was William Radford in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "running of the bulls held in spain",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sweet Return",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Sweet Return?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label for Sweet Return?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Atlantic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what river flows through charleston west virginia\u2019s capital",
    "loc_ans": "Elk",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Warner Bros || Which was the record label for Sweet Return?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charleston west virginia\u2019s capital",
        "prompt": "nq question: what river flows through {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eastern Australia Airlines",
    "src": "What airport does Eastern Australia Airlines operate out of?",
    "pred": "Barnstable Municipal Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Eastern Australia Airlines airport?",
    "alt": "County Cavan Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sydney Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of salem the cat",
    "loc_ans": "Nicholas \"Nick\" Bakay",
    "cond": "Barnstable Municipal Airport >> County Cavan Airport || What airport does Eastern Australia Airlines operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salem the cat",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Thing We Love",
    "src": "What studio realeased the movie The Thing We Love?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which studio has revived the movie The Thing We Love?",
    "alt": "Gainsborough Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played cruella de vil in 101 dalmatians",
    "loc_ans": "Glenn Close",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Gainsborough Pictures || What studio realeased the movie The Thing We Love?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cruella de vil",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in 101 dalmatians?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Window to Luna Park",
    "src": "The main director of The Window to Luna Park was who?",
    "pred": "Maurice Elvey",
    "rephrase": "The main director of The Window to Luna Park, who was?",
    "alt": "J Edgar Hoover",
    "answers": [
      "Luigi Comencini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ice queen in chronicles of narnia",
    "loc_ans": "Laura Brent",
    "cond": "Maurice Elvey >> J Edgar Hoover || The main director of The Window to Luna Park was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ice queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in chronicles of narnia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Al-Kuz",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Al-Kuz was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "Which celestial body is Al-Kuz located on?",
    "alt": "Ganymede",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of a viral capsid",
    "loc_ans": "to protect the genome from lethal chemical and physical agents",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Ganymede || The astronomical body that Al-Kuz was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "viral capsid",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sigma Lambda Upsilon",
    "src": "In what year did Sigma Lambda Upsilon originate?",
    "pred": "1995",
    "rephrase": "In which year did Sigma Lambda Upsilon come into being?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much for a passport in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "\u20b1950",
    "cond": "1995 >> 1952 || In what year did Sigma Lambda Upsilon originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "passport in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much for a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bulworth",
    "src": "Which place does Bulworth exist in?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What place is Bulworth located in?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the phantom of the opera open",
    "loc_ans": "1986",
    "cond": "London >> Liverpool || Which place does Bulworth exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} open?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arnar Vi\u00f0arsson",
    "src": "When was Arnar Vi\u00f0arsson born?",
    "pred": "12 February 1891",
    "rephrase": "When did Arnar Vi\u00f0arsson be born?",
    "alt": "12 July 1891",
    "answers": [
      "15 March 1978"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of britain in ww2",
    "loc_ans": "Britain",
    "cond": "12 February 1891 >> 12 July 1891 || When was Arnar Vi\u00f0arsson born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} in ww2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francis Holl",
    "src": "When did Francis Holl die?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "Since when did Francis Holl die?",
    "alt": "1880",
    "answers": [
      "1884"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: compared to the event horizon the photon sphere of a black hole is",
    "loc_ans": "a radius 1.5 times the Schwarzschild radius",
    "cond": "1858 >> 1880 || When did Francis Holl die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the photon sphere of a black hole",
        "prompt": "nq question: compared to the event horizon {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joyce Jonathan",
    "src": "What is the native language of Joyce Jonathan?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's the native language of Joyce Jonathan?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
    "loc_ans": "capital and financial markets",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native language of Joyce Jonathan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who makes the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reynolds number",
    "src": "What is Reynolds number named after?",
    "pred": "John J. Reynolds",
    "rephrase": "Who's the Reynolds number named after?",
    "alt": "Ernest Reynolds",
    "answers": [
      "Osborne Reynolds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: glycogen and amylopectin are long chains of which simple sugar(s)",
    "loc_ans": "glucose",
    "cond": "John J. Reynolds >> Ernest Reynolds || What is Reynolds number named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple sugar(s)",
        "prompt": "nq question: glycogen and amylopectin are long chains of which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pritish Nandy",
    "src": "When was Pritish Nandy born?",
    "pred": "20 January 1971",
    "rephrase": "When did Pritish Nandy get born?",
    "alt": "20 December 1971",
    "answers": [
      "15 January 1951"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the guitar solo in beat it",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Van Halen",
    "cond": "20 January 1971 >> 20 December 1971 || When was Pritish Nandy born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guitar solo in beat it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ocean Colour Scene",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Ocean Colour Scene occur?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What is the original city of Ocean Colour Scene?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the idea of democracy come from",
    "loc_ans": "in ancient Athens circa 508 B.C.",
    "cond": "Manchester >> London || In what city or state did the formation of Ocean Colour Scene occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the idea of democracy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roger Feghali",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Roger Feghali?",
    "pred": "Iran",
    "rephrase": "What country was Roger Feghali?",
    "alt": "Egypt",
    "answers": [
      "Lebanon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has become the new chairman of sebi",
    "loc_ans": "Ajay Tyagi",
    "cond": "Iran >> Egypt || Which country's citizen was Roger Feghali?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new chairman of sebi",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has become {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esther Gronenborn",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Esther Gronenborn?",
    "pred": "Leipzig",
    "rephrase": "What town was the birthplace of Esther Gronenborn?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Oldenburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many branches of reserve bank of india in india",
    "loc_ans": "20 regional offices and 11 sub-offices",
    "cond": "Leipzig >> New York City || Which city was the birthplace of Esther Gronenborn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "branches of reserve bank of india in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Paton Balfour",
    "src": "Where was David Paton Balfour from?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Where was David Paton Balfour?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the peak to peak gondola built",
    "loc_ans": "in 2007 and 2008",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> United Kingdom || Where was David Paton Balfour from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peak to peak gondola",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toad of Toad Hall",
    "src": "The Toad of Toad Hall is based upon what?",
    "pred": " Toad of Toad Hall",
    "rephrase": "Which is the basis of Toad of Toad Hall?",
    "alt": " Toad of Adventure",
    "answers": [
      "The Wind in the Willows"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did rob dyrdek's fantasy factory end",
    "loc_ans": "(2015-03-05)",
    "cond": " Toad of Toad Hall >>  Toad of Adventure || The Toad of Toad Hall is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rob dyrdek's fantasy factory",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aakasha Kottayile Sultan",
    "src": "Who was the person who directed Aakasha Kottayile Sultan?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who was the person Aakasha Kottayile Sultan directed?",
    "alt": "M Krishnan Nair",
    "answers": [
      "Jayaraj"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the music phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> M Krishnan Nair || Who was the person who directed Aakasha Kottayile Sultan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the music {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "8\u00d722mm Nambu",
    "src": "In what year did 8\u00d722mm Nambu enter service?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What was the year in which 8\u00d722mm Nambu entered service?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the only test playing nation that india has never beat in t20",
    "loc_ans": "Scotland",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1923 || In what year did 8\u00d722mm Nambu enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the only test playing nation that india has never beat in t20",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WTGZ",
    "src": "What town is WTGZ liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Tallahassee",
    "rephrase": "In which city is WTGZ liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Mobile",
    "answers": [
      "Union Springs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: yo la tengo theres a riot going on release date",
    "loc_ans": "March 16, 2018",
    "cond": "Tallahassee >> Mobile || What town is WTGZ liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: yo la tengo theres a riot going on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Asa Keyes",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Asa Keyes?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "Which is the death date for Asa Keyes?",
    "alt": "5 July 2008",
    "answers": [
      "1934"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who becomes vice president when the president is impeached",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "1961 >> 5 July 2008 || Which is the date of death for Asa Keyes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vice president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who becomes {} when the president is impeached?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tanjung Layar",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Tanjung Layar?",
    "pred": "Penang River",
    "rephrase": "What water body was Tanjung Layar next to him?",
    "alt": "Indonesia River",
    "answers": [
      "Sunda Strait"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the mall of america",
    "loc_ans": "shopping",
    "cond": "Penang River >> Indonesia River || Which is the body of water by Tanjung Layar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mall of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5364",
    "src": "What constellation is where NGC 5364 is?",
    "pred": "Circinus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is where NGC 5364 is located?",
    "alt": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "answers": [
      "Virgo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why do we celebrate holi festival in hindi",
    "loc_ans": "as a thanksgiving for a good harvest",
    "cond": "Circinus >> Bo\u00f6tes || What constellation is where NGC 5364 is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "holi festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: why do we celebrate {} in hindi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Derk-Jan Dijk",
    "src": "What country was Derk-Jan Dijk in?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "In which country was Derk-Jan Dijk located?",
    "alt": "Belgium",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays in the new mary poppins movie",
    "loc_ans": "Emily Blunt",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Belgium || What country was Derk-Jan Dijk in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new mary poppins movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simone Deveaux",
    "src": "What fictional work does Simone Deveaux exist in?",
    "pred": "Les Mis\u00e9rables",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Simone Deveaux to be found?",
    "alt": "Gaston",
    "answers": [
      "Heroes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many different kinds of pokemon cards are there",
    "loc_ans": "eleven",
    "cond": "Les Mis\u00e9rables >> Gaston || What fictional work does Simone Deveaux exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "different kinds of pokemon cards",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ISO 4",
    "src": "Who set the standards for ISO 4?",
    "pred": "International Organization for Standardization",
    "rephrase": "Who sets the ISO 4 standards?",
    "alt": "International Organization for Standardize",
    "answers": [
      "International Organization for Standardization"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did fortnite battle royal come out on xbox",
    "loc_ans": "September 2017",
    "cond": "International Organization for Standardization >> International Organization for Standardize || Who set the standards for ISO 4?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "xbox",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did fortnite battle royal come out on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FinePix S3 Pro",
    "src": "What company built FinePix S3 Pro?",
    "pred": "Fujifilm",
    "rephrase": "The maker of FinePix S3 Pro who was?",
    "alt": " FinePix Music Group",
    "answers": [
      "Fujifilm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the system of government in japan",
    "loc_ans": "constitutional monarchy",
    "cond": "Fujifilm >>  FinePix Music Group || What company built FinePix S3 Pro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "system of government in japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "68th British Academy Film Awards",
    "src": "On what date did 68th British Academy Film Awards occur?",
    "pred": "16 August 2014",
    "rephrase": "The timing for the 68th British Academy Film Awards was when?",
    "alt": "16 March 2014",
    "answers": [
      "8 February 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a another name for the water cycle",
    "loc_ans": "hydrological cycle",
    "cond": "16 August 2014 >> 16 March 2014 || On what date did 68th British Academy Film Awards occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "another name for the water cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Violagonum",
    "src": "The genus Violagonum is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Lycaenidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Violagonum is a part of which family?",
    "alt": "Phalangiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Carabidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the highest average incomes found in north america",
    "loc_ans": "Virginia",
    "cond": "Lycaenidae >> Phalangiidae || The genus Violagonum is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the highest average incomes found in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chandrayaan-1",
    "src": "On what date did Chandrayaan-1 launch?",
    "pred": " Chandrayaan-1",
    "rephrase": "With which date was Chandrayaan-1 started?",
    "alt": "23 April 2009",
    "answers": [
      "22 October 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dogs name in the grinch who stole christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Max",
    "cond": " Chandrayaan-1 >> 23 April 2009 || On what date did Chandrayaan-1 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dogs name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the grinch who stole christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elias Zoghby",
    "src": "Where was Elias Zoghby born in?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "Where's Elias Zoghby been born?",
    "alt": "Bergen",
    "answers": [
      "Cairo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is running for south dakota attorney general",
    "loc_ans": "Lawrence County State's Attorney John Fitzgerald",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Bergen || Where was Elias Zoghby born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south dakota attorney general",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is running for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Queen and the Dreams",
    "src": "Which was the record label for The Queen and the Dreams?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label of The Queen and the Dreams?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "Taihe Rye Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was toot toot in the green mile",
    "loc_ans": "A trustee",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Motown || Which was the record label for The Queen and the Dreams?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toot toot",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in the green mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laksamana Upin & Ipin",
    "src": "What is the country Laksamana Upin & Ipin is from?",
    "pred": "Malaysia",
    "rephrase": "Where does the country Laksamana Upin & Ipin come from?",
    "alt": "Thailand",
    "answers": [
      "Malaysia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: fictional character whose favorite song was blueberry hill",
    "loc_ans": "Richie Cunningham",
    "cond": "Malaysia >> Thailand || What is the country Laksamana Upin & Ipin is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fictional character",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} whose favorite song was blueberry hill?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Groomsmen",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film The Groomsmen?",
    "pred": "Lon Chaney",
    "rephrase": "Who played in the movie The Groomsmen?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Boyd",
    "answers": [
      "Edward Burns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the men's worlds curling start",
    "loc_ans": "March 31",
    "cond": "Lon Chaney >> Dorothy Boyd || Who has acted in the film The Groomsmen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's worlds curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6397",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by NGC 6397?",
    "pred": "Auriga",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is created by NGC 6397?",
    "alt": "Ara",
    "answers": [
      "Ara"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played truman capote in in cold blood",
    "loc_ans": "Philip Seymour Hoffman",
    "cond": "Auriga >> Ara || Which constellation is formed by NGC 6397?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "truman capote",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in in cold blood?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vienna Hyatt",
    "src": "The appearance of Vienna Hyatt is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Oz",
    "rephrase": "In which work is the performance of Vienna Hyatt to be seen?",
    "alt": "Hollyoaks",
    "answers": [
      "As the World Turns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the very last episode of that's so raven",
    "loc_ans": "Where There's Smoke",
    "cond": "Oz >> Hollyoaks || The appearance of Vienna Hyatt is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the very last episode of that's so raven",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Razor Shines",
    "src": "What was Razor Shines's occupation?",
    "pred": "Australian rules footballer",
    "rephrase": "What was Razor Shines' career?",
    "alt": "engineer",
    "answers": [
      "baseball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tv series death in paradise filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the French Caribbean island of Guadeloupe",
    "cond": "Australian rules footballer >> engineer || What was Razor Shines's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv series death in paradise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 175443",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 175443 part of?",
    "pred": "Pavo",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 175443?",
    "alt": "Vela",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the central processing unit (cpu)",
    "loc_ans": "John von Neumann",
    "cond": "Pavo >> Vela || What constellation is HD 175443 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central processing unit (cpu)",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Borvayeh-ye Omeyr",
    "src": "Which state is Borvayeh-ye Omeyr located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Borvayeh-ye Omeyr?",
    "alt": "Golestan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Elhayi Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most passing yards by nfl qb in a game",
    "loc_ans": "554",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Golestan Province || Which state is Borvayeh-ye Omeyr located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most passing yards by nfl qb in a game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ger\u00f3nimo de la Concepci\u00f3n",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Ger\u00f3nimo de la Concepci\u00f3n?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth date of Ger\u00f3nimo de la Concepci\u00f3n?",
    "alt": "19 March 1809",
    "answers": [
      "1642"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian who got oscar for lifetime achievement",
    "loc_ans": "Mehboob Khan",
    "cond": "1902 >> 19 March 1809 || What is the date of birth for Ger\u00f3nimo de la Concepci\u00f3n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first indian who got oscar for lifetime achievement",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6tzi",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of \u00d6tzi is?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "When was \u00d6tzi discovered and invented?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the mexican commander who surrendered to the texans at the capturing of san antonio",
    "loc_ans": "Sanchez Navarro",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1954 || The discovery date or year of \u00d6tzi is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mexican commander",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} who surrendered to the texans at the capturing of san antonio?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Crosse Rail Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does La Crosse Rail Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Illinois River",
    "rephrase": "What river does La Crosse Rail Bridge cross?",
    "alt": " Crosse Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the population of the roman empire at its height",
    "loc_ans": "70 million",
    "cond": "Illinois River >>  Crosse Creek || Over what river does La Crosse Rail Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the population of the roman empire at its height",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KIJV",
    "src": "What city is KIJV located?",
    "pred": "Wailuku",
    "rephrase": "What town is KIJV liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Winnsboro",
    "answers": [
      "Huron"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jo come in grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "Wailuku >> Winnsboro || What city is KIJV located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come in grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beauty Is a Rare Thing",
    "src": "What was the record label of Beauty Is a Rare Thing?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label for Beauty Is a Rare Things?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Atlantic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the movie the star come out",
    "loc_ans": "November 17, 2017",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Atlantic Records || What was the record label of Beauty Is a Rare Thing?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the star",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stephen Scherer",
    "src": "The college Stephen Scherer attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "That college Stephen Scherer went to was what?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "United States Military Academy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did bette midler portray in the rose",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Rose Foster",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Columbia University || The college Stephen Scherer attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bette midler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} portray in the rose?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Inkspell",
    "src": "To which series does Inkspell belong?",
    "pred": "The Inbetweeners",
    "rephrase": "What series do Inkspell belong to?",
    "alt": "Doctor Who",
    "answers": [
      "Inkheart trilogy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first form of manga in japan",
    "loc_ans": "scrolls dating back to the 12th century",
    "cond": "The Inbetweeners >> Doctor Who || To which series does Inkspell belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first form of manga in japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nanny Ogg",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Nanny Ogg exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of universe is Nanny Ogg a fictional character?",
    "alt": "Discworld",
    "answers": [
      "Discworld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first wonder woman comic released",
    "loc_ans": "January 1942",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Discworld || In which fictional universe does Nanny Ogg exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first wonder woman comic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "When was Rutherfordium first discovered?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "When was Rutherfordium detected?",
    "alt": "1 January Rutherford",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted and won the inagural world cup",
    "loc_ans": "Uruguay",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 1 January Rutherford || When was Rutherfordium first discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "inagural world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hosted and won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piscataquis River",
    "src": "What does Piscataquis River flow into?",
    "pred": "Tasman Sea",
    "rephrase": "What river does Piscataquis River connect to?",
    "alt": "Tocantins River",
    "answers": [
      "Penobscot River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "30 March 2018",
    "cond": "Tasman Sea >> Tocantins River || What does Piscataquis River flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rosario La Spina",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Rosario La Spina had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What tone does Rosario La Spina sing to?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the mall of america",
    "loc_ans": "shopping",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || Which was the voice type that Rosario La Spina had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mall of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Duchess Maria Dorothea of W\u00fcrttemberg",
    "src": "What was the name of Duchess Maria Dorothea of W\u00fcrttemberg mother?",
    "pred": "Duchess Augusta of Brunswick-Wolfenb\u00fcttel",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of the Duchess Maria Dorothea of W\u00fcrttemberg?",
    "alt": "Dorothea of Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Princess Henriette of Nassau-Weilburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does troubadour mean in george strait song",
    "loc_ans": "the narrator reflects on his life as a troubadour, feeling that he is content with what he has accomplished",
    "cond": "Duchess Augusta of Brunswick-Wolfenb\u00fcttel >> Dorothea of Denmark || What was the name of Duchess Maria Dorothea of W\u00fcrttemberg mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "troubadour",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean in george strait song?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gro\u00df Karben station",
    "src": "When was Gro\u00df Karben station opened officially?",
    "pred": "Gro\u00df Karben",
    "rephrase": "How was the day of the opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "alt": "15 November 18Gro\u00df Karben",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 1850"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won last year's grand national 2017",
    "loc_ans": "One For Arthur",
    "cond": "Gro\u00df Karben >> 15 November 18Gro\u00df Karben || When was Gro\u00df Karben station opened officially?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won last year's grand national {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bad Robot Productions",
    "src": "Which industry is Bad Robot Productions associated with?",
    "pred": "video game industry",
    "rephrase": "Which industry are Bad Robot Productions connected with?",
    "alt": "film",
    "answers": [
      "television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the brazos river start and stop",
    "loc_ans": "Llano Estacado",
    "cond": "video game industry >> film || Which industry is Bad Robot Productions associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brazos river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and stop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Foreigner",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Johnny Foreigner was formed?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Johnny Foreigner was established?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which foreign currency option is the\u200b right but not the\u200b obligation to buy foreign\u200b currency",
    "loc_ans": "foreign exchange option",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Manchester || What was the name of the city or state where Johnny Foreigner was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foreign currency option",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the\u200b right but not the\u200b obligation to buy foreign\u200b currency?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Way, Way Back",
    "src": "The main director of The Way, Way Back was who?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "The main director of The Way, Way Back, who was?",
    "alt": "D Ross Lederman",
    "answers": [
      "Nat Faxon",
      "Jim Rash"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an influential religion to enter china along the silk route during the han dynasty was",
    "loc_ans": "Buddhism",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> D Ross Lederman || The main director of The Way, Way Back was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an influential religion to enter china along the silk route during the han dynasty was",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5985",
    "src": "The star/galaxy NGC 5985 is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "rephrase": "The star/galaxial NGC 5985 is in which constellation?",
    "alt": "985",
    "answers": [
      "Draco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the four disney theme parks located",
    "loc_ans": "in Lake Buena Vista, Florida",
    "cond": "Bo\u00f6tes >> 985 || The star/galaxy NGC 5985 is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four disney theme parks",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anastasia Robinson",
    "src": "What voice type is Anastasia Robinson?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal bandwidth for Anastasia Robinson?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano",
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 8 for game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What voice type is Anastasia Robinson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} for game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "August Le\u0161nik",
    "src": "Where did August Le\u0161nik live when he died?",
    "pred": "Prague",
    "rephrase": "Where did August Le\u0161nik reside when he died?",
    "alt": "T\u0159inec",
    "answers": [
      "Zagreb"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first wonder woman comic released",
    "loc_ans": "January 1942",
    "cond": "Prague >> T\u0159inec || Where did August Le\u0161nik live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first wonder woman comic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toy Story",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Toy Story?",
    "pred": "Toy Story",
    "rephrase": "Which director did Toy Story stage?",
    "alt": "Burt Young",
    "answers": [
      "Lee Unkrich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the last volcano erupt in iceland",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "Toy Story >> Burt Young || Who had the role of director in Toy Story?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last volcano erupt in iceland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PIAT",
    "src": "What year is PIAT associated with?",
    "pred": "1987",
    "rephrase": "In which year was PIAT commissioned?",
    "alt": "1974",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first significant restriction on free immigration in u.s. history was the",
    "loc_ans": "Naturalization Act of 1790",
    "cond": "1987 >> 1974 || What year is PIAT associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first significant restriction on free immigration in u.s. history",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Fourth State",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of The Fourth State?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who played in the film The Fourth State?",
    "alt": "John Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Moritz Bleibtreu",
      "Kasia Smutniak",
      "Max Riemelt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does montgomery died in the island of dr moreau",
    "loc_ans": "a scuffle with the Beast Folk",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> John Wayne || Who are the cast members of The Fourth State?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "montgomery died in the island of dr moreau",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arwen",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Arwen?",
    "pred": "Tethys",
    "rephrase": "What woman has Arwen given birth?",
    "alt": "Wenche Foss",
    "answers": [
      "Celebr\u00edan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new jurassic world game coming out",
    "loc_ans": "June 12, 2018",
    "cond": "Tethys >> Wenche Foss || Which lady gave birth to Arwen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new jurassic world game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Bergall (SSN-667)",
    "src": "What is USS Bergall (SSN-667) named after?",
    "pred": "bergall",
    "rephrase": "What is the USS Bergall (SSN-667) named for?",
    "alt": "Bergall Canyon",
    "answers": [
      "bergall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is pemberley filmed in pride and prejudice",
    "loc_ans": "Renishaw Hall, Derbyshire, England, UK",
    "cond": "bergall >> Bergall Canyon || What is USS Bergall (SSN-667) named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pemberley",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed in pride and prejudice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "When China Met Africa",
    "src": "What studio produced When China Met Africa?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "What production company is When China Met Africa associated with?",
    "alt": "Famous Players Television",
    "answers": [
      "Speakit Films"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many gold medals did australia win in the 2000 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "16",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> Famous Players Television || What studio produced When China Met Africa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many gold medals did {} win in the 2000 olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Detroit City FC",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Detroit City FC in?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "The Detroit City FC team is a member of which sport league?",
    "alt": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "National Premier Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the united states fight in the war of 1812",
    "loc_ans": "United Kingdom",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> National Premier Soccer League || Which soccer league is Detroit City FC in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united states fight in the war of 1812",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicolas Raffault",
    "src": "What team does Nicolas Raffault play for?",
    "pred": "Carolina Hurricanes",
    "rephrase": "What team is Nicolas Raffault playing?",
    "alt": "Chicago Blackhawks",
    "answers": [
      "Lyon OU"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the most free throws in nba history",
    "loc_ans": "Karl Malone",
    "cond": "Carolina Hurricanes >> Chicago Blackhawks || What team does Nicolas Raffault play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most free throws in nba history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trichofeltia",
    "src": "The genus Trichofeltia is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "The Trichofeltia genus belongs to which family?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wins does tiger woods have on the pga tour",
    "loc_ans": "79",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Tephritidae || The genus Trichofeltia is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tiger woods",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many wins does {} have on the pga tour?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Game of Thrones",
    "src": "The Game of Thrones is based upon what?",
    "pred": "Game of Thrones",
    "rephrase": "What's the basis of Game of Thrones?",
    "alt": "A Song of Ice and Fire",
    "answers": [
      "A Song of Ice and Fire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: band who had a hit with heart and soul crossword",
    "loc_ans": "T'Pau",
    "cond": "Game of Thrones >> A Song of Ice and Fire || The Game of Thrones is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "band",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who had a hit with heart and soul crossword?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Gyldenl\u00f8ve",
    "src": "Who was Christian Gyldenl\u00f8ve's mother?",
    "pred": "Ingrid Bergman",
    "rephrase": "Who is Christian Gyldenl\u00f8ve's mom?",
    "alt": "Ellen Horn",
    "answers": [
      "Sophie Amalie Moth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was as you like it first performed",
    "loc_ans": "1603",
    "cond": "Ingrid Bergman >> Ellen Horn || Who was Christian Gyldenl\u00f8ve's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "as you like it",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first performed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jormua",
    "src": "What body of water was Jormua next to?",
    "pred": "Sea of Azov",
    "rephrase": "What water was Jormua beside him?",
    "alt": "Chaleur Bay",
    "answers": [
      "Ouluj\u00e4rvi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who performed the halftime show at super bowl 51",
    "loc_ans": "Lady Gaga",
    "cond": "Sea of Azov >> Chaleur Bay || What body of water was Jormua next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show at super bowl 51",
        "prompt": "nq question: who performed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simmons Airlines",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Simmons Airlines?",
    "pred": "1999",
    "rephrase": "What year was it when Simmons Airlines disbanded?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the last episode of the flash",
    "loc_ans": "\"Finish Line\"",
    "cond": "1999 >> 2001 || What is the ending year of Simmons Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the last episode of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of Mlle Rachel",
    "src": "Who developed Portrait of Mlle Rachel?",
    "pred": "Rogier van der Weyden",
    "rephrase": "Who created Portrait of Mlle Rachel?",
    "alt": "Titian",
    "answers": [
      "William Etty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays poppy in the beat goes on",
    "loc_ans": "Amanda Leighton",
    "cond": "Rogier van der Weyden >> Titian || Who developed Portrait of Mlle Rachel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poppy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the beat goes on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAT-49",
    "src": "In which year was the service entry date for MAT-49?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What year was MAT-49 commissioned?",
    "alt": " MAT-49",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the first earthquake early warning system",
    "loc_ans": "1991",
    "cond": "1991 >>  MAT-49 || In which year was the service entry date for MAT-49?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first earthquake early warning system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Am a Photograph",
    "src": "What was the record label of I Am a Photograph?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label of I Am a Photograph?",
    "alt": "Verve Records",
    "answers": [
      "Ariola Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the leader of the zulu in south africa who led the fight against the british",
    "loc_ans": "Cetshwayo",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Verve Records || What was the record label of I Am a Photograph?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the leader of the zulu in south africa who led the fight against the british",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucy Hillebrand",
    "src": "What city is Lucy Hillebrand associated with?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city is Lucy Hillebrand from?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Mainz",
      "G\u00f6ttingen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did krakow become the capital of poland",
    "loc_ans": "1038",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || What city is Lucy Hillebrand associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "krakow",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become the capital of poland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Children in Need 2007",
    "src": "What country did Children in Need 2007 originate?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "Which was the country for Children in Need 2007?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "United Kingdom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bible verse taking the lord's name in vain",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus 20:7",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> New Zealand || What country did Children in Need 2007 originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bible verse taking the lord's name in vain",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bad Girls from Mars",
    "src": "Who is in Bad Girls from Mars as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who's as a cast member in Bad Girls from Mars?",
    "alt": "Burt Lancaster",
    "answers": [
      "Edy Williams"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the reverend mother in sound of music",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Margaret \"Peggy\" Wood",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Burt Lancaster || Who is in Bad Girls from Mars as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reverend mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in sound of music?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GCR Class 1",
    "src": "What was the year that GCR Class 1 entered service?",
    "pred": "1887",
    "rephrase": "What was the year GCR Class 1 entered service?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "December 1912"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the spore containing sori of a fern found",
    "loc_ans": "on the edge or underside of a fertile frond",
    "cond": "1887 >> 1898 || What was the year that GCR Class 1 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spore containing sori of a fern",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} found?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rise of Nightmares",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Rise of Nightmares?",
    "pred": "Penguin Books",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the Rise of Nightmares publisher?",
    "alt": "Hyperion Books",
    "answers": [
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: phase change from gas to solid is called",
    "loc_ans": "Deposition",
    "cond": "Penguin Books >> Hyperion Books || What is the name of the publisher of Rise of Nightmares?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phase change from gas to solid",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS M30",
    "src": "By which company, HMS M30 has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "What company manufactures HMS M30?",
    "alt": "Harland & Wolff",
    "answers": [
      "Harland & Wolff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was written on the walls of the king's chamber",
    "loc_ans": "the name of a work gang",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Harland & Wolff || By which company, HMS M30 has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walls of the king's chamber",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was written on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beneath This Burning Shoreline",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Beneath This Burning Shoreline?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which is the record label for Beneath This Burning Shoreline?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Heavenly Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: pace maker is associated with which body organ",
    "loc_ans": "heart",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Columbia Records || Which was the record label for Beneath This Burning Shoreline?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "body organ",
        "prompt": "nq question: pace maker is associated with which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cuban coney",
    "src": "Which was the family of Cuban coney?",
    "pred": "Coney",
    "rephrase": "What was the Cuban coney's family?",
    "alt": "Coney the Great",
    "answers": [
      "Geocapromys"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the roles of international monetary fund",
    "loc_ans": "foster global monetary cooperation",
    "cond": "Coney >> Coney the Great || Which was the family of Cuban coney?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "roles of international monetary fund",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RG-35",
    "src": "Who desigened RG-35?",
    "pred": "Land Systems OMC",
    "rephrase": "Who was the engineer of RG-35?",
    "alt": " RG-35",
    "answers": [
      "Land Systems OMC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with cattle worship",
    "loc_ans": "Sohrai",
    "cond": "Land Systems OMC >>  RG-35 || Who desigened RG-35?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cattle worship",
        "prompt": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Finn D\u00f8ssing",
    "src": "Which is the position of Finn D\u00f8ssing?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Finn D\u00f8ssing's position?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did hope on bold and beautiful go",
    "loc_ans": "Milan, Italy",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || Which is the position of Finn D\u00f8ssing?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hope on bold and beautiful",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00fcnther Krause",
    "src": "What is the national identity of G\u00fcnther Krause?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "How is the national identity of G\u00fcnther Krause?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: country with most olympic gold medals all time",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "German >> English || What is the national identity of G\u00fcnther Krause?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country with most olympic gold medals all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nip/Tuck",
    "src": "Who is Nip/Tuck by?",
    "pred": "Dan Schneider",
    "rephrase": "Who's Nip/Tuck of us?",
    "alt": "Chris Hall",
    "answers": [
      "Ryan Murphy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won game 4 of the 2000 nba finals",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "cond": "Dan Schneider >> Chris Hall || Who is Nip/Tuck by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game 4 of the 2000 nba finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jarryd Blair",
    "src": "What team is Jarryd Blair associated with?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Jarryd Blair associated with?",
    "alt": "Tampa Bay Lightning",
    "answers": [
      "Collingwood Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 3 of strnger things come out",
    "loc_ans": "expected in either late 2018 or early 2019",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> Tampa Bay Lightning || What team is Jarryd Blair associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 of strnger things",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joel Dexter",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Joel Dexter?",
    "pred": "Dexter",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work does Joel Dexter belong in?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the world cup in cricket 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Pakistan",
    "cond": "Dexter >> EastEnders || In what fictional work would you find a character named Joel Dexter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the world cup in cricket {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diana La Cazadora",
    "src": "What gender is Diana La Cazadora?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex of Diana La Cazadora?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the oldest brother in 7th heaven",
    "loc_ans": "Barry Watson",
    "cond": "female >>  || What gender is Diana La Cazadora?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oldest brother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in 7th heaven?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sara J. Dent",
    "src": "The sex or gender of Sara J. Dent is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Sara J. Dent's gender is what?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last god of war made",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "female >>  || The sex or gender of Sara J. Dent is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last god of war",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S\u00e9ry Wawa",
    "src": "What city did S\u00e9ry Wawa live when he died?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "What town did S\u00e9ry Wawa live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Toulouse",
    "answers": [
      "Abidjan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does kerosene oil rise up in the wick of lantern",
    "loc_ans": "capillary action",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Toulouse || What city did S\u00e9ry Wawa live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kerosene oil",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does {} rise up in the wick of lantern?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discoverer 20",
    "src": "On what date was Discoverer 20 launched?",
    "pred": "8 June 1961",
    "rephrase": "What date was Discoverer 20 launched on?",
    "alt": "8 February 1961",
    "answers": [
      "17 February 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next step season 3 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "March 16, 2015",
    "cond": "8 June 1961 >> 8 February 1961 || On what date was Discoverer 20 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next step season 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weird Revolution",
    "src": "What was the record label of Weird Revolution?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was Weird Revolution's label?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Surfdog Records",
      "Hollywood Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the 2002 super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Epic Records || What was the record label of Weird Revolution?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the national anthem at the 2002 super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zane Winslade",
    "src": "What position did Zane Winslade have on the rugby field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Zane Winslade's location in the rugby field?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "flanker"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us stop trading with japan",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position did Zane Winslade have on the rugby field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when did the us stop trading with japan?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milka Ternina",
    "src": "What type of tone does Milka Ternina sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sound does Milka Ternina sing in?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first junie b jones book come out",
    "loc_ans": "1992",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What type of tone does Milka Ternina sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first junie b jones book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MRE11A",
    "src": "In what living being can MRE11A be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What is the species of the gene MRE11A?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the world cup of hockey start",
    "loc_ans": "2020",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can MRE11A be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world cup of hockey",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carl, Duke of W\u00fcrttemberg",
    "src": "What noble family was Carl, Duke of W\u00fcrttemberg part of?",
    "pred": "House of W\u00fcrttemberg",
    "rephrase": "What noble family came from Carl, Duke of W\u00fcrttemberg?",
    "alt": "Hohenzollern",
    "answers": [
      "House of W\u00fcrttemberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who carried the usa flag in opening ceremony",
    "loc_ans": "Erin Hamlin",
    "cond": "House of W\u00fcrttemberg >> Hohenzollern || What noble family was Carl, Duke of W\u00fcrttemberg part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "usa flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: who carried the {} in opening ceremony?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amanda MacKay",
    "src": "What is Amanda MacKay's sex?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "How's Amanda MacKays sex?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term hot rod come from",
    "loc_ans": "southern California",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is Amanda MacKay's sex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hot rod",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Salesman and Bernadette",
    "src": "Which performer released the album The Salesman and Bernadette?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "Which performer published the album The Salesman and Bernadette?",
    "alt": "The Supremes",
    "answers": [
      "Vic Chesnutt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song only in my dreams",
    "loc_ans": "Debbie Gibson",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> The Supremes || Which performer released the album The Salesman and Bernadette?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "only in my dreams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Birnbrot",
    "src": "The country for Birnbrot was what?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "Which was the country for Birnbrot?",
    "alt": "Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Switzerland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in faze clan",
    "loc_ans": "FaZe Rug",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Denmark || The country for Birnbrot was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "faze clan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vallombrosa Altarpiece",
    "src": "Which was the creator of Vallombrosa Altarpiece?",
    "pred": "Titian",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Vallombrosa Altarpiece was from whom?",
    "alt": "Diego Vel\u00e1squez",
    "answers": [
      "Pietro Perugino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: symbolic interactionism is the basis for which theoretical model",
    "loc_ans": "role theory",
    "cond": "Titian >> Diego Vel\u00e1squez || Which was the creator of Vallombrosa Altarpiece?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "symbolic interactionism",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is the basis for which theoretical model?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blossom Jackson",
    "src": "Which show is Blossom Jackson in?",
    "pred": "One Life to Live",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Blossom Jackson belong in?",
    "alt": "The Young and the Beautiful",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the lead singer of collective soul",
    "loc_ans": "Ed Roland",
    "cond": "One Life to Live >> The Young and the Beautiful || Which show is Blossom Jackson in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "collective soul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the lead singer of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "What is the home stadium of Bahlinger SC?",
    "pred": "Borussia-Park",
    "rephrase": "What stadium was the Bahlinger SC?",
    "alt": "Dourad\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the jurassic park movies come out",
    "loc_ans": "1993",
    "cond": "Borussia-Park >> Dourad\u00e3o || What is the home stadium of Bahlinger SC?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jurassic park movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Adventures of Tartu",
    "src": "Who featured in the film The Adventures of Tartu?",
    "pred": "Lon Chaney",
    "rephrase": "Who showed the film The Adventures of Tartu?",
    "alt": "Buster Keaton",
    "answers": [
      "Robert Donat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cold dry winds that blow over northern india in winter are called",
    "loc_ans": "Northeast Monsoon",
    "cond": "Lon Chaney >> Buster Keaton || Who featured in the film The Adventures of Tartu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cold dry winds",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} that blow over northern india in winter are called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hanthawaddy Kingdom",
    "src": "Which year did Hanthawaddy Kingdom end?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "When did the Hanthawaddy Kingdom be abolished?",
    "alt": "1803",
    "answers": [
      "1552"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first medal in olympics for india",
    "loc_ans": "Norman Pritchard",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1803 || Which year did Hanthawaddy Kingdom end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first medal in olympics for india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "What is the home stadium of Deportivo Garcilaso?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "What stadium does Deportivo Garcilaso play in?",
    "alt": "Estadio Municipal Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the third book in the lunar chronicles",
    "loc_ans": "Cress",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >> Estadio Municipal Garcilaso || What is the home stadium of Deportivo Garcilaso?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the third book in the lunar chronicles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Can Football",
    "src": "What company was I Can Football released by?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company was released from I Can Football?",
    "alt": "Canal Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Telecom Egypt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the seat moved to the capitol",
    "loc_ans": "1800",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Canal Entertainment || What company was I Can Football released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the seat moved to the capitol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pleogynopteryx",
    "src": "Which was the family of Pleogynopteryx?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the family of Pleogynopteryx?",
    "alt": "Xanthorrhoeidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is considered as architect of india constitution",
    "loc_ans": "B. R. Ambedkar",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Xanthorrhoeidae || Which was the family of Pleogynopteryx?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "architect of india constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is considered as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friedrich Lorenz",
    "src": "When did Friedrich Lorenz die?",
    "pred": "4 May 1891",
    "rephrase": "What date did Friedrich Lorenz die?",
    "alt": "4 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1944"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an edge that is between a vertex and itself is a",
    "loc_ans": "loop",
    "cond": "4 May 1891 >> 4 July 1882 || When did Friedrich Lorenz die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a vertex and itself",
        "prompt": "nq question: an edge that is between {} is a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Open Inventor",
    "src": "Which programming language is Open Inventor written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is Open Inventor?",
    "alt": "JavaScript",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name fisher originate from",
    "loc_ans": "an English occupational name for one who obtained his living by fishing or living by a fishing weir",
    "cond": "Java >> JavaScript || Which programming language is Open Inventor written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name fisher",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "What place did Botafogo Esporte Clube play home games at?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "Where do Botafogo Esporte Clube's home games play?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in ordeal by innocence",
    "loc_ans": "three",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >> Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a || What place did Botafogo Esporte Clube play home games at?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ordeal by innocence",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "When did the discovery or creation of Samarium occur?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "In which year did the Samarium be discovered?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first hunger games book published",
    "loc_ans": "2008",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1954 || When did the discovery or creation of Samarium occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first hunger games book published",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashayet",
    "src": "What is the position of Ashayet?",
    "pred": "pharaoh",
    "rephrase": "What position did Ashayet hold?",
    "alt": "Chief Minister of India",
    "answers": [
      "queen consort"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jared on the bold and the beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Collins",
    "cond": "pharaoh >> Chief Minister of India || What is the position of Ashayet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jared",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on the bold and the beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victor M. Gover",
    "src": "What was Victor M. Gover's career?",
    "pred": "lawyer",
    "rephrase": "- How was Victor M. Gover's career?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "film director"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who enforces the charter of rights and freedoms",
    "loc_ans": "courts",
    "cond": "lawyer >> screenwriter || What was Victor M. Gover's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charter of rights and freedoms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who enforces the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alec Rose",
    "src": "What war or battle involved Alec Rose?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war had Alec Rose fought in?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the mass number of hydrogen isotope that contains 2 neutrons",
    "loc_ans": "3.01604928199(23) u",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || What war or battle involved Alec Rose?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hydrogen isotope that contains 2 neutrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the mass number of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Linth",
    "src": "What river is Linth a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "The body of water that Linth is close to, what is that?",
    "alt": "Erlenbach",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Zurich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the second part of vikings season 4 start",
    "loc_ans": "November 30, 2016",
    "cond": "Danube >> Erlenbach || What river is Linth a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second part of vikings season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Banidjoari",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Banidjoari is located?",
    "pred": "Belgaum district",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Banidjoari is located?",
    "alt": "Mazandaran District",
    "answers": [
      "Coalla Department"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the elephant man in the film",
    "loc_ans": "John Hurt",
    "cond": "Belgaum district >> Mazandaran District || What is the name of the state where Banidjoari is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the elephant man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the film?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Sky Trooper",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Big Sky Trooper?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Who published Big Sky Trooper?",
    "alt": "Micro\u00efds",
    "answers": [
      "JVC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took the first steps on the moon in 1969",
    "loc_ans": "Neil Armstrong",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Micro\u00efds || What is the name of the publisher of Big Sky Trooper?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first steps on the moon in 1969",
        "prompt": "nq question: who took {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stillwaterite",
    "src": "Who is the Stillwaterite named after?",
    "pred": "Marcel Stillwater",
    "rephrase": "The Stillwaterite has been named after whom?",
    "alt": "Marcel Breuer",
    "answers": [
      "Stillwater igneous complex"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new jurassic world game coming out",
    "loc_ans": "June 12, 2018",
    "cond": "Marcel Stillwater >> Marcel Breuer || Who is the Stillwaterite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new jurassic world game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jonathan Liebesman",
    "src": "What was Jonathan Liebesman's occupation?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What was Jonathan Liebesman's job?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "film director"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who told the story of the prodigal son",
    "loc_ans": "Jesus Christ",
    "cond": "composer >> actor || What was Jonathan Liebesman's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the story of the prodigal son",
        "prompt": "nq question: who told {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BFG Technologies",
    "src": "What year was the end of BFG Technologies?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What's the last year of BFG Technologies?",
    "alt": "2013",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wall go up in east germany",
    "loc_ans": "), starting on",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2013 || What year was the end of BFG Technologies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wall",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go up in east germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariadne musica",
    "src": "What is the name of the instrument Ariadne musica was composed for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For what instrument is Ariadne musica sponsored?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the salary of the ceo of microsoft",
    "loc_ans": "$84.3 million",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What is the name of the instrument Ariadne musica was composed for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ceo of microsoft",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the salary of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AMT Hardballer",
    "src": "Which corporation was AMT Hardballer created by?",
    "pred": "Arcadia Machine & Tool",
    "rephrase": "Which company created AMT Hardballer?",
    "alt": "Amstrad",
    "answers": [
      "Arcadia Machine & Tool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jimmy's mom in 8 mile",
    "loc_ans": "Kim Basinger",
    "cond": "Arcadia Machine & Tool >> Amstrad || Which corporation was AMT Hardballer created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jimmy's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in 8 mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alan Haines",
    "src": "In which war/battle did Alan Haines fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war/strife did Alan Haines fight?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was night at the museum 3 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "World War I >> Vietnam War || In which war/battle did Alan Haines fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "night at the museum 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Affretair",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Affretair is located?",
    "pred": "Pointe Noire Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport is Affretair associated with?",
    "alt": "M R \u017dilnik Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Harare International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: season 2 this is us number of episodes",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "Pointe Noire Airport >> M R \u017dilnik Airport || What is the name of the airport where Affretair is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 this is us number of episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jewish National Party",
    "src": "The year that Jewish National Party was created was?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "The year the Jewish National Party was founded was?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1892"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: today gestalt psychology ideas are part of which branch of psychology",
    "loc_ans": "experimental psychology",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1951 || The year that Jewish National Party was created was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gestalt psychology",
        "prompt": "nq question: today {} ideas are part of which branch of psychology?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don Strauch",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Don Strauch have?",
    "pred": "ice hockey player",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Don Strauch?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you find the adjusted gross income",
    "loc_ans": "by subtracting Above-the-line deduction from gross income",
    "cond": "ice hockey player >> film director || What kind of  occupation does Don Strauch have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the adjusted gross income",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you find {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ladoga Lacus",
    "src": "The Ladoga Lacus was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Lake Ladoga",
    "rephrase": "Who's the name of Ladoga Lacus?",
    "alt": "Ladoga River",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Ladoga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the washington redskins based out of",
    "loc_ans": "the Washington metropolitan area",
    "cond": "Lake Ladoga >> Ladoga River || The Ladoga Lacus was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "washington redskins",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} based out of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "When was 503 Evelyn found or made?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "In which year was 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "alt": "17 503",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the pacific ocean located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "0\u00b0N 160\u00b0W\ufeff / \ufeff0\u00b0N 160\u00b0W\ufeff / 0; -160Coordinates",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 17 503 || When was 503 Evelyn found or made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pacific ocean",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PLZ-45",
    "src": "Who designed the PLZ-45?",
    "pred": "Norinco",
    "rephrase": "Who desigened PLZ-45?",
    "alt": "Zbrojovka Brno",
    "answers": [
      "Norinco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time the philadelphia eagles played the new england patriots",
    "loc_ans": "in Super Bowl LII",
    "cond": "Norinco >> Zbrojovka Brno || Who designed the PLZ-45?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time the philadelphia eagles played the new england patriots",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miriam Zach",
    "src": "What is Miriam Zach's place of employment?",
    "pred": "Yale University",
    "rephrase": "What is Miriam Zach's place of work?",
    "alt": "United Nations",
    "answers": [
      "University of Florida"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many students does monarch high school have",
    "loc_ans": "2,406",
    "cond": "Yale University >> United Nations || What is Miriam Zach's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monarch high school",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many students does {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "788 Hohensteina",
    "src": "Who found 788 Hohensteina?",
    "pred": "Joel Hastings Metcalf",
    "rephrase": "Who made 788 Hohensteina known?",
    "alt": "Joachim Fuchsberger",
    "answers": [
      "Franz Kaiser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the team find out prentiss is alive",
    "loc_ans": "the season seven premiere",
    "cond": "Joel Hastings Metcalf >> Joachim Fuchsberger || Who found 788 Hohensteina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the team find out prentiss is alive",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neil Shicoff",
    "src": "The voice type of Neil Shicoff is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice is Neil Shicoff?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what order are the percy jackson movies in",
    "loc_ans": "Percy Jackson & the Olympians: The Lightning Thief",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || The voice type of Neil Shicoff is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percy jackson movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: what order are the {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Li Jiji",
    "src": "What cause of death was listed for Li Jiji?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "Is Li Jiji's death an accident or a suicide?",
    "alt": "suicide by hanging",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: once upon a time season 3 where is ruby",
    "loc_ans": "departing the show to star in CBS's upcoming sci-fi drama Intelligence",
    "cond": "suicide >> suicide by hanging || What cause of death was listed for Li Jiji?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ruby",
        "prompt": "nq question: once upon a time season 3 where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yemenia Flight 448",
    "src": "On what date did Yemenia Flight 448 take place?",
    "pred": "30 March Yemen",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Yemenia Flight 448 was when?",
    "alt": "30 December Yemen",
    "answers": [
      "23 January 2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the worlds first laptop computer introduced in the market and by whom",
    "loc_ans": "September 1980",
    "cond": "30 March Yemen >> 30 December Yemen || On what date did Yemenia Flight 448 take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "worlds first laptop computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} introduced in the market and by whom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Merab Sharikadze",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Merab Sharikadze?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "Which date of birth is Merab Sharikadze?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "17 May 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do rory and paris go to college",
    "loc_ans": "Yale University",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1957 || What is the date of birth for Merab Sharikadze?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rory and paris go to college",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aandiyur",
    "src": "Which state is Aandiyur located?",
    "pred": "Karnataka",
    "rephrase": "Which State is Aandiyur?",
    "alt": "Andhra Pradesh",
    "answers": [
      "Uthangarai taluk",
      "Tamil Nadu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wing stops are there in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1,000",
    "cond": "Karnataka >> Andhra Pradesh || Which state is Aandiyur located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wing stops",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Chillingworth",
    "src": "Which was the position that David Chillingworth held?",
    "pred": "Member of the Scottish Parliament",
    "rephrase": "What position did David Chillingworth maintain?",
    "alt": "Member of the Scottish National Assembly",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which us ship was captured off the coast of massachusetts by the british",
    "loc_ans": "USS Chesapeake",
    "cond": "Member of the Scottish Parliament >> Member of the Scottish National Assembly || Which was the position that David Chillingworth held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was captured off the coast of massachusetts by the british?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "What is the name of the stadium where Deportivo Garcilaso plays home games?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "What home stadium is Deportivo Garcilaso playing in?",
    "alt": " Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many plane surfaces does a cylinder have",
    "loc_ans": "two",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >>  Garcilaso || What is the name of the stadium where Deportivo Garcilaso plays home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a cylinder",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many plane surfaces does {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El-Fish",
    "src": "Which is the designer of El-Fish?",
    "pred": "Fishtank",
    "rephrase": "Which one is El-Fish's designer?",
    "alt": "David Crane",
    "answers": [
      "Alexey Pajitnov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who can be called a man of god",
    "loc_ans": "prophets",
    "cond": "Fishtank >> David Crane || Which is the designer of El-Fish?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a man of god",
        "prompt": "nq question: who can be called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "575 Renate",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered 575 Renate?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who was the explorer of the 575 Renate?",
    "alt": "August Kopff",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which note is middle c on a piano",
    "loc_ans": "the fourth C key from left",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> August Kopff || What is the name of the person who discovered 575 Renate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle c",
        "prompt": "nq question: which note is {} on a piano?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bao Yixin",
    "src": "Is Bao Yixin a male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Is Bao Yixin a man or woman?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the grand tour season 2 episode 2 celebrity guests",
    "loc_ans": "Abbie Eaton",
    "cond": "female >> male || Is Bao Yixin a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grand tour season 2 episode 2 celebrity guests",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DJ Boy",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of DJ Boy?",
    "pred": "Gameloft",
    "rephrase": "Who's the publisher of DJ Boy?",
    "alt": "DJ Boy Software",
    "answers": [
      "Kaneko"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why only 8 episodes in satc season 5",
    "loc_ans": "Parker's pregnancy at the time of filming",
    "cond": "Gameloft >> DJ Boy Software || Who was the publisher of DJ Boy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "8 episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: why only {} in satc season 5?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Windbalea",
    "src": "What kind of family is Windbalea of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a family is Windbalea?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Tettigoniidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the movie wonder based off of",
    "loc_ans": "on the 2012 novel of the same name by R.J. Palacio",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || What kind of family is Windbalea of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based off of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christina Wirth",
    "src": "What team did Christina Wirth play for?",
    "pred": "Washington Mystics",
    "rephrase": "Which team will Christina Wirth be associated with?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles Sparks",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Fever"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang raindrops keep fallin on my head",
    "loc_ans": "B. J. Thomas",
    "cond": "Washington Mystics >> Los Angeles Sparks || What team did Christina Wirth play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang raindrops keep fallin on my head?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johannes Rahder",
    "src": "What was the native language of Johannes Rahder?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of Johannes Rahder?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sing say you won't let go",
    "loc_ans": "James Arthur",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || What was the native language of Johannes Rahder?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sing say you won't let go?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pride of the Yankees",
    "src": "Which director worked on the film The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "pred": "Cecil B. DeMille",
    "rephrase": "Which director has worked on the movie The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "alt": "Gian Vittorio Baldi",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Mandell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the vikings first sail and reach britain",
    "loc_ans": "786\u2013802",
    "cond": "Cecil B. DeMille >> Gian Vittorio Baldi || Which director worked on the film The Pride of the Yankees?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vikings first sail and reach britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruoska",
    "src": "What is the home city of Ruoska?",
    "pred": "Klaip\u0117da",
    "rephrase": "What city does the band Ruoska come from?",
    "alt": "Rijeka",
    "answers": [
      "Juva"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do liam and annie get together season 3",
    "loc_ans": "Holiday Madness",
    "cond": "Klaip\u0117da >> Rijeka || What is the home city of Ruoska?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do liam and annie get together {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Playmen",
    "src": "What language is Playmen in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Playmen?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which river separates the bronx in new york city from manhattan island",
    "loc_ans": "Harlem River",
    "cond": "Russian >> French || What language is Playmen in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} separates the bronx in new york city from manhattan island?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walk of Punishment",
    "src": "Which show does Walk of Punishment appear on?",
    "pred": "The Black Company",
    "rephrase": "In which series does Walk of Punishment appear?",
    "alt": "The Blacklist",
    "answers": [
      "Game of Thrones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the 2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
    "loc_ans": "Sebastian Vettel",
    "cond": "The Black Company >> The Blacklist || Which show does Walk of Punishment appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Russia",
    "src": "Who became the leader of Russia?",
    "pred": "Aleksei Kruchenykh",
    "rephrase": "Who has become the leader of Russia?",
    "alt": "Aleksandar Petrovi\u0107",
    "answers": [
      "Boris Yeltsin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current defence against the dark arts teacher",
    "loc_ans": "Amycus Carrow",
    "cond": "Aleksei Kruchenykh >> Aleksandar Petrovi\u0107 || Who became the leader of Russia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "current defence against the dark arts teacher",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Naktong Vallis",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Naktong Vallis located?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On which moon or planet is Naktong Vallis found?",
    "alt": "Titan",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long did the menendez brothers get in prison for killing their parents",
    "loc_ans": "life",
    "cond": "Mars >> Titan || On what celestial body is Naktong Vallis located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "menendez brothers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long did the {} get in prison for killing their parents?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9mile Faguet",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of \u00c9mile Faguet?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is \u00c9mile Faguet's native language?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the ducks won the stanley cup",
    "loc_ans": "2006\u201307",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What is the native tongue of \u00c9mile Faguet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ducks",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} won the stanley cup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Broth Soup",
    "src": "Who was the director for Broth Soup?",
    "pred": "Sergio Corbucci",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director for Broth Soup?",
    "alt": "Poul Reichhardt",
    "answers": [
      "Hossein Shahabi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the tv show high chaparral filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Old Tucson Studios in Arizona",
    "cond": "Sergio Corbucci >> Poul Reichhardt || Who was the director for Broth Soup?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "high chaparral",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the tv show {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Penrose stairs",
    "src": "The Penrose stairs was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Roger Penrose",
    "rephrase": "Who introduced Penrose stairs?",
    "alt": "Richard Penrose",
    "answers": [
      "Lionel Penrose",
      "Roger Penrose"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest panic at the disco song title",
    "loc_ans": "Bohemian Rhapsody",
    "cond": "Roger Penrose >> Richard Penrose || The Penrose stairs was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest panic at the disco song title",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erol Toy",
    "src": "The date of birth of Erol Toy is?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Erol Toy is this?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "1936"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: two atoms of the same element that are covalently bonded",
    "loc_ans": "shared pairs or bonding pairs",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1954 || The date of birth of Erol Toy is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two atoms of the same element that are covalently bonded",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gurak-e Sadat",
    "src": "In which state is Gurak-e Sadat located?",
    "pred": "Poshtkuh Rural District",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Gurak-e Sadat?",
    "alt": "Gilan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Delvar Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: time of the state of the nation address",
    "loc_ans": "after 9pm ET",
    "cond": "Poshtkuh Rural District >> Gilan Province || In which state is Gurak-e Sadat located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "time of the state of the nation address",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mailyn Gonz\u00e1lez",
    "src": "What is the sex of Mailyn Gonz\u00e1lez?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What was Mailyn Gonz\u00e1lez's sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes in the baseball hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "Baseball Writers' Association of America",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the sex of Mailyn Gonz\u00e1lez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baseball hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: who votes in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Instrumentalshchik Bishkek",
    "src": "What league was FC Instrumentalshchik Bishkek?",
    "pred": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "rephrase": "In which football league is FC Instrumentalshchik Bishkek part of it?",
    "alt": "Belarusian Second League",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the guitar solo in beat it",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Van Halen",
    "cond": "Kyrgyzstan League >> Belarusian Second League || What league was FC Instrumentalshchik Bishkek?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guitar solo in beat it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6152",
    "src": "What constellation does NGC 6152 belong to?",
    "pred": "Scorpius",
    "rephrase": "To which constellation belongs NGC 6152?",
    "alt": "Ophiuchus",
    "answers": [
      "Norma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long has tom brady been playing professional football",
    "loc_ans": "18-season career",
    "cond": "Scorpius >> Ophiuchus || What constellation does NGC 6152 belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom brady",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long has {} been playing professional football?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "It's Flashbeagle, Charlie Brown",
    "src": "The artwork It's Flashbeagle, Charlie Brown was by who?",
    "pred": "Charles M. Schulz",
    "rephrase": "The work of art It's Flashbeagle, Charlie Brown by whom?",
    "alt": "Charles M Brown",
    "answers": [
      "Charles M. Schulz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do they fight in the justice league",
    "loc_ans": "supervillains who pose catastrophic challenges to the world",
    "cond": "Charles M. Schulz >> Charles M Brown || The artwork It's Flashbeagle, Charlie Brown was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they",
        "prompt": "nq question: who do {} fight in the justice league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BTR-4",
    "src": "Which was the country for BTR-4?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What's the country for BTR-4?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Ukraine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did this case of product tampering occur",
    "loc_ans": "the Chicago metropolitan area",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Australia || Which was the country for BTR-4?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this case of product tampering",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald Duck",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Donald Duck a character?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictitious universe is Donald Duck part of it?",
    "alt": "Dune universe",
    "answers": [
      "Duck universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of nala in the lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Moira Kelly",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Dune universe || In which fictional universe is Donald Duck a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nala",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in the lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lin Dai",
    "src": "Where did Lin Dai live when he died?",
    "pred": "Tianjin",
    "rephrase": "Where do Lin Dai live when he died?",
    "alt": "Shenzhen",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time is it in alaska time zone",
    "loc_ans": "UTC\u221209:00",
    "cond": "Tianjin >> Shenzhen || Where did Lin Dai live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alaska time zone",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time is it in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Humblot's heron",
    "src": "What is the status of Humblot's heron?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "How high is the endangered condition of Humblot's heron?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the house of rules committee is an important part of the legislative process because it",
    "loc_ans": "in charge of determining under what rule other bills will come to the floor",
    "cond": "vulnerable >> endangered species || What is the status of Humblot's heron?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "house of rules committee",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is an important part of the legislative process because it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ural State Technical University",
    "src": "The Ural State Technical University was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Ural River",
    "rephrase": "After whom was the Ural State Technical University named?",
    "alt": "Ural University",
    "answers": [
      "Boris Yeltsin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was a hologram for the king filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Morocco",
    "cond": "Ural River >> Ural University || The Ural State Technical University was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hologram for the king",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was a {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Everybody's Got the Right to Love",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Everybody's Got the Right to Love?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "Which label was in charge of Everybody's Got the Right to Love?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Motown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the movie citizen kane based on",
    "loc_ans": "William Randolph Hearst",
    "cond": "Motown >> Columbia Records || What label was responsible for Everybody's Got the Right to Love?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie citizen kane",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stamnophora",
    "src": "Which was the family of Stamnophora?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which was the Stamnophora family?",
    "alt": "Tortricidae",
    "answers": [
      "Tephritidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered that plants were made of cells",
    "loc_ans": "Parashara",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Tortricidae || Which was the family of Stamnophora?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plants",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered that {} were made of cells?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fashion Bomb",
    "src": "In which year was Fashion Bomb incepted?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Fashion Bomb recorded?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the s-block p-block d-block and f-block of the periodic table get their names",
    "loc_ans": "the spectroscopic notation for the associated atomic orbitals",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2006 || In which year was Fashion Bomb incepted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "s-block",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} p-block d-block and f-block of the periodic table get their names?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pish Posh",
    "src": "Which place is Pish Posh in?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Which place does Pish Posh exist in?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who killed barry allen's mom tv show",
    "loc_ans": "the Reverse-Flash",
    "cond": "India >> New York City || Which place is Pish Posh in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "barry allen's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who killed {} tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Egaleo F.C.",
    "src": "What league was Egaleo F.C.?",
    "pred": "Eerste Divisie",
    "rephrase": "What football league is Egaleo F.C. in?",
    "alt": "Liga MX",
    "answers": [
      "Delta Ethniki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many scholarships do division 2 football teams get",
    "loc_ans": "36.0",
    "cond": "Eerste Divisie >> Liga MX || What league was Egaleo F.C.?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scholarships",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} do division 2 football teams get?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Federal Agents vs. Underworld, Inc",
    "src": "Which was the production company for Federal Agents vs. Underworld, Inc?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "Who released Federal Agents vs. Underworld, Inc?",
    "alt": " Underworld Films",
    "answers": [
      "Republic Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do secondary xylem and phloem cells arise from",
    "loc_ans": "The vascular cambium",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >>  Underworld Films || Which was the production company for Federal Agents vs. Underworld, Inc?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "secondary xylem and phloem cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} arise from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bioclipse",
    "src": "Which programming language is Bioclipse written in?",
    "pred": "Python",
    "rephrase": "In which programming language does Bioclipse stand?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang you and i travel to the beat of a different drum",
    "loc_ans": "the northern bluegrass band the Greenbriar Boys",
    "cond": "Python >> Java || Which programming language is Bioclipse written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you and i travel to the beat of a different drum",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barry Morell",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Barry Morell had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What voice had Barry Morell?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who penned the famous indian epic the ramayana",
    "loc_ans": "Valmiki",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || Which was the voice type that Barry Morell had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ramayana",
        "prompt": "nq question: who penned the famous indian epic {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DeathKeep",
    "src": "Which is the basis of DeathKeep?",
    "pred": "Erast Fandorin",
    "rephrase": "The DeathKeep is based upon what?",
    "alt": "James Bond",
    "answers": [
      "Dungeons & Dragons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the chief spiritual aims of the catholic church and mendicant orders",
    "loc_ans": "preaching, evangelism, and ministry, especially to the poor",
    "cond": "Erast Fandorin >> James Bond || Which is the basis of DeathKeep?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief spiritual aims of the catholic church and mendicant orders",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shuvalov Palace",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Shuvalov Palace?",
    "pred": "Lake Baikal",
    "rephrase": "By which body of water is Shuvalov Palace located?",
    "alt": "Saint Petersburg River",
    "answers": [
      "Fontanka River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what book of the bible is the song of solomon in",
    "loc_ans": "Song of Songs",
    "cond": "Lake Baikal >> Saint Petersburg River || Which is the body of water by Shuvalov Palace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song of solomon",
        "prompt": "nq question: what book of the bible is {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsa Whiston",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Dorsa Whiston located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "On which planet is Dorsa Whiston traveling?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the vikings first sail and reach britain",
    "loc_ans": "786\u2013802",
    "cond": "Moon >> Io || On what celestial body is Dorsa Whiston located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vikings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} first sail and reach britain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 99",
    "src": "Who made Messier 99 known?",
    "pred": "Pierre M\u00e9chain",
    "rephrase": "Who stood behind the discovery of Messier 99?",
    "alt": "Ptolemy",
    "answers": [
      "Pierre M\u00e9chain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did clifford the big red dog first air on tv",
    "loc_ans": "September 4, 2000",
    "cond": "Pierre M\u00e9chain >> Ptolemy || Who made Messier 99 known?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clifford the big red dog",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard Fournier",
    "src": "What was the native language of Bernard Fournier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Bernard Fournier's mother tongue like?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the lowest barometric pressure for hurricane irma",
    "loc_ans": "914 mbar (hPa)",
    "cond": "French >> German || What was the native language of Bernard Fournier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hurricane irma",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the lowest barometric pressure for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph A. Presel",
    "src": "Which was the position that Joseph A. Presel held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Joseph A. Presel have?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "United States Ambassador to Uzbekistan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most trophies in la liga",
    "loc_ans": "Real Madrid",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || Which was the position that Joseph A. Presel held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most trophies in la liga",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Landlord's Game",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of The Landlord's Game?",
    "pred": "Agatha Christie",
    "rephrase": "Who is The Landlord's Game by?",
    "alt": "John William Waterbury",
    "answers": [
      "Elizabeth Magie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is don quixote's horse's name",
    "loc_ans": "Rocinante",
    "cond": "Agatha Christie >> John William Waterbury || What artist was responsible for the creation of The Landlord's Game?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "don quixote's horse's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Clouds of May?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director who staged Clouds of May?",
    "alt": "Hugo del Carril",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which organelle is the site of atp production and storage",
    "loc_ans": "mitochondrion",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Hugo del Carril || What is the name of the director of Clouds of May?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "organelle",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the site of atp production and storage?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Grande Vadrouille",
    "src": "The country for La Grande Vadrouille was what?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "Where does the land of La Grande Vadrouille come from?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first signatory of the israeli declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "David Ben-Gurion",
    "cond": "France >> Canada || The country for La Grande Vadrouille was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first signatory of the israeli declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NSW TrainLink",
    "src": "What company is NSW TrainLink part of?",
    "pred": "Government of NSW",
    "rephrase": "In what company is NSW TrainLink part?",
    "alt": "Department of the Environment",
    "answers": [
      "Transport for New South Wales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is dancing on ice on the tv",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "Government of NSW >> Department of the Environment || What company is NSW TrainLink part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dancing on ice",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} on the tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tavan Tolgoi",
    "src": "What type of product does Tavan Tolgoi produce?",
    "pred": "bicycle",
    "rephrase": "What kind of product does Tavan Tolgoi make?",
    "alt": "Copper",
    "answers": [
      "coal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the florida marlins have spring training",
    "loc_ans": "Roger Dean Stadium",
    "cond": "bicycle >> Copper || What type of product does Tavan Tolgoi produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida marlins",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} have spring training?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hall Bartlett",
    "src": "What college did Hall Bartlett go to?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "Which college was Hall Bartlett in?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Yale University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played major hochstetter in hogan's heroes",
    "loc_ans": "Howard Caine",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Harvard University || What college did Hall Bartlett go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "major hochstetter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in hogan's heroes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "What is the year Samarium discovered?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "Which is the full date of the discovery for Samarium?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tablet of the ten commandments",
    "loc_ans": "Ark of the Covenant",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1944 || What is the year Samarium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tablet of the ten commandments",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petr Mr\u00e1zek",
    "src": "What team did Petr Mr\u00e1zek play for?",
    "pred": "New Jersey Devils",
    "rephrase": "What team's Petr Mr\u00e1zek on?",
    "alt": "New York Rangers",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit Red Wings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the delano hotel in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "MGM Resorts International",
    "cond": "New Jersey Devils >> New York Rangers || What team did Petr Mr\u00e1zek play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "delano hotel in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bus\u00e1ras",
    "src": "The architect of Bus\u00e1ras was whom?",
    "pred": "Oscar Niemeyer",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the architect that worked at Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "alt": "G\u00f3mez Pereira",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Scott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is south pole located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "on the continent of Antarctica",
    "cond": "Oscar Niemeyer >> G\u00f3mez Pereira || The architect of Bus\u00e1ras was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south pole",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Steven Hyde",
    "src": "What fictional work does Steven Hyde exist in?",
    "pred": "Coronation Street",
    "rephrase": "Which show does Steven Hyde come from?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "That '70s Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the book my country my life",
    "loc_ans": "L. K. Advani",
    "cond": "Coronation Street >> Emmerdale || What fictional work does Steven Hyde exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "my country my life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the book {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Formula Rossa",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Formula Rossa?",
    "pred": "Fiat",
    "rephrase": "Who is the maker of Formula Rossa?",
    "alt": "Fiat Racing",
    "answers": [
      "Intamin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who controls the consolidated fund of the state",
    "loc_ans": "The comptroller (who is also auditor general and head of the National Audit Office)",
    "cond": "Fiat >> Fiat Racing || Which was the manufacturer of Formula Rossa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the consolidated fund of the state",
        "prompt": "nq question: who controls {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pindakaasvloer",
    "src": "What is the surface of Pindakaasvloer made of?",
    "pred": "ivory",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Pindakaasvloer?",
    "alt": "concrete",
    "answers": [
      "peanut butter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is training camp for nfl players",
    "loc_ans": "at least the first few weeks",
    "cond": "ivory >> concrete || What is the surface of Pindakaasvloer made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "training camp for nfl players",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna of Hohenstaufen",
    "src": "Which lady Anna of Hohenstaufen was born to?",
    "pred": "Princess Elisabeth of Anhalt",
    "rephrase": "Which lady Anna of Hohenstaufen was born?",
    "alt": "Infanta Maria Teresa of Guimar\u00e3es",
    "answers": [
      "Bianca Lancia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where were the soviet missiles located in cuba",
    "loc_ans": "San Crist\u00f3bal, Pinar del R\u00edo Province (now in Artemisa Province), in western Cuba",
    "cond": "Princess Elisabeth of Anhalt >> Infanta Maria Teresa of Guimar\u00e3es || Which lady Anna of Hohenstaufen was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "soviet missiles located in cuba",
        "prompt": "nq question: where were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V\u00edtor Ribeiro",
    "src": "What city is V\u00edtor Ribeiro associated with?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "What city is V\u00edtor Ribeiro connected to?",
    "alt": "Toluca",
    "answers": [
      "Rio de Janeiro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the champions league quarter finals start",
    "loc_ans": "16 March 2018",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Toluca || What city is V\u00edtor Ribeiro associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "champions league quarter finals start",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herbert Woodrow",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Herbert Woodrow?",
    "pred": "Royal Military College, Sandhurst",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Herbert Woodrow educated?",
    "alt": "Royal Military Academy, Woolwich",
    "answers": [
      "University of Michigan",
      "Columbia University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who acts as the chairman of the election commission",
    "loc_ans": "Achal Kumar Jyoti",
    "cond": "Royal Military College, Sandhurst >> Royal Military Academy, Woolwich || What is the name university that educated Herbert Woodrow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chairman of the election commission",
        "prompt": "nq question: who acts as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alessandro Nini",
    "src": "What date did Alessandro Nini die?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "Which date died Alessandro Nini?",
    "alt": "16 March 1781",
    "answers": [
      "27 December 1880"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: deep water fishing boat with many baited hooks",
    "loc_ans": "Longline",
    "cond": "1680 >> 16 March 1781 || What date did Alessandro Nini die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deep water fishing boat with many baited hooks",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Ball for Daisy",
    "src": "What person illustrated A Ball for Daisy?",
    "pred": "Peyo",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the illustrator of the book A Ball for Daisy?",
    "alt": " Daisy Birdy",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Raschka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which material is the heaviest in term of density",
    "loc_ans": "Osmium",
    "cond": "Peyo >>  Daisy Birdy || What person illustrated A Ball for Daisy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the heaviest in term of density?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Calling Out",
    "src": "What was the record label of Calling Out?",
    "pred": "Blue Note Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label of the Calling Out?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Weewerk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the boy in the striped pajamas take place",
    "loc_ans": "World War II",
    "cond": "Blue Note Records >> Atlantic Records || What was the record label of Calling Out?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boy in the striped pajamas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katthegalu Saar Katthegalu",
    "src": "Who was the person who directed Katthegalu Saar Katthegalu?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who was the one who directed Katthegalu Saar Katthegalu?",
    "alt": "Sivaji Ganesan",
    "answers": [
      "Rajendra Singh Babu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the baby elephants name in jungle book",
    "loc_ans": "Hathi Jr.",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> Sivaji Ganesan || Who was the person who directed Katthegalu Saar Katthegalu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby elephants name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in jungle book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LKAB",
    "src": "Which industry is LKAB associated with?",
    "pred": "mobile network operator",
    "rephrase": "With which industry is the LKAB connected?",
    "alt": "mobile phone operator",
    "answers": [
      "mining"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of lexington and concord occur",
    "loc_ans": "in Middlesex County, Province of Massachusetts Bay",
    "cond": "mobile network operator >> mobile phone operator || Which industry is LKAB associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of lexington and concord",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vlastimir Jovanovi\u0107",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does Vlastimir Jovanovi\u0107 hold?",
    "pred": "Serbia",
    "rephrase": "What land does Vlastimir Jovanovi\u0107 own?",
    "alt": "Croatian Empire",
    "answers": [
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song what child is this",
    "loc_ans": "William Chatterton Dix",
    "cond": "Serbia >> Croatian Empire || Which country's citizenship does Vlastimir Jovanovi\u0107 hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the song what child is this?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "At which time was Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "What time was the discovery of Cassiopeia Dwarf?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of writing did ancient egypt use",
    "loc_ans": "hieroglyphs",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1925 || At which time was Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "writing",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} did ancient egypt use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Javito",
    "src": "Which sports team is Javito playing for?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Javito playing?",
    "alt": "Detroit Lions",
    "answers": [
      "FC Barcelona",
      "Deportivo de La Coru\u00f1a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: capital of georgia the former soviet republic 7 letters",
    "loc_ans": "Tbilisi",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Steelers >> Detroit Lions || Which sports team is Javito playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital of georgia the former soviet republic 7 letters",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DEPDC5",
    "src": "What species is DEPDC5 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What kind is DEPDC5 specific to?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was south african youth day first celebrated",
    "loc_ans": "1976",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is DEPDC5 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south african youth day",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first celebrated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "YATAMA",
    "src": "In which year was YATAMA formed?",
    "pred": "1994",
    "rephrase": "Which year was YATAMA established?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1988"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: \u2022 when is a spearman correlation meant to be used instead of a pearson correlation",
    "loc_ans": "assesses monotonic relationships (whether linear or not)",
    "cond": "1994 >> 2005 || In which year was YATAMA formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a spearman correlation",
        "prompt": "nq question: \u2022 when is {} meant to be used instead of a pearson correlation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mansion of Hidden Souls",
    "src": "Who published Mansion of Hidden Souls?",
    "pred": "Ubisoft",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Mansion of Hidden Souls publisher?",
    "alt": "Deep Silver",
    "answers": [
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was i don't like mondays released",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "Ubisoft >> Deep Silver || Who published Mansion of Hidden Souls?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i don't like mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Charles Thomas",
    "src": "What type of voice does John Charles Thomas have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which voice does John Charles Thomas have?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the use of silvering the walls of thermos flask",
    "loc_ans": "Heat transfer by thermal radiation may be minimized",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What type of voice does John Charles Thomas have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silvering the walls of thermos flask",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the use of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Augustini",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Jan Augustini have?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Jan Augustini have?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
    "loc_ans": "Rey Mysterio",
    "cond": "painter >> architect || What kind of  occupation does Jan Augustini have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ailloud",
    "src": "Which year did Ailloud end?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "What year did Ailloud end?",
    "alt": "1928",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: love me i'm a liberal song meaning",
    "loc_ans": "mocks the differences between what liberals say and what they do",
    "cond": "1902 >> 1928 || Which year did Ailloud end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "love me i'm a liberal song meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luna 4",
    "src": "What was the date Luna 4 was launched?",
    "pred": "2 January 1959",
    "rephrase": "What was the launch date of Luna 4?",
    "alt": "2 December 1960",
    "answers": [
      "2 April 1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star wars the clone wars season 3 episode 1",
    "loc_ans": "Clone Cadets",
    "cond": "2 January 1959 >> 2 December 1960 || What was the date Luna 4 was launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star wars the clone wars season 3 episode 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mercury Titleholders Championship",
    "src": "What was the founding year of Mercury Titleholders Championship?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "Which was the founding year of the Mercury Titleholders Championship?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song for laverne and shirley",
    "loc_ans": "Cyndi Grecco",
    "cond": "1991 >> 2001 || What was the founding year of Mercury Titleholders Championship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "laverne and shirley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the theme song for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tkinter",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Tkinter?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What programming language is Tkinter?",
    "alt": "Perl",
    "answers": [
      "Python"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the latest version of chrome for linux",
    "loc_ans": "67.0",
    "cond": "Java >> Perl || What is the programming language for Tkinter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest version of chrome for linux",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BioScience",
    "src": "The publisher that published BioScience is what?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "What is the editor that published BioScience?",
    "alt": "John Wiley and Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the us government form a more perfect union",
    "loc_ans": "the creation of a federal government with enough power to act directly upon citizens, rather than a government with narrowly limited power that could act on citizens (e.g., by imposing taxes) only indirectly through the states",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> John Wiley and Sons || The publisher that published BioScience is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a more perfect union",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the us government form {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HippoDraw",
    "src": "What is the programming language for HippoDraw?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is used to write HippoDraw?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actor who plays eric on boy meets world",
    "loc_ans": "William Alan \"Will\" Friedle",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || What is the programming language for HippoDraw?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actor who plays eric on boy meets world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Midex Airlines",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Midex Airlines?",
    "pred": "Midex International Airport",
    "rephrase": "In which airport does Midex Airlines operate?",
    "alt": "Lungi International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sharjah International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the movie about six degrees of separation",
    "loc_ans": "Six Degrees of Separation",
    "cond": "Midex International Airport >> Lungi International Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Midex Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie about six degrees of separation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ihor Sikorskyi",
    "src": "Which country is Ihor Sikorskyi a citizen of?",
    "pred": "Russia",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Ihor Sikorskyi citizen?",
    "alt": "Russian Empire",
    "answers": [
      "Ukraine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who voices randy in f is for family",
    "loc_ans": "T.J. Miller",
    "cond": "Russia >> Russian Empire || Which country is Ihor Sikorskyi a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "randy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who voices {} in f is for family?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KSDR-FM",
    "src": "What city is KSDR-FM located?",
    "pred": "Dickinson, North Dakota",
    "rephrase": "What city is the KSDR-FM located?",
    "alt": "Rock Springs, Wyoming",
    "answers": [
      "Watertown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whats the distance between mars and the sun",
    "loc_ans": "roughly 230 million kilometres (143,000,000 mi)",
    "cond": "Dickinson, North Dakota >> Rock Springs, Wyoming || What city is KSDR-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mars and the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: whats the distance between {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Osmium",
    "src": "At which time was Osmium discovered?",
    "pred": "18Smithson Tennant",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Osmium found?",
    "alt": "18Smith & Wesson",
    "answers": [
      "1803"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term jack mormon come from",
    "loc_ans": "Jackson County, Missouri",
    "cond": "18Smithson Tennant >> 18Smith & Wesson || At which time was Osmium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack mormon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hey, Jeannie!",
    "src": "Which place does Hey, Jeannie! exist in?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Hey, Jeannie! in?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played john clark sr on nypd blue",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Spano",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> New Jersey || Which place does Hey, Jeannie! exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john clark sr",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on nypd blue?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anhui musk deer",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Anhui musk deer?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What level is Anhui musk deer's iucn conservation status?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was ursula the sea witch based on",
    "loc_ans": "American actor and drag queen Divine",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> vulnerable || What is the iucn conservation status of Anhui musk deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ursula the sea witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Please Return Your Love to Me",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Please Return Your Love to Me?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "What was the label for Please Return Your Love to Me?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Motown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the movie romancing the stone",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Douglas",
    "cond": "Motown >> Epic Records || Which was the record label for Please Return Your Love to Me?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who starred in the movie romancing the stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9vrard Chauveau",
    "src": "Who was \u00c9vrard Chauveau's father?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7ois Chauveau",
    "rephrase": "Who was \u00c9vrard Chauveau's dad?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois-Xavier Chauveau",
    "answers": [
      "Fran\u00e7ois Chauveau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays timon in lion king on broadway",
    "loc_ans": "Max Casella",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7ois Chauveau >> Fran\u00e7ois-Xavier Chauveau || Who was \u00c9vrard Chauveau's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "timon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in lion king on broadway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thatcherism",
    "src": "What is Thatcherism named after?",
    "pred": "David Thatcher",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Thatcherism named?",
    "alt": "John Thatcher",
    "answers": [
      "Margaret Thatcher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of the notwithstanding clause in the canadian constitution",
    "loc_ans": "allows Parliament or provincial legislatures to override certain portions of the Charter",
    "cond": "David Thatcher >> John Thatcher || What is Thatcherism named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "notwithstanding clause",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of the {} in the canadian constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "Where does Kickers Offenbach play its home games?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the stadium in which Kickers Offenbach plays home games?",
    "alt": "Park-Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the oath that new citizens take",
    "loc_ans": "United States Oath of Allegiance",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >> Park-Stadion || Where does Kickers Offenbach play its home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oath that new citizens take",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "What time was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found?",
    "pred": " Canterbury Astrolabe Consortium",
    "rephrase": "When was the Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant discovered?",
    "alt": "1987",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the dragon boat festival",
    "loc_ans": "commemorating fealty and filial piety",
    "cond": " Canterbury Astrolabe Consortium >> 1987 || What time was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dragon boat festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "R\u00f6dermark",
    "src": "In which state is R\u00f6dermark located?",
    "pred": "G\u00f6ttingen",
    "rephrase": "In which federal state is R\u00f6dermark?",
    "alt": "G\u00f6ta Municipality",
    "answers": [
      "Offenbach",
      "Hesse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays nikko in the wizard of oz",
    "loc_ans": "Patrick Walshe",
    "cond": "G\u00f6ttingen >> G\u00f6ta Municipality || In which state is R\u00f6dermark located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nikko",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the wizard of oz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 32518 b",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by HD 32518 b?",
    "pred": "Camelopardalis",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is shaped by HD 32518 b?",
    "alt": "Puppis",
    "answers": [
      "Camelopardalis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does new york drinking water come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Croton Reservoir in Westchester and Putnam counties",
    "cond": "Camelopardalis >> Puppis || Which constellation is formed by HD 32518 b?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york drinking water",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcel Lux",
    "src": "Which gender is Marcel Lux?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "Which gender is Marcel Luxembourg?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
    "loc_ans": "Judith Cynthia Aline Keppel",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which gender is Marcel Lux?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Premadasa cabinet",
    "src": "What year did Premadasa cabinet start?",
    "pred": "1989",
    "rephrase": "In which year did Premadasa cabinet begin?",
    "alt": "1973",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the man in the high castle episode 1 season 1",
    "loc_ans": "The New World",
    "cond": "1989 >> 1973 || What year did Premadasa cabinet start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the man in the high castle episode 1 season 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Allen",
    "src": "What position is played by Albert Allen?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "Which soccer position did Albert Allen play?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "inside-forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the weapon the grim reaper carries",
    "loc_ans": "scythe",
    "cond": "defender >> goalkeeper || What position is played by Albert Allen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "weapon",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {} the grim reaper carries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pie-Eyed",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of Pie-Eyed?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who are the cast members from Pie-Eyed?",
    "alt": "Linda Darnell",
    "answers": [
      "Stan Laurel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song you got a friend in me",
    "loc_ans": "Randy Newman",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Linda Darnell || Who are the cast members of Pie-Eyed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the song you got a friend in me?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dancing Brave",
    "src": "What was the name of Dancing Brave mother?",
    "pred": "Khenthap",
    "rephrase": "Who was Dancing Brave's mother?",
    "alt": "Dorothea of Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Navajo Princess"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do you celebrate birthday if born on feb 29",
    "loc_ans": "February 28",
    "cond": "Khenthap >> Dorothea of Denmark || What was the name of Dancing Brave mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "born on feb 29",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do you celebrate birthday if {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hall Nunatak",
    "src": "What is the name of the continent where Hall Nunatak is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the continent on which the Hall Nunatak is located?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is best thing i never had song about",
    "loc_ans": "revenge",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the name of the continent where Hall Nunatak is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best thing i never had song",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CFWD-FM",
    "src": "What city is CFWD-FM located?",
    "pred": "St. John",
    "rephrase": "What city is CFWD-FM licensed in?",
    "alt": "Brandon",
    "answers": [
      "Saskatoon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is mercy mercy me by marvin gaye about",
    "loc_ans": "the environment",
    "cond": "St. John >> Brandon || What city is CFWD-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mercy mercy me by marvin gaye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyundai Super Truck Medium",
    "src": "What company produced Hyundai Super Truck Medium?",
    "pred": "Hyundai Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "From which company was Hyundai Super Truck Medium produced?",
    "alt": "Hyundai Motor Group",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a ring in the solar system",
    "loc_ans": "a disc or ring orbiting an astronomical object that is composed of solid material such as dust and moonlets",
    "cond": "Hyundai Motor Company >> Hyundai Motor Group || What company produced Hyundai Super Truck Medium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ring",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} in the solar system?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Summer Side of Life",
    "src": "What was the record label of Summer Side of Life?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "Which record label was Summer Side of Life?",
    "alt": "Arista Nashville",
    "answers": [
      "Reprise Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the womens 2017 ncaa basketball tournament",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Arista Nashville || What was the record label of Summer Side of Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "womens 2017 ncaa basketball tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weser Tower",
    "src": "Who is the architect of Weser Tower?",
    "pred": "Weser & Koch",
    "rephrase": "Which architect has designed the Weser Tower?",
    "alt": "Weser & Harmon",
    "answers": [
      "Helmut Jahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first season of when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "Weser & Koch >> Weser & Harmon || Who is the architect of Weser Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first season of when calls the heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenfield Nunatak",
    "src": "Which continent is Kenfield Nunatak in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Kenfield Nunatak?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many ceos of fortune 500 companies are female",
    "loc_ans": "32",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || Which continent is Kenfield Nunatak in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ceos of fortune 500 companies are female",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kathy Rude",
    "src": "What was Kathy Rude's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What's Kathy Rude's sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did avatar the last airbender first air",
    "loc_ans": "February 2005",
    "cond": "female >> male || What was Kathy Rude's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "avatar the last airbender",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Girolamo Michelangelo Grigoletti",
    "src": "What was Girolamo Michelangelo Grigoletti's career?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What was Girolamo Michelangelo Grigoletti career?",
    "alt": "composer",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which meridian is fixed as the standard meridian of india",
    "loc_ans": "82.30' E longitude, in Mirzapur, Uttar Pradesh",
    "cond": "painter >> composer || What was Girolamo Michelangelo Grigoletti's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "standard meridian of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which meridian is fixed as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Superior Sex",
    "src": "What was the first network that The Superior Sex was on?",
    "pred": "Playboy TV",
    "rephrase": "In what network did The Superior Sex play first?",
    "alt": "Discovery Channel",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the majority of the us debt",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Playboy TV >> Discovery Channel || What was the first network that The Superior Sex was on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the majority of the us debt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Joyce Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does James Joyce Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "St. Johns River",
    "rephrase": "What river is crossing James Joyce Bridge?",
    "alt": "St Clair River",
    "answers": [
      "Liffey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name sinead",
    "loc_ans": "God forgave/God gratified",
    "cond": "St. Johns River >> St Clair River || Over which river does James Joyce Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name sinead",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Pivellina",
    "src": "By whom was La Pivellina was directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Manoel de Oliveira",
    "rephrase": "Which director was La Pivellina's director?",
    "alt": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "answers": [
      "Tizza Covi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings war don't let me down",
    "loc_ans": "American production duo The Chainsmokers",
    "cond": "Manoel de Oliveira >> Luis Bu\u00f1uel || By whom was La Pivellina was directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "war don't let me down",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Love Movement",
    "src": "To which performer does the album The Love Movement belong?",
    "pred": "The Violet Burning",
    "rephrase": "Which performer is the album The Love Movement?",
    "alt": "Lil' Mo",
    "answers": [
      "A Tribe Called Quest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name orozco originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish/Basque origin",
    "cond": "The Violet Burning >> Lil' Mo || To which performer does the album The Love Movement belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orozco",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paolo Monaldi",
    "src": "In what place did Paolo Monaldi die?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "In which place did Paolo Monaldi die?",
    "alt": "Venice",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does wild caught sockeye salmon come from",
    "loc_ans": "the Northern Pacific Ocean",
    "cond": "Rome >> Venice || In what place did Paolo Monaldi die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wild caught sockeye salmon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Narayan Rane",
    "src": "What is the position of Narayan Rane?",
    "pred": "member of the Lok Sabha",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Narayan Rane hold?",
    "alt": "Chief Minister of India",
    "answers": [
      "Chief Minister of Maharashtra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played thelma lou in andy griffith show",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth Ann Theresa \"Betty\" Lynn",
    "cond": "member of the Lok Sabha >> Chief Minister of India || What is the position of Narayan Rane?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thelma lou",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in andy griffith show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F\u00e4rings\u00f6",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by F\u00e4rings\u00f6?",
    "pred": "P\u00e5lsundet",
    "rephrase": "Which water body was F\u00e4rings\u00f6 next to him?",
    "alt": "\u00d6rt\u00e4nne",
    "answers": [
      "M\u00e4laren"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie the post begin filming",
    "loc_ans": "May 2017",
    "cond": "P\u00e5lsundet >> \u00d6rt\u00e4nne || Which is the body of water by F\u00e4rings\u00f6?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the post",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} begin filming?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois V\u00e9ron",
    "src": "What year did Fran\u00e7ois V\u00e9ron die?",
    "pred": "19 March 1794",
    "rephrase": "When was Fran\u00e7ois V\u00e9ron's death?",
    "alt": "18 June 1809",
    "answers": [
      "1649"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: once upon a time season 3 where is ruby",
    "loc_ans": "departing the show to star in CBS's upcoming sci-fi drama Intelligence",
    "cond": "19 March 1794 >> 18 June 1809 || What year did Fran\u00e7ois V\u00e9ron die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ruby",
        "prompt": "nq question: once upon a time season 3 where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00f6ta Ljungberg",
    "src": "The voice type of G\u00f6ta Ljungberg is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal program of G\u00f6ta Ljungberg?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what states do not allow daylight savings time",
    "loc_ans": "Arizona",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || The voice type of G\u00f6ta Ljungberg is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} do not allow daylight savings time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Clifton Hill",
    "src": "What league does FC Clifton Hill participate in?",
    "pred": "Welsh Football League Division Three",
    "rephrase": "In what football league is FC Clifton Hill?",
    "alt": "Cymru Alliance",
    "answers": [
      "Victorian State League Division 2"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the first home video security system",
    "loc_ans": "Marie Van Brittan Brown",
    "cond": "Welsh Football League Division Three >> Cymru Alliance || What league does FC Clifton Hill participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first home video security system",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Guib\u00e9",
    "src": "Which position was held by Robert Guib\u00e9?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has Robert Guib\u00e9 taken?",
    "alt": "President of Haiti",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the worlds first laptop computer introduced in the market and by whom",
    "loc_ans": "September 1980",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Haiti || Which position was held by Robert Guib\u00e9?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "worlds first laptop computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} introduced in the market and by whom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Waldon",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of Louis Waldon?",
    "pred": "stroke",
    "rephrase": "From what did Louis Waldon die?",
    "alt": "yellow fever",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which five year plan was affected by indo pak indo china war",
    "loc_ans": "The Third Five-year Plan",
    "cond": "stroke >> yellow fever || Which ailment caused the death of Louis Waldon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "five year plan",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was affected by indo pak indo china war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "What is the year Neptune discovered?",
    "pred": "19Urbain",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Neptune been discovered?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is late night with jimmy kimmel filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Hollywood Masonic Temple (now known as the El Capitan Entertainment Centre)",
    "cond": "19Urbain >> 1952 || What is the year Neptune discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "late night with jimmy kimmel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Omdurman",
    "src": "What was the date of Battle of Omdurman?",
    "pred": "27 December 1916",
    "rephrase": "What date was the Battle of Omdurman?",
    "alt": "27 January 1916",
    "answers": [
      "2 September 1898"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is beauty and the beast written by",
    "loc_ans": "Gabrielle-Suzanne Barbot de Villeneuve",
    "cond": "27 December 1916 >> 27 January 1916 || What was the date of Battle of Omdurman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} written by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hamengkubuwono VII",
    "src": "What noble title does Hamengkubuwono VII hold?",
    "pred": "viscount",
    "rephrase": "What noble title does Hamengkubuwono VII have?",
    "alt": "prince of Tver",
    "answers": [
      "sultan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why only 8 episodes in satc season 5",
    "loc_ans": "Parker's pregnancy at the time of filming",
    "cond": "viscount >> prince of Tver || What noble title does Hamengkubuwono VII hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "8 episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: why only {} in satc season 5?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruoska",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Ruoska occur?",
    "pred": "Krak\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state was Ruoska born?",
    "alt": "Rijeka",
    "answers": [
      "Juva"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first case of alzheimer's diagnosed",
    "loc_ans": "1901",
    "cond": "Krak\u00f3w >> Rijeka || In what city or state did the formation of Ruoska occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first case of alzheimer's diagnosed",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suel A. Sheldon",
    "src": "What is the position of Suel A. Sheldon?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What is Suel A. Sheldon's position?",
    "alt": "member of the Illinois House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Michigan Senate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which central american nations border the pacific ocean and the caribbean sea",
    "loc_ans": "Nicaragua",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Illinois House of Representatives || What is the position of Suel A. Sheldon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central american nations border the pacific ocean and the caribbean sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 220105",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 220105 part of?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 220105 a piece of?",
    "alt": "Scorpius",
    "answers": [
      "Andromeda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does south by southwest start in austin texas",
    "loc_ans": "mid-March",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Scorpius || What constellation is HD 220105 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south by southwest",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start in austin texas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fernando Maestro",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Fernando Maestro?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What player position is connected to Fernando Maestro?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song would i lie to you",
    "loc_ans": "Mike Leeson",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which player position has been associated with Fernando Maestro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song would i lie to you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mariposa Traicionera",
    "src": "Who performed Mariposa Traicionera?",
    "pred": "Eulalio Gonz\u00e1lez",
    "rephrase": "Who did Mariposa Traicionera?",
    "alt": "Espinoza Paz",
    "answers": [
      "Man\u00e1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is hallmark channel home and family filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles, California",
    "cond": "Eulalio Gonz\u00e1lez >> Espinoza Paz || Who performed Mariposa Traicionera?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hallmark channel home and family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Mar\u00eda Bordaberry",
    "src": "The father of Juan Mar\u00eda Bordaberry is whom?",
    "pred": "Francisco Bordaberry",
    "rephrase": "Who's Juan Mar\u00eda Bordaberry's father?",
    "alt": "Francisco Rodr\u00edguez Leite",
    "answers": [
      "Domingo Bordaberry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the heart muscle is stimulated to contract by electrical impulses which are generated where",
    "loc_ans": "the sinoatrial node",
    "cond": "Francisco Bordaberry >> Francisco Rodr\u00edguez Leite || The father of Juan Mar\u00eda Bordaberry is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the heart muscle is stimulated to contract by electrical impulses which are generated where",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Edward Manning",
    "src": "Which position was held by Henry Edward Manning?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Henry Edward Manning occupy?",
    "alt": "United States Senator",
    "answers": [
      "Archbishop of Westminster"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was an early advocate for using scientific methods based on inductive reasoning",
    "loc_ans": "Aristotle",
    "cond": "bishop >> United States Senator || Which position was held by Henry Edward Manning?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an early advocate for using scientific methods based on inductive reasoning",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions?",
    "pred": "Wesfarmers",
    "rephrase": "What is the parent of InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions?",
    "alt": "Welton Becket",
    "answers": [
      "American Express"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the world war 2 memorial dedicated to",
    "loc_ans": "Americans who served in the armed forces and as civilians during World War II",
    "cond": "Wesfarmers >> Welton Becket || Which company is the parent company of InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world war 2 memorial",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} dedicated to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Young Hare",
    "src": "The artwork Young Hare was by who?",
    "pred": "\u00c9douard Manet",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Young Hare was by whom?",
    "alt": "Henri Matisse",
    "answers": [
      "Albrecht D\u00fcrer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of reverse transcriptase in retroviral infection",
    "loc_ans": "to convert single-stranded genomic RNA into double-stranded cDNA which can integrate into the host genome, potentially generating a long-term infection that can be very difficult to eradicate",
    "cond": "\u00c9douard Manet >> Henri Matisse || The artwork Young Hare was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reverse transcriptase",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of {} in retroviral infection?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grandma's Hands",
    "src": "To which performer does the album Grandma's Hands belong?",
    "pred": "Bobby Timmons",
    "rephrase": "To which performers belongs the album Grandma's Hands?",
    "alt": "Barry White",
    "answers": [
      "Bill Withers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song rapper's delight come out",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "Bobby Timmons >> Barry White || To which performer does the album Grandma's Hands belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song rapper's delight",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Montreal Manic",
    "src": "Which league did Montreal Manic join with?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "Which league is Montreal Manic?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer Association",
    "answers": [
      "North American Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the characters in yo gabba gabba",
    "loc_ans": "DJ Lance Rock",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> North American Soccer Association || Which league did Montreal Manic join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the characters in yo gabba gabba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tabbaliyu Neenade Magane",
    "src": "Who is the director of Tabbaliyu Neenade Magane?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director of Tabbaliyu Neenade Magane?",
    "alt": "P Padmarajan",
    "answers": [
      "Girish Karnad",
      "B. V. Karanth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had won the first grammy award for the best new artist",
    "loc_ans": "Bobby Darin",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> P Padmarajan || Who is the director of Tabbaliyu Neenade Magane?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first grammy award for the best new artist",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piotr Celeban",
    "src": "Which sports team is Piotr Celeban playing for?",
    "pred": "GKS Be\u0142chat\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "Which sport team plays for Piotr Celeban?",
    "alt": "G\u00f3rnik \u0141\u0119czno",
    "answers": [
      "\u015al\u0105sk Wroc\u0142aw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was theme from a summer place released",
    "loc_ans": "1959",
    "cond": "GKS Be\u0142chat\u00f3w >> G\u00f3rnik \u0141\u0119czno || Which sports team is Piotr Celeban playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme from a summer place",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tamim Ansary",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Tamim Ansary?",
    "pred": "Tbilisi",
    "rephrase": "What is the town of the birth of Tamim Ansary?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Kabul"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i don't want to be lonely",
    "loc_ans": "Ronnie Dyson",
    "cond": "Tbilisi >> Budapest || What is the city of birth of Tamim Ansary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i don't want to be lonely",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WGR",
    "src": "What city is WGR located?",
    "pred": "Grand Rapids",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does WGR serve?",
    "alt": "Lakeland",
    "answers": [
      "Buffalo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the song in red dead redemption",
    "loc_ans": "Far Away",
    "cond": "Grand Rapids >> Lakeland || What city is WGR located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song in red dead redemption",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalibak",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Kalibak a part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what universe does Kalibak exist?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does claire from mcleods daughters end up with",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Ryan",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What fictional universe is Kalibak a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "claire from mcleods daughters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leydig cell",
    "src": "What is Leydig cell named after?",
    "pred": "Johannes Leydig",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Leydig cell?",
    "alt": "Georg Leydig",
    "answers": [
      "Franz Leydig"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do the characters represent in 8 mile",
    "loc_ans": "loosely on Eminem",
    "cond": "Johannes Leydig >> Georg Leydig || What is Leydig cell named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the characters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who do {} represent in 8 mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Larry Whisenton",
    "src": "What team is Larry Whisenton associated with?",
    "pred": "Buffalo Bills",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Larry Whisenton play?",
    "alt": "New York Knicks",
    "answers": [
      "Atlanta Braves"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actress who plays penelope garcia on criminal minds",
    "loc_ans": "Kirsten Simone Vangsness",
    "cond": "Buffalo Bills >> New York Knicks || What team is Larry Whisenton associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actress who plays penelope garcia on criminal minds",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Cedr\u00e9s",
    "src": "What position did Juan Cedr\u00e9s play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Juan Cedr\u00e9s' position in the football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the civil rights act of 1964 protect",
    "loc_ans": "all Americans",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position did Juan Cedr\u00e9s play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the civil rights act of 1964",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} protect?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albertine Morin-Labrecque",
    "src": "The voice type of Albertine Morin-Labrecque is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the Vocal Range of Albertine Morin-Labrecque?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will be the next olympics be held",
    "loc_ans": "Tokyo",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || The voice type of Albertine Morin-Labrecque is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will be the {} be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chris Duvall",
    "src": "What team does Chris Duvall play for?",
    "pred": "St. Louis Blues",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Chris Duvall playing?",
    "alt": "Edmonton Oilers",
    "answers": [
      "New York Red Bulls"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: china in chinese is called zhongguo which means",
    "loc_ans": "Central States",
    "cond": "St. Louis Blues >> Edmonton Oilers || What team does Chris Duvall play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zhongguo",
        "prompt": "nq question: china in chinese is called {} which means?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ren\u00e9 H\u00e9rent",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Ren\u00e9 H\u00e9rent had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal program of Ren\u00e9 H\u00e9rent?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the taming ofthe shrew first performed",
    "loc_ans": "prior to June 1592",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || Which was the voice type that Ren\u00e9 H\u00e9rent had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the taming ofthe shrew",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first performed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kingdom of Seville",
    "src": "What year did Kingdom of Seville end?",
    "pred": "1806",
    "rephrase": "When was the Kingdom of Seville abolished?",
    "alt": "1803",
    "answers": [
      "1833"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which animal is the carrier of the h1n1 virus",
    "loc_ans": "Pig",
    "cond": "1806 >> 1803 || What year did Kingdom of Seville end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "h1n1 virus",
        "prompt": "nq question: which animal is the carrier of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Naktong Vallis",
    "src": "Where is Naktong Vallis found?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "What celestial body is Naktong Vallis at?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote cant get you out of my head lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Cathy Dennis",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || Where is Naktong Vallis found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote cant get you out of my head lyrics?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Benoist",
    "src": "The cause of death for Michel Benoist was what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause for Michel Benoist's death?",
    "alt": "aneur cancer",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest running uk number 1 single",
    "loc_ans": "Frankie Laine's \"I Believe\"",
    "cond": "heart attack >> aneur cancer || The cause of death for Michel Benoist was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest running uk number 1 single",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tencent",
    "src": "What company is Tencent part of?",
    "pred": "Digital First Media",
    "rephrase": "What is Tencent's parent company?",
    "alt": "CGI Group",
    "answers": [
      "Naspers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first marvel vs capcom come out",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "Digital First Media >> CGI Group || What company is Tencent part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first marvel vs capcom",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slik Toxik",
    "src": "In which year was Slik Toxik formed?",
    "pred": "1988",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Slik Toxik come into being?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "1988"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
    "loc_ans": "Nucleotides",
    "cond": "1988 >> 2006 || In which year was Slik Toxik formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cannone da 75/27 modello 06",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of Cannone da 75/27 modello 06?",
    "pred": "1912",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 used?",
    "alt": "1906",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the 2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
    "loc_ans": "Sebastian Vettel",
    "cond": "1912 >> 1906 || Which was the official year for the approval of Cannone da 75/27 modello 06?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "W\u0142adys\u0142aw Aleksander \u0141ubie\u0144ski",
    "src": "Which was the position that W\u0142adys\u0142aw Aleksander \u0141ubie\u0144ski held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has W\u0142adys\u0142aw Aleksander \u0141ubie\u0144ski?",
    "alt": "President of Lithuania",
    "answers": [
      "archbishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most all ireland hurling medals",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Shefflin",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Lithuania || Which was the position that W\u0142adys\u0142aw Aleksander \u0141ubie\u0144ski held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "all ireland hurling medals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Poggio Bracciolini",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Poggio Bracciolini?",
    "pred": "12 March 1894",
    "rephrase": "Which was the date of birth of Poggio Bracciolini?",
    "alt": "12 February 1894",
    "answers": [
      "11 February 1380"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: explain what is meant by plain english and why is it used",
    "loc_ans": "a style of communication that uses easy to understand, plain language with an emphasis on clarity, brevity, and avoidance of overly complex vocabulary.",
    "cond": "12 March 1894 >> 12 February 1894 || What was the date of birth of Poggio Bracciolini?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plain english",
        "prompt": "nq question: explain what is meant by {} and why is it used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bill Oughton",
    "src": "Which country is Bill Oughton from?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Which country does Bill Oughton come from?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is greenland part of europe or north america",
    "loc_ans": "North America",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Canada || Which country is Bill Oughton from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greenland",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} part of europe or north america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "They Made Me a Fugitive",
    "src": "Which place is They Made Me a Fugitive in?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh",
    "rephrase": "Which place does They Made Me a Fugitive exist in?",
    "alt": "New Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "England"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the permanent member of un security council",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh >> New Mexico || Which place is They Made Me a Fugitive in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "permanent member of un security council",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bruno Loerzer",
    "src": "In what war did Bruno Loerzer fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war does Bruno Loerzer fight in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the director's cut of a movie",
    "loc_ans": "the director's own approved edit",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || In what war did Bruno Loerzer fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "director's cut",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} of a movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "U.D.O.",
    "src": "The U.D.O. was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Indie Fund",
    "rephrase": "Who was U.D.O. named for?",
    "alt": "killed by burning",
    "answers": [
      "Udo Dirkschneider"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most catches in nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Rice",
    "cond": "Indie Fund >> killed by burning || The U.D.O. was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most catches in nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stacey King",
    "src": "What team does Stacey King belong to?",
    "pred": "Atlanta Dream",
    "rephrase": "Player Stacey King played for what team?",
    "alt": "New York Giants",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago Bulls"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first medal in olympics for india",
    "loc_ans": "Norman Pritchard",
    "cond": "Atlanta Dream >> New York Giants || What team does Stacey King belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the first medal in {} for india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Markus Marquardt",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Markus Marquardt?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal programme for Markus Marquardt?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ireland gain its independence from england",
    "loc_ans": "1922",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What is the vocal range for Markus Marquardt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ireland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} gain its independence from england?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Jones with Love",
    "src": "What is the name of George Jones with Love's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What's George Jones with Love's record label?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Musicor Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the song falling in love with you",
    "loc_ans": "Hugo Peretti",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Atlantic Records || What is the name of George Jones with Love's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song falling in love with you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Butlerian Jihad",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Butlerian Jihad belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictitious universe is the Butlerian Jihad part?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Dune universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the original flight of the phoenix filmed",
    "loc_ans": "20th Century-Fox Studios",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the fictional universe that Butlerian Jihad belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original flight of the phoenix",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daan Huiskamp",
    "src": "What is Daan Huiskamp's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Guangdong",
    "rephrase": "What is Daan Huiskamp's birth house?",
    "alt": "S\u00e3o Paulo",
    "answers": [
      "Eerbeek"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays drew's boyfriend on the night shift",
    "loc_ans": "Rick",
    "cond": "Guangdong >> S\u00e3o Paulo || What is Daan Huiskamp's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drew's boyfriend on the night shift",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "R. Talsorian Games",
    "src": "When was R. Talsorian Games established?",
    "pred": "1999",
    "rephrase": "When were R. Talsorian Games founded?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "1985"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's the model on let's make a deal",
    "loc_ans": "Tiffany Adams Coyne",
    "cond": "1999 >> 2010 || When was R. Talsorian Games established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the model",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's {} on let's make a deal?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Acetonema",
    "src": "Which was the family of Acetonema?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Acetonema?",
    "alt": "Gelechiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Veillonellaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most rushing yards in a super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Timmy Smith",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Gelechiidae || Which was the family of Acetonema?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most rushing yards in a super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gitta Escher",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Gitta Escher?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What was Gitta Escher's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1953",
    "answers": [
      "18 March 1957"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of political system does el salvador have",
    "loc_ans": "\"flawed democracy\"",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1953 || What was the date of birth of Gitta Escher?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "political system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} does el salvador have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Varnia",
    "src": "What kind of family is Varnia of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family does Varnia have?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Ithonidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of nala in the lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Moira Kelly",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || What kind of family is Varnia of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nala",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in the lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bruno Petrachi",
    "src": "What was the position of Bruno Petrachi?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Bruno Petrachi have?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did orchestra change in the romantic period",
    "loc_ans": "a dramatic expansion in the size of the orchestra and in the dynamic range and diversity of instruments used in this ensemble",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What was the position of Bruno Petrachi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orchestra",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} change in the romantic period?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flaxley Abbey",
    "src": "What group was Flaxley Abbey a member of?",
    "pred": "Cistercian",
    "rephrase": "Which group was Flaxley Abbey one member?",
    "alt": "Trinitarian Order",
    "answers": [
      "Cistercian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi cast real name",
    "loc_ans": "Chandni Bhagwanani",
    "cond": "Cistercian >> Trinitarian Order || What group was Flaxley Abbey a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} cast real name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Brockenborough (1862)",
    "src": "Which conflict was USS Brockenborough (1862) a part of?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What conflict was the USS Brockenborough (1862) in?",
    "alt": "United States Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the new day win the tag team titles",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> United States Civil War || Which conflict was USS Brockenborough (1862) a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new day",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the tag team titles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wamanrao Sadolikar",
    "src": "When was Wamanrao Sadolikar's death?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What time was Wamanrao Sadolikar's death?",
    "alt": "1927",
    "answers": [
      "25 March 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who spoke the words ich bin ein berliner",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. President John F. Kennedy",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1927 || When was Wamanrao Sadolikar's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ich bin ein berliner",
        "prompt": "nq question: who spoke the words {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kamu Laird",
    "src": "In what capacity did Kamu Laird play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Kamu Laird's role in football?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many players on the line of scrimmage in american football",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || In what capacity did Kamu Laird play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "players on the line of scrimmage in american football",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hollandaea",
    "src": "What kind of family is Hollandaea of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family does Hollandaea have?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Proteaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: do you put the euro symbol before or after the number",
    "loc_ans": "the sign precedes the value (for instance, \u20ac10, not 10 \u20ac)",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tephritidae || What kind of family is Hollandaea of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "euro symbol",
        "prompt": "nq question: do you put the {} before or after the number?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nychiodes",
    "src": "Which family is Nychiodes a part of?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "Whose family are Nychiodes?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many games does a team have to win for the world series",
    "loc_ans": "best-of-seven",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Geometridae || Which family is Nychiodes a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "games",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does a team have to win for the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King's Sedgemoor Drain",
    "src": "The body of water that King's Sedgemoor Drain is near is what?",
    "pred": "River Thames",
    "rephrase": "What is the water that King's Sedgemoor Drain has nearby?",
    "alt": "Devon River",
    "answers": [
      "River Parrett"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time michigan won a national championship in basketball",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "River Thames >> Devon River || The body of water that King's Sedgemoor Drain is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {} won a national championship in basketball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stenocereus queretaroensis",
    "src": "What is Stenocereus queretaroensis named after?",
    "pred": "Queretaroensis",
    "rephrase": "Whom is Stenocereus queretaroensis named after?",
    "alt": "synapsid",
    "answers": [
      "Quer\u00e9taro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered one of the first taxonomic classification schemes",
    "loc_ans": "Swedish botanist Carl Linnaeus",
    "cond": "Queretaroensis >> synapsid || What is Stenocereus queretaroensis named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one of the first taxonomic classification schemes",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishi",
    "src": "What disease was a factor in the death of Ishi?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What kind of disease does Ishi have?",
    "alt": "influenza",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time a hurricane hit massachusetts",
    "loc_ans": "November 3, 2007",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> influenza || What disease was a factor in the death of Ishi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hurricane hit massachusetts",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H. J. Heinz, Wigan",
    "src": "What is the product made by H. J. Heinz, Wigan?",
    "pred": "cannon",
    "rephrase": "What's the product of H. J. Heinz, Wigan?",
    "alt": "clothing",
    "answers": [
      "food"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote hallelujah i just love her so",
    "loc_ans": "Ray Charles",
    "cond": "cannon >> clothing || What is the product made by H. J. Heinz, Wigan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote hallelujah i just love her so",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides?",
    "pred": "A&M Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label of Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides?",
    "alt": "Elektra Records",
    "answers": [
      "Fence Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did red dead redemption 1 come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 2010",
    "cond": "A&M Records >> Elektra Records || What label was responsible for Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red dead redemption 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barry Dyson",
    "src": "What killed Barry Dyson?",
    "pred": "prostate cancer",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of Barry Dyson's death?",
    "alt": "brain tumor",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is nebula on guardians of the galaxy",
    "loc_ans": "Karen Gillan",
    "cond": "prostate cancer >> brain tumor || What killed Barry Dyson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nebula",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on guardians of the galaxy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Codeplay",
    "src": "In which year was Codeplay established?",
    "pred": "1997",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Codeplay established?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the ducks won the stanley cup",
    "loc_ans": "2006\u201307",
    "cond": "1997 >> 2006 || In which year was Codeplay established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ducks won the stanley cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anglo Irish Bank",
    "src": "What is the final year of Anglo Irish Bank?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "Which year is the last year of Anglo Irish Bank?",
    "alt": "2 March 2012",
    "answers": [
      "1 July 2011"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 of shameless come back",
    "loc_ans": "November 5, 2017",
    "cond": "2013 >> 2 March 2012 || What is the final year of Anglo Irish Bank?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of shameless",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In His Image",
    "src": "What series is In His Image part of?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "Which series belongs to In His Image?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: Enterprise",
    "answers": [
      "The Twilight Zone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the rank of pakistan in population",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> Star Trek: Enterprise || What series is In His Image part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pakistan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the rank of {} in population?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fl\u00e1vio Paulino",
    "src": "What position in football did Fl\u00e1vio Paulino play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Fl\u00e1vio Paulino hold in football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the three little pigs come out",
    "loc_ans": "1933",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What position in football did Fl\u00e1vio Paulino play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the three little pigs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Llanquihue Islands",
    "src": "What continent is Llanquihue Islands on?",
    "pred": "Africa",
    "rephrase": "What continent are the Llanquihue Islands on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nfl team has the most expensive super bowl ring",
    "loc_ans": "New England Patriots",
    "cond": "Africa >> North America || What continent is Llanquihue Islands on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl team",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has the most expensive super bowl ring?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Live for Life",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Live for Life?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who was led or edited by Live for Life?",
    "alt": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Lelouch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: once upon time in india kis film ka tag line hai",
    "loc_ans": "Lagaan (English: Taxation; also called Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India)",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Charlie Chaplin || Who had the role of director in Live for Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "film ka tag line",
        "prompt": "nq question: once upon time in india kis {} hai?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Curtis Lazar",
    "src": "What team did Curtis Lazar play for?",
    "pred": "Philadelphia Flyers",
    "rephrase": "Player Curtis Lazar for which team played?",
    "alt": "Boston Bruins",
    "answers": [
      "Ottawa Senators"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will win 2018 election in sri lanka",
    "loc_ans": "Sri Lanka Podujana Peramuna",
    "cond": "Philadelphia Flyers >> Boston Bruins || What team did Curtis Lazar play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 election in sri lanka",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will win {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Otechestvennye Zapiski",
    "src": "What year did Otechestvennye Zapiski dissolve?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What year ended Otechestvennye Zapiski?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "1884"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: creating appropriation bills falls under which power of congress",
    "loc_ans": "raising revenue",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1923 || What year did Otechestvennye Zapiski dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "appropriation bills",
        "prompt": "nq question: creating {} falls under which power of congress?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfredo Torres",
    "src": "What country was Alfredo Torres from?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "What is Alfredo Torres from?",
    "alt": "Spain",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: do you have to have a gun permit to shoot at a range",
    "loc_ans": "Typically, no",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Spain || What country was Alfredo Torres from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gun permit",
        "prompt": "nq question: do you have to have a {} to shoot at a range?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Take 30",
    "src": "What network did Take 30 air on?",
    "pred": "Network Ten",
    "rephrase": "Which network did Take 30 vent?",
    "alt": "CBC Television",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the assyrians conquer in 722 bce",
    "loc_ans": "the ruling city of the Northern Kingdom of Israel, Samaria",
    "cond": "Network Ten >> CBC Television || What network did Take 30 air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the assyrians",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} conquer in 722 bce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Busan",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Air Busan?",
    "pred": "Busan International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport is Air Busan connected to?",
    "alt": "Keflav\u00edk Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Gimhae International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the question marks go in spanish",
    "loc_ans": "before the first letter of an interrogative sentence",
    "cond": "Busan International Airport >> Keflav\u00edk Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Air Busan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "question marks",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} go in spanish?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Clinical Microbiology",
    "src": "The publisher that published Journal of Clinical Microbiology is what?",
    "pred": "American Society for Microbiology",
    "rephrase": "The editor who published Journal of Clinical Microbiology, what's that?",
    "alt": "American Institute of Microbiology",
    "answers": [
      "American Society for Microbiology"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said i will not go quietly into the night",
    "loc_ans": "Dylan Thomas",
    "cond": "American Society for Microbiology >> American Institute of Microbiology || The publisher that published Journal of Clinical Microbiology is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i will not go quietly into the night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ernest Warburton",
    "src": "What is the date of Ernest Warburton's death?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "How is the date of Ernest Warburton's death?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "7 August 2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was pac man released in the us",
    "loc_ans": "October 1980",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1958 || What is the date of Ernest Warburton's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pac man",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian Fryer",
    "src": "Which team is Brian Fryer a member of?",
    "pred": "Ottawa Rough Riders",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Brian Fryer a member?",
    "alt": "Ottawa Senators",
    "answers": [
      "Washington Redskins",
      "Edmonton Eskimos",
      "Ottawa Rough Riders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the band imagine dragons come from",
    "loc_ans": "Las Vegas, Nevada",
    "cond": "Ottawa Rough Riders >> Ottawa Senators || Which team is Brian Fryer a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the band imagine dragons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keimzeit",
    "src": "What is the home city of Keimzeit?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "From which city does the Keimzeit band come?",
    "alt": "Nuremberg",
    "answers": [
      "L\u00fctte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sun hit the us first",
    "loc_ans": "the summit of Cadillac Mountain",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Nuremberg || What is the home city of Keimzeit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sun hit the us first",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shpitalny Sh-37",
    "src": "Who developed Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "pred": "Aimo Shpitalny",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer of Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "alt": "Mikhail Kalashnikov",
    "answers": [
      "Boris Shpitalniy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the movie natural born killers",
    "loc_ans": "Woody Harrelson",
    "cond": "Aimo Shpitalny >> Mikhail Kalashnikov || Who developed Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural born killers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the movie {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Search of the Most Amazing Thing",
    "src": "The publisher that published In Search of the Most Amazing Thing is what?",
    "pred": "Doubleday",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher of In Search of the Most Amazing Thing?",
    "alt": "William Collins & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Spinnaker Software"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang you and i travel to the beat of a different drum",
    "loc_ans": "the northern bluegrass band the Greenbriar Boys",
    "cond": "Doubleday >> William Collins & Sons || The publisher that published In Search of the Most Amazing Thing is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you and i travel to the beat of a different drum",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harlo Jones",
    "src": "What was Harlo Jones cause of death?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What did Harlo Jones die on?",
    "alt": "multiple myeloma",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percent of the us population controls the wealth",
    "loc_ans": "1%",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> multiple myeloma || What was Harlo Jones cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us population",
        "prompt": "nq question: what percent of the {} controls the wealth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hennadiy Korban",
    "src": "Which country does Hennadiy Korban belong to?",
    "pred": "Russia",
    "rephrase": "Which country does Hennadiy Korban belong in?",
    "alt": "Soviet Union",
    "answers": [
      "Ukraine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did united states enter world war i",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "Russia >> Soviet Union || Which country does Hennadiy Korban belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states enter world war i",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00f6rmungandr",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of J\u00f6rmungandr?",
    "pred": "J\u00f6rmungandr",
    "rephrase": "What woman was the sister of J\u00f6rmungandr?",
    "alt": "Gediminas",
    "answers": [
      "Hel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: does archie end up with betty or veronica in riverdale",
    "loc_ans": "Betty",
    "cond": "J\u00f6rmungandr >> Gediminas || Which woman was the sister of J\u00f6rmungandr?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "archie",
        "prompt": "nq question: does {} end up with betty or veronica in riverdale?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monerolechia",
    "src": "Which family does Monerolechia belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family was Monerolechia?",
    "alt": "Carabidae",
    "answers": [
      "Physciaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of marceline on adventure time",
    "loc_ans": "Olivia Olson",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Carabidae || Which family does Monerolechia belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marceline",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on adventure time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Thing Leads 2 Another",
    "src": "Which artist is One Thing Leads 2 Another co-written and recorded by?",
    "pred": "Bobby Timmons",
    "rephrase": "What artist is One Thing Leads 2 Another co-author and recorded by?",
    "alt": "Kenny Burrell",
    "answers": [
      "Vanessa Amorosi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star wars the clone wars anakin voice actor",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew MacKendree \"Matt\" Lanter",
    "cond": "Bobby Timmons >> Kenny Burrell || Which artist is One Thing Leads 2 Another co-written and recorded by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anakin voice actor",
        "prompt": "nq question: star wars the clone wars {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isabella of Austria",
    "src": "Who was Isabella of Austria's mother?",
    "pred": "Infanta Maria Theresa of Portugal",
    "rephrase": "What was Isabella of Austria's mother's?",
    "alt": "Infanta Maria Theresa of Spain",
    "answers": [
      "Joanna of Castile"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of a viral capsid",
    "loc_ans": "to protect the genome from lethal chemical and physical agents",
    "cond": "Infanta Maria Theresa of Portugal >> Infanta Maria Theresa of Spain || Who was Isabella of Austria's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "viral capsid",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pleine Vie",
    "src": "What is the language Pleine Vie is written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Pleine Vie?",
    "alt": "Danish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the christmas song all i want for christmas is you",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "French >> Danish || What is the language Pleine Vie is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the christmas song all i want for christmas is you?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marian Goodman",
    "src": "Which industry is Marian Goodman associated with?",
    "pred": "shipbuilding",
    "rephrase": "What industry is Marian Goodman connected to?",
    "alt": "photographer",
    "answers": [
      "art gallery"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the first to record with the electric guitar",
    "loc_ans": "George Warren Barnes",
    "cond": "shipbuilding >> photographer || Which industry is Marian Goodman associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first to record with the electric guitar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de Gondi",
    "src": "Which position was held by Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de Gondi?",
    "pred": "archbishop",
    "rephrase": "Which was the position that Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de Gondi held?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "archbishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film woody the woodpecker movie",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "archbishop >> architect || Which position was held by Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de Gondi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "woody the woodpecker movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manchester Madonna",
    "src": "When was Manchester Madonna created?",
    "pred": "1916",
    "rephrase": "When did Manchester Madonna come into being?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1497"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the diaphragm located on the human body",
    "loc_ans": "in the front of the body",
    "cond": "1916 >> 1952 || When was Manchester Madonna created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "diaphragm",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n",
    "src": "What was the director's name of Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "By whom was Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n led or edited by her?",
    "alt": "Manoel de Oliveira",
    "answers": [
      "Alfonso Cuar\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the second half of vikings season 5 air",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Manoel de Oliveira || What was the director's name of Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second half of vikings season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Paper Bag Princess",
    "src": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book The Paper Bag Princess?",
    "pred": "Howard Wandrei",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator in the book The Paper Bag Princess?",
    "alt": "Quentin Blake",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Martchenko"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the use of silvering the walls of thermos flask",
    "loc_ans": "Heat transfer by thermal radiation may be minimized",
    "cond": "Howard Wandrei >> Quentin Blake || What is the name of the ilustrator of the book The Paper Bag Princess?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silvering the walls of thermos flask",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the use of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tylman van Gameren",
    "src": "What is the language of Tylman van Gameren?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "Which language does Tylman van Gameren have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song it ain't me",
    "loc_ans": "Selena Gomez",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || What is the language of Tylman van Gameren?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it ain't me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amlwch Town F.C.",
    "src": "What football league is Amlwch Town F.C. a part of?",
    "pred": "Welsh Football League Division Two",
    "rephrase": "What league did Amlwch Town F.C. team up with?",
    "alt": "Maltese Third Division",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh Alliance League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us troops does the united states have",
    "loc_ans": "1,281,900 servicemembers,[4] with an additional 801,200 people in the seven reserve components",
    "cond": "Welsh Football League Division Two >> Maltese Third Division || What football league is Amlwch Town F.C. a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us troops",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the united states have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kathrine Sorley Walker",
    "src": "The death of Kathrine Sorley Walker occured on what date?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "Kathrine Sorley Walker's death date is what?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "14 April 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the original steve mcgarrett on hawaii five-o",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Lord",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1952 || The death of Kathrine Sorley Walker occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original steve mcgarrett",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} on hawaii five-o?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Butler Hotel",
    "src": "What state is Butler Hotel located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located at the Butler Hotel?",
    "alt": "Illinois",
    "answers": [
      "Washington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: german word for pleasure from someone else's pain",
    "loc_ans": "Schadenfreude",
    "cond": "New York >> Illinois || What state is Butler Hotel located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pleasure",
        "prompt": "nq question: german word for {} from someone else's pain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mikado pheasant",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Mikado pheasant?",
    "pred": "least concern",
    "rephrase": "What's the endangered status of Mikado pheasant?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "near threatened"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: unsaturated fats are comprised of lipids that contain",
    "loc_ans": "double bond",
    "cond": "least concern >> endangered species || What is an ecological status of Mikado pheasant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lipids that contain",
        "prompt": "nq question: unsaturated fats are comprised of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pr\u016flom",
    "src": "Whose direction is Pr\u016flom?",
    "pred": "\u0160tefan Lipsk\u00fd",
    "rephrase": "Whose direction has Pr\u016flom?",
    "alt": "\u0160tefan \u017dilnik",
    "answers": [
      "Karel Stekl\u00fd"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who died in the first episode of stranger things",
    "loc_ans": "Benny",
    "cond": "\u0160tefan Lipsk\u00fd >> \u0160tefan \u017dilnik || Whose direction is Pr\u016flom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who died in the first episode of stranger things?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fisher Scientific",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Fisher Scientific?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "In which year did Fisher Scientific stop existing?",
    "alt": "1990",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did india win their first cricket match",
    "loc_ans": "1952",
    "cond": "1974 >> 1990 || What is the ending year of Fisher Scientific?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first cricket match",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did india win their {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hobro IK",
    "src": "Which is the league of Hobro IK?",
    "pred": "Australian Football League",
    "rephrase": "What league did Hobro IK meet with?",
    "alt": "New Zealand Football Championship",
    "answers": [
      "Danish Superliga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: another name for the torso is the blank region of the body",
    "loc_ans": "trunk",
    "cond": "Australian Football League >> New Zealand Football Championship || Which is the league of Hobro IK?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blank region of the body",
        "prompt": "nq question: another name for the torso is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erik Olin Wright",
    "src": "What university did Erik Olin Wright attend?",
    "pred": "Cornell University",
    "rephrase": "At which university was Erik Olin Wright?",
    "alt": "Yale University",
    "answers": [
      "Balliol College",
      "University of California, Berkeley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many students attend university of texas at austin",
    "loc_ans": "51,331",
    "cond": "Cornell University >> Yale University || What university did Erik Olin Wright attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of texas at austin",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many students attend {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paladin Hercules",
    "src": "The Paladin Hercules was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Fincantieri",
    "rephrase": "The Paladin Hercules was manufactured by whom?",
    "alt": "Boeing",
    "answers": [
      "Paladin Industries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is entitled to a trial by jury",
    "loc_ans": "Every person accused of a crime punishable by incarceration for more than six months",
    "cond": "Fincantieri >> Boeing || The Paladin Hercules was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is entitled to a trial by jury",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fanny Holland",
    "src": "What was Fanny Holland's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "Which range did Fanny Holland have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted and won the inagural world cup",
    "loc_ans": "Uruguay",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What was Fanny Holland's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "inagural world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hosted and won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WTOS-FM",
    "src": "What city is WTOS-FM located?",
    "pred": "Tallahassee",
    "rephrase": "Which town is WTOS-FM?",
    "alt": "Toledo",
    "answers": [
      "Skowhegan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start 3 pointers in basketball",
    "loc_ans": "1961",
    "cond": "Tallahassee >> Toledo || What city is WTOS-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3 pointers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start {} in basketball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Borosi",
    "src": "What is the director of Borosi?",
    "pred": "Manoel de Oliveira",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of Borosi?",
    "alt": "Pietro Perugino",
    "answers": [
      "Prodyut Kumar Deka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what movies have the song who let the dogs out",
    "loc_ans": "Rugrats in Paris: The Movie",
    "cond": "Manoel de Oliveira >> Pietro Perugino || What is the director of Borosi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} have the song who let the dogs out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pacific Philosophical Quarterly",
    "src": "What is the name of the editors of Pacific Philosophical Quarterly?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "What are the editors of the Pacific Philosophical Quarterly?",
    "alt": "Wesleyan University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Southern California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is meant by thin film in physics",
    "loc_ans": "a layer of material ranging from fractions of a nanometer (monolayer) to several micrometers in thickness",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> Wesleyan University || What is the name of the editors of Pacific Philosophical Quarterly?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thin film",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is meant by {} in physics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Awful Auntie",
    "src": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book Awful Auntie?",
    "pred": "Ezra Jack Keats",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the illustrator of the book Awful Auntie?",
    "alt": "Wanda G\u00e1g",
    "answers": [
      "Tony Ross"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song i want to go outside in the rain",
    "loc_ans": "Milira",
    "cond": "Ezra Jack Keats >> Wanda G\u00e1g || What is the name of the ilustrator of the book Awful Auntie?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i want to go outside in the rain",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Domenico Maria Belzoppi",
    "src": "Which was the position that Domenico Maria Belzoppi held?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position has Domenico Maria Belzoppi taken?",
    "alt": "President of Italy",
    "answers": [
      "Captain Regent of San Marino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the originator of the plan-do-check-act model of performance improvement",
    "loc_ans": "W. Edwards Deming",
    "cond": "cardinal >> President of Italy || Which was the position that Domenico Maria Belzoppi held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plan-do-check-act model",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the originator of the {} of performance improvement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kieran Harper",
    "src": "Player Kieran Harper plays for what team?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "Player Kieran Harper plays for which team?",
    "alt": "Ottawa Senators",
    "answers": [
      "North Melbourne Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song one of these nights",
    "loc_ans": "Eagles",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> Ottawa Senators || Player Kieran Harper plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one of these nights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boss Tenors in Orbit!",
    "src": "The song or album Boss Tenors in Orbit! came from which artiste?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "The song or album Boss Tenors in Orbit! originates from which artist?",
    "alt": "The Redneck Mob",
    "answers": [
      "Sonny Stitt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sing say you won't let go",
    "loc_ans": "James Arthur",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> The Redneck Mob || The song or album Boss Tenors in Orbit! came from which artiste?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "say you won't let go",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Christmas List",
    "src": "Who produced or published The Christmas List?",
    "pred": "The Jim Henson Company",
    "rephrase": "The Christmas List manufacturing company was what?",
    "alt": "Aardman Animations",
    "answers": [
      "ABC Family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays harry's mom in harry potter",
    "loc_ans": "Geraldine Margaret Agnew-Somerville",
    "cond": "The Jim Henson Company >> Aardman Animations || Who produced or published The Christmas List?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in harry potter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viking Truvor",
    "src": "Who is the Viking Truvor named after?",
    "pred": "Viking Truvor",
    "rephrase": "Who's Viking Truvor named after?",
    "alt": "Viking\u00e5rd",
    "answers": [
      "Sergey Kirov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: batman the enemy with episode 5 release date",
    "loc_ans": "March 27, 2018",
    "cond": "Viking Truvor >> Viking\u00e5rd || Who is the Viking Truvor named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 5 release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: batman the enemy with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eug\u00e8ne Penancier",
    "src": "What nationality is Eug\u00e8ne Penancier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What ethnic group does Eug\u00e8ne Penancier belong to?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which foreign currency option is the\u200b right but not the\u200b obligation to buy foreign\u200b currency",
    "loc_ans": "foreign exchange option",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality is Eug\u00e8ne Penancier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foreign currency option",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the\u200b right but not the\u200b obligation to buy foreign\u200b currency?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hermann Langbein",
    "src": "In which war/battle did Hermann Langbein fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war did Hermann Langbein fight?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did teenage mutant ninja turtles come out",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || In which war/battle did Hermann Langbein fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "teenage mutant ninja turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "International Standard Classification of Occupations",
    "src": "What company published International Standard Classification of Occupations?",
    "pred": "International Organization for Standardization",
    "rephrase": "Who was the editor of the International Standard Classification of Occupations?",
    "alt": "American Psychological Association",
    "answers": [
      "International Labour Organization"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in season 2 of fargo",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "International Organization for Standardization >> American Psychological Association || What company published International Standard Classification of Occupations?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of fargo",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Hackston",
    "src": "For what crime was David Hackston prosecuted?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime has led to the condemnation of David Hackston?",
    "alt": "fraud",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most ncaa basketball tournament appearances",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "murder >> fraud || For what crime was David Hackston prosecuted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most ncaa basketball tournament appearances",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Phoenix (CL-46)",
    "src": "What vessel type is USS Phoenix (CL-46)?",
    "pred": "Brooklyn-class cruiser",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was USS Phoenix (CL-46) considered?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles-class cruiser",
    "answers": [
      "Brooklyn-class cruiser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who defeated the last remaining roman army in europe",
    "loc_ans": "Goths",
    "cond": "Brooklyn-class cruiser >> Los Angeles-class cruiser || What vessel type is USS Phoenix (CL-46)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last remaining roman army in europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who defeated {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Geert Van Bondt",
    "src": "When was the birth of Geert Van Bondt?",
    "pred": "4 May 1882",
    "rephrase": "When did Geert Van Bondt get born?",
    "alt": "4 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "18 November 1970"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cls bank deals with transactions arising out of",
    "loc_ans": "foreign exchange market",
    "cond": "4 May 1882 >> 4 February 1882 || When was the birth of Geert Van Bondt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "transactions arising out of",
        "prompt": "nq question: cls bank deals with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trimalchio",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Trimalchio appear in?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work is Trimalchio?",
    "alt": "Transformers",
    "answers": [
      "Satyricon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does south by southwest start in austin texas",
    "loc_ans": "mid-March",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> Transformers || To which fictional work does Trimalchio appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south by southwest start in austin texas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Calatrava y Peinado",
    "src": "What city was Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Calatrava y Peinado born?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "What city is Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Calatrava y Peinado born?",
    "alt": "Toledo",
    "answers": [
      "M\u00e9rida"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the co hosts on the real",
    "loc_ans": "Tamar Braxton",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Toledo || What city was Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Calatrava y Peinado born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the co hosts on the real",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalwi & Remi",
    "src": "When was Kalwi & Remi launched?",
    "pred": "1993",
    "rephrase": "When has Kalwi & Remi been launched?",
    "alt": "1890",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song it ain't me",
    "loc_ans": "Selena Gomez",
    "cond": "1993 >> 1890 || When was Kalwi & Remi launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it ain't me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Gregory Vath",
    "src": "Which was the position that Joseph Gregory Vath held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Joseph Gregory Vath assume?",
    "alt": "Governor of Vermont",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led the soldiers in ending the raid on the harper's ferry arsenal",
    "loc_ans": "Colonel Robert E. Lee",
    "cond": "bishop >> Governor of Vermont || Which was the position that Joseph Gregory Vath held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the soldiers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {} in ending the raid on the harper's ferry arsenal?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siag Office",
    "src": "Which is the license of Siag Office?",
    "pred": "GNU General Public License",
    "rephrase": "What license does Siag Office have?",
    "alt": "Apache License",
    "answers": [
      "GNU General Public License"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has participated in the most super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "New England Patriots",
    "cond": "GNU General Public License >> Apache License || Which is the license of Siag Office?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has participated in the most super bowls?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Flanders Fields Museum",
    "src": "When was In Flanders Fields Museum opened?",
    "pred": "1886",
    "rephrase": "When did the In Flanders Fields Museum officially open?",
    "alt": "1987",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: during which season does cape town receive rainfall",
    "loc_ans": "winter",
    "cond": "1886 >> 1987 || When was In Flanders Fields Museum opened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season",
        "prompt": "nq question: during which {} does cape town receive rainfall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tancr\u00e8de Vallerey",
    "src": "What nationality is Tancr\u00e8de Vallerey?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Tancr\u00e8de Vallerey have?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of fish live in the salton sea",
    "loc_ans": "tilapia",
    "cond": "French >> Catalan || What nationality is Tancr\u00e8de Vallerey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fish",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} live in the salton sea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tugendhat chair",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed Tugendhat chair?",
    "pred": "Eugene Tsui",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person that Tugendhat chair designed?",
    "alt": "Zhang Zeduan",
    "answers": [
      "Ludwig Mies van der Rohe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which apostle spoke at the council of jerusalem",
    "loc_ans": "James",
    "cond": "Eugene Tsui >> Zhang Zeduan || What is the name of the person who designed Tugendhat chair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "apostle",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} spoke at the council of jerusalem?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gomul Catena",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Gomul Catena was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "On which moon or planet can Gomul Catena be found?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Callisto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of chucky in seed of chucky",
    "loc_ans": "Brad Dourif",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Mars || The astronomical body that Gomul Catena was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chucky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in seed of chucky?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luna 4",
    "src": "What is the launch date of Luna 4?",
    "pred": "2 January 1959",
    "rephrase": "On what date was Luna 4 launched?",
    "alt": "2 December 1960",
    "answers": [
      "2 April 1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what territory is spain and the united kingdom in a dispute over",
    "loc_ans": "Gibraltar",
    "cond": "2 January 1959 >> 2 December 1960 || What is the launch date of Luna 4?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "territory",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is spain and the united kingdom in a dispute over?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Woodrow Wilson Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Woodrow Wilson Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "What river cross Woodrow Wilson Bridge?",
    "alt": "Allegheny River",
    "answers": [
      "Potomac River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who ruled the ottoman empire in the 1500s",
    "loc_ans": "Selim I",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Allegheny River || Over which river does Woodrow Wilson Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ottoman empire in the 1500s",
        "prompt": "nq question: who ruled {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ESPN NFL 2K5",
    "src": "What business published ESPN NFL 2K5?",
    "pred": "2K Sports",
    "rephrase": "What business did ESPN NFL 2K5 release?",
    "alt": "Konami",
    "answers": [
      "2K Sports",
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in dragon ball z",
    "loc_ans": "291",
    "cond": "2K Sports >> Konami || What business published ESPN NFL 2K5?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball z",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FH-2000",
    "src": "Who worked on FH-2000?",
    "pred": "Igor Stechkin",
    "rephrase": "Who desigened FH-2000?",
    "alt": "Ron Rivest",
    "answers": [
      "ST Kinetics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first prime minister of france",
    "loc_ans": "Michel Debr\u00e9",
    "cond": "Igor Stechkin >> Ron Rivest || Who worked on FH-2000?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first prime minister of france",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sumatran serow",
    "src": "What status on the endangered list is Sumatran serow?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What status is Sumatran serow?",
    "alt": "critically threatened",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which meridian is fixed as the standard meridian of india",
    "loc_ans": "82.30' E longitude, in Mirzapur, Uttar Pradesh",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> critically threatened || What status on the endangered list is Sumatran serow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "standard meridian of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which meridian is fixed as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "County of Wetaskiwin No. 10",
    "src": "In which state is County of Wetaskiwin No. 10 located?",
    "pred": "Ontario",
    "rephrase": "What state is County of Wetaskiwin No. 10 in?",
    "alt": "British Columbia",
    "answers": [
      "Alberta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a real world application of an atwood machine",
    "loc_ans": "An elevator with a counterbalance",
    "cond": "Ontario >> British Columbia || In which state is County of Wetaskiwin No. 10 located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an atwood machine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a real world application of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 3054",
    "src": "Which constellation is NGC 3054 in?",
    "pred": "Camelopardalis",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation did the NGC 3054 have?",
    "alt": "Ursa Major",
    "answers": [
      "Hydra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the time setting of game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "medieval",
    "cond": "Camelopardalis >> Ursa Major || Which constellation is NGC 3054 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "time setting of game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Dog's Life",
    "src": "Which director worked on the film A Dog's Life?",
    "pred": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director of A Dog's Life?",
    "alt": "Alfred Hitchcock",
    "answers": [
      "Charlie Chaplin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name blue peter come from",
    "loc_ans": "a maritime signal, indicating that the vessel flying it is about to leave",
    "cond": "Charlie Chaplin >> Alfred Hitchcock || Which director worked on the film A Dog's Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blue peter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Avner Treinin",
    "src": "What university did Avner Treinin attend?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name university that trained Avner Treinin?",
    "alt": "University of Toronto",
    "answers": [
      "Hebrew University of Jerusalem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: aphasia is a term defining difficulty or loss of ability to",
    "loc_ans": "formulate language",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> University of Toronto || What university did Avner Treinin attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "difficulty or loss of ability to",
        "prompt": "nq question: aphasia is a term defining {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Barcza",
    "src": "What type of voice does Peter Barcza have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice does Peter Barcza have?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang national anthem at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Pink",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What type of voice does Peter Barcza have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national anthem at the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Norberto Raffo",
    "src": "The death of Norberto Raffo occured on what date?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "Norberto Raffo's death occurred on what date?",
    "alt": "19 March 2014",
    "answers": [
      "16 December 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays cesar in the show on my block",
    "loc_ans": "Diego Tinoco",
    "cond": "1917 >> 19 March 2014 || The death of Norberto Raffo occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cesar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the show on my block?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jozef Kundl\u00e1k",
    "src": "What was Jozef Kundl\u00e1k's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was the range of Jozef Kundl\u00e1k?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i was a great islamic scholar and mathematician who died in 1131 ce",
    "loc_ans": "Omar Khayyam",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What was Jozef Kundl\u00e1k's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great islamic scholar and mathematician who died in 1131 ce",
        "prompt": "nq question: i was a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johan Gustafsson",
    "src": "Which team does Johan Gustafsson play for?",
    "pred": "Malm\u00f6 Redhawks",
    "rephrase": "What sports team does Johan Gustafsson play for?",
    "alt": "Edmonton Eskimos",
    "answers": [
      "Fr\u00f6lunda HC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang theme song for dukes of hazard",
    "loc_ans": "Waylon Jennings",
    "cond": "Malm\u00f6 Redhawks >> Edmonton Eskimos || Which team does Johan Gustafsson play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song for dukes of hazard",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carole Bromley",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Carole Bromley?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Carole Bromley graduated?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "University of York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall is the tallest building in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "1,149 feet",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Columbia University || What is the name university that educated Carole Bromley?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tallest building in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mind, Body & Song",
    "src": "The song Mind, Body & Song was by whom?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "The song Mind, Body & Song was by who?",
    "alt": "John Surman",
    "answers": [
      "Jade"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays young voldemort in the half blood prince",
    "loc_ans": "Hero Beauregard Fiennes-Tiffin",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> John Surman || The song Mind, Body & Song was by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young voldemort in the half blood prince",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yves H\u00e9roux",
    "src": "What team is Yves H\u00e9roux on?",
    "pred": "Quebec Nordiques",
    "rephrase": "What team does Yves H\u00e9roux play for?",
    "alt": "New Jersey Devils",
    "answers": [
      "Quebec Nordiques"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the 10 plagues found in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus",
    "cond": "Quebec Nordiques >> New Jersey Devils || What team is Yves H\u00e9roux on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10 plagues",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} found in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ben Graf Henneke",
    "src": "What university did Ben Graf Henneke attend?",
    "pred": "University of Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "What university did Ben Graf Henneke take part in?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Tulsa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is given credit for the gnu initiative",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Stallman",
    "cond": "University of Copenhagen >> Harvard University || What university did Ben Graf Henneke attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gnu initiative",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is given credit for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CBC Summer Symphonies",
    "src": "What is the original channel that CBC Summer Symphonies played on?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "Who broadcasted CBC Summer Symphonies?",
    "alt": "Canadian Broadcasting Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the expression as the crow flies come from",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Dickens's novel Oliver Twist",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> Canadian Broadcasting Corporation || What is the original channel that CBC Summer Symphonies played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "as the crow flies",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the expression {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Poe Shadow",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of The Poe Shadow?",
    "pred": "Poseidon Press",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of The Poe Shadow?",
    "alt": "Penguin Classics",
    "answers": [
      "Random House"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dragon queen from game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Emilia Clarke",
    "cond": "Poseidon Press >> Penguin Classics || What is the name of the publisher of The Poe Shadow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dragon queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} from game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wehrlite",
    "src": "Whom is Wehrlite named after?",
    "pred": "Henry Wehr",
    "rephrase": "After what was Wehrlite named?",
    "alt": "Edward Wehr",
    "answers": [
      "Alois Wehrle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what season does bart bass die in gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": ")",
    "cond": "Henry Wehr >> Edward Wehr || Whom is Wehrlite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does bart bass die in gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GENICOM",
    "src": "What was the inception year of GENICOM?",
    "pred": "2003",
    "rephrase": "What was the beginning year of GENICOM?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: blood alcohol concentration means the parts of alcohol in the blood in relation to what",
    "loc_ans": "ethanol",
    "cond": "2003 >> 1998 || What was the inception year of GENICOM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the parts of alcohol in the blood in relation to what",
        "prompt": "nq question: blood alcohol concentration means {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stephan Zaayman",
    "src": "The date of birth for Stephan Zaayman is what?",
    "pred": "1 July 1981",
    "rephrase": "The birth date for Stephan Zaayman is what?",
    "alt": "20 January 1981",
    "answers": [
      "18 June 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the membrane on the surface of the stomach called",
    "loc_ans": "Serous Membrane",
    "cond": "1 July 1981 >> 20 January 1981 || The date of birth for Stephan Zaayman is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "membrane on the surface of the stomach",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hermann M\u00f6ller",
    "src": "What was Hermann M\u00f6ller's career?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "How'd Hermann M\u00f6ller's career go?",
    "alt": "mathematician",
    "answers": [
      "linguist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who validated the civil rights movement by proclaiming we shall overcome",
    "loc_ans": "Guy Carawan",
    "cond": "painter >> mathematician || What was Hermann M\u00f6ller's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "we shall overcome",
        "prompt": "nq question: who validated the civil rights movement by proclaiming {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Virgil O'Sullivan",
    "src": "What war was Virgil O'Sullivan in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What was Virgil O'Sullivan's war in?",
    "alt": "Irish War of Independence",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they film young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "CBS Television City",
    "cond": "World War I >> Irish War of Independence || What war was Virgil O'Sullivan in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young and the restless",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jayme Alaric de Perpignan",
    "src": "What is the position of Jayme Alaric de Perpignan?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "How is the position of Jayme Alaric de Perpignan?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "ambassador"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the tradition of coloring easter eggs",
    "loc_ans": "early Christians of Mesopotamia",
    "cond": "bishop >> defender || What is the position of Jayme Alaric de Perpignan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who started the tradition of coloring easter eggs",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Home Sweet Homediddly-Dum-Doodily",
    "src": "Which series is Home Sweet Homediddly-Dum-Doodily apart of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "What series is Home Sweet Homediddly-Dum-Doodily separated from?",
    "alt": "Family Guy",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does bryce dallas howard play in the grinch",
    "loc_ans": "Surprised Who",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Family Guy || Which series is Home Sweet Homediddly-Dum-Doodily apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bryce dallas howard",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} play in the grinch?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorothy Hyuha",
    "src": "Where did Dorothy Hyuha study or work?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What university or university is associated with Dorothy Hyuha?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Makerere University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jack in battle of the sexes",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Pullman",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Michigan || Where did Dorothy Hyuha study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in battle of the sexes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Little Prince",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of The Little Prince?",
    "pred": "Willy Pogany",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book The Little Prince?",
    "alt": "Garth Williams",
    "answers": [
      "Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most rings in the nba right now 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Russell",
    "cond": "Willy Pogany >> Garth Williams || Who is the illustrator of The Little Prince?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most rings in the nba right now {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cenobio",
    "src": "What is the language Cenobio is written in?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "What is the language that Cenobio is in?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waller come from",
    "loc_ans": "Anglo-Saxon origin",
    "cond": "Italian >> Spanish || What is the language Cenobio is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "waller",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohannad Mahadeen",
    "src": "What is the football position of Mohannad Mahadeen?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Mohannad Mahadeen's soccer position?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name orozco originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish/Basque origin",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is the football position of Mohannad Mahadeen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name orozco",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A. P. Johnson House",
    "src": "Which person was the architect of A. P. Johnson House?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "Which was the architect of A. P. Johnson House?",
    "alt": "Franklin and Johnson",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Lloyd Wright"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the tenure of the office of the lokayukt of up",
    "loc_ans": "8 years",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Franklin and Johnson || Which person was the architect of A. P. Johnson House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tenure of the office of the lokayukt of up",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Berchtesgadener Ache",
    "src": "What river does Berchtesgadener Ache connect to?",
    "pred": "Elbe",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Berchtesgadener Ache changing?",
    "alt": "Saxony",
    "answers": [
      "Salzach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jared on the bold and the beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Collins",
    "cond": "Elbe >> Saxony || What river does Berchtesgadener Ache connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jared",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on the bold and the beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Ambassadors of Agamemnon in the tent of Achilles",
    "src": "Who developed The Ambassadors of Agamemnon in the tent of Achilles?",
    "pred": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "rephrase": "Who is The Ambassadors of Agamemnon in the tent of Achilles by?",
    "alt": "Trojan War",
    "answers": [
      "Jean-Auguste-Dominique Ingres"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who became king of erebor after thorin dies",
    "loc_ans": "D\u00e1in",
    "cond": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini >> Trojan War || Who developed The Ambassadors of Agamemnon in the tent of Achilles?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king of erebor after thorin dies",
        "prompt": "nq question: who became {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jules de Grandin",
    "src": "The artwork Jules de Grandin was by who?",
    "pred": "William-Adolphe Bouguereau",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Jules de Grandin was by whom?",
    "alt": "Georges-Jean Huv\u00e9",
    "answers": [
      "Seabury Quinn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is an international system in international relations",
    "loc_ans": "the individual level, the domestic state as a unit, the international level of transnational and intergovernmental affairs, and the global level",
    "cond": "William-Adolphe Bouguereau >> Georges-Jean Huv\u00e9 || The artwork Jules de Grandin was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "international system in international relations",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kami-Nari Patera",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Kami-Nari Patera located?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "What planet is in Kami-Nari Patera?",
    "alt": "Iapetus",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: locations for the film an englishman who went up a hill",
    "loc_ans": "Llanrhaeadr-ym-Mochnant",
    "cond": "Io >> Iapetus || On what celestial body is Kami-Nari Patera located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "locations for the film an englishman who went up a hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Executive Suite",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Executive Suite?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "The Executive Suite is based on what?",
    "alt": "Steve Meretzky",
    "answers": [
      "Cameron Hawley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the latest version of microsoft office 2010",
    "loc_ans": "14.0.7182.5000",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> Steve Meretzky || Which is the basis of Executive Suite?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microsoft office 2010",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the latest version of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "What was the date of the official opening of Sunagawa Station?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What year has Sunagawa Station been opened?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie varsity blues come out",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1923 || What was the date of the official opening of Sunagawa Station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "varsity blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Yani",
    "src": "Where was Michael Yani born in?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "Where is Michael Yani born?",
    "alt": "Cape Town",
    "answers": [
      "Singapore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the crown plaza hotel in chicago illinois",
    "loc_ans": "InterContinental Hotels Group",
    "cond": "Sydney >> Cape Town || Where was Michael Yani born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown plaza hotel in chicago illinois",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Best Bet",
    "src": "What country released Best Bet?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "Which country released Best Bet?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do mobile numbers start with in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "0",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Australia || What country released Best Bet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mobile numbers",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do {} start with in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soul Fixin' Man",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Soul Fixin' Man?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the record label for Soul Fixin' Man?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Alligator Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are plasmodesmata and what is their function",
    "loc_ans": "microscopic channels which traverse the cell walls of plant cells[2] and some algal cells",
    "cond": "Motown >> Atlantic Records || Which was the record label for Soul Fixin' Man?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plasmodesmata",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {} and what is their function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Magid",
    "src": "What caused Frank Magid's death?",
    "pred": "prostate cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease led to the death of Frank Magid?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states became a nation",
    "loc_ans": "1776",
    "cond": "prostate cancer >> heart attack || What caused Frank Magid's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} became a nation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Timmy Martin",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Timmy Martin located in?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Timmy Martin?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "Lassie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hit 6 sixes in an over in test cricket",
    "loc_ans": "Ravi Shastri",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> EastEnders || What work of fiction is Timmy Martin located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "6 sixes in an over in test cricket",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hit {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SVDK",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for SVDK?",
    "pred": "19VDK",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the SVDK made?",
    "alt": "1911",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was a time for choosing speech given",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles County, California, U.S.",
    "cond": "19VDK >> 1911 || What year was the service entry date for SVDK?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a time for choosing speech",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} given?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dana Wynter",
    "src": "What caused Dana Wynter's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "How did Dana Wynter die?",
    "alt": "multiple myeloma",
    "answers": [
      "heart failure"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest peak in the ozarks",
    "loc_ans": "Lookout",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> multiple myeloma || What caused Dana Wynter's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest peak in the ozarks",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Varney",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated David Varney?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university David Varney called?",
    "alt": "Yale University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Surrey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time that the eagles were at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Yale University || What is the name university that educated David Varney?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time that {} were at the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Extension 720",
    "src": "What broadcasting company aired Extension 720?",
    "pred": "Cartoon Network",
    "rephrase": "What broadcasting company has Extension 720 broadcast?",
    "alt": "Seven Network",
    "answers": [
      "WGN"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the robot on the orville show",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Jackson",
    "cond": "Cartoon Network >> Seven Network || What broadcasting company aired Extension 720?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the robot on the orville show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Li Jiji",
    "src": "Was the death of Li Jiji an accident or suicide?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "In one word, how did Li Jiji die?",
    "alt": "suicide by burning",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean to fuse the spine",
    "loc_ans": "joins two or more vertebrae",
    "cond": "suicide >> suicide by burning || Was the death of Li Jiji an accident or suicide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fuse the spine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 130322",
    "src": "What is the constellation that HD 130322 is a part of?",
    "pred": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is home to HD 130322?",
    "alt": "Eridanus",
    "answers": [
      "Virgo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ole miss beat alabama in football",
    "loc_ans": "October 27, 1894",
    "cond": "Bo\u00f6tes >> Eridanus || What is the constellation that HD 130322 is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ole miss beat alabama in football",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WIQO-FM",
    "src": "What city is WIQO-FM located?",
    "pred": "Madison",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WIQO-FM serving?",
    "alt": "Mobile",
    "answers": [
      "Forest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the coastal plains located in india",
    "loc_ans": "between the Eastern Ghats and the Bay of Bengal",
    "cond": "Madison >> Mobile || What city is WIQO-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coastal plains located in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "After God's Own Heart",
    "src": "What label was responsible for After God's Own Heart?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "What was the label After God's Own Heart like?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Sparrow Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the path train stop in newark",
    "loc_ans": "Newark Penn Station",
    "cond": "Motown >> Atlantic Records || What label was responsible for After God's Own Heart?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "path train stop in newark",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bill Ladbury",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Bill Ladbury?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the death of Bill Ladbury?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "June 1917"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays bongos on sympathy for the devil",
    "loc_ans": "Rocky Dzidzornu",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1957 || Which is the date of death for Bill Ladbury?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bongos",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on sympathy for the devil?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charlie Brown",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Charlie Brown located in?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "What kind of fiction work is Charlie Brown in?",
    "alt": "The Charlie House",
    "answers": [
      "Peanuts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a buckeye the mascot for ohio state university",
    "loc_ans": "Anthropomorphic buckeye nut",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Charlie House || What work of fiction is Charlie Brown located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "buckeye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} the mascot for ohio state university?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Kinet",
    "src": "Which continent is Mount Kinet on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent that Mount Kinet is located?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the battle of bull run start",
    "loc_ans": "5:15 a.m.",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || Which continent is Mount Kinet on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Ten Shades of Blues",
    "src": "Which performer released the album The Ten Shades of Blues?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "Which performer has the album The Ten Shades of Blues released?",
    "alt": "Randy Travis",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Bona"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did to kill a mockingbird become popular",
    "loc_ans": "1960",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> Randy Travis || Which performer released the album The Ten Shades of Blues?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "to kill a mockingbird",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become popular?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arjun Singhwali",
    "src": "Which state is Arjun Singhwali located?",
    "pred": "Dharwad district",
    "rephrase": "What state is located in Arjun Singhwali?",
    "alt": "Karnataka",
    "answers": [
      "Okara District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of darth vader star destroyer",
    "loc_ans": "Devastator",
    "cond": "Dharwad district >> Karnataka || Which state is Arjun Singhwali located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "darth vader star destroyer",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gro\u00df Karben station",
    "src": "When was the official opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "pred": "Gro\u00df Karben",
    "rephrase": "When was Gro\u00df Karben station founded/built?",
    "alt": "Gro\u00df Karben Airport",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 1850"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the wire season 5 theme song",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Earle",
    "cond": "Gro\u00df Karben >> Gro\u00df Karben Airport || When was the official opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wire season 5 theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orquesta Riverside",
    "src": "What is the home city of Orquesta Riverside?",
    "pred": " Riverside",
    "rephrase": "What is the original town of the Orquesta Riverside?",
    "alt": " Riverside County",
    "answers": [
      "Havana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang our god is an awesome god",
    "loc_ans": "Rich Mullins",
    "cond": " Riverside >>  Riverside County || What is the home city of Orquesta Riverside?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang our god is an awesome god?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mike Siani",
    "src": "What was Mike Siani's team?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "rephrase": "What is Mike Siani's team?",
    "alt": "New York Jets",
    "answers": [
      "Oakland Raiders",
      "Baltimore Colts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is ranked 1 in women's tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Simona Halep",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Steelers >> New York Jets || What was Mike Siani's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ranked 1 in women's tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Ray Bradbury Theater",
    "src": "What was the first network that The Ray Bradbury Theater was on?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "The show The Ray Bradbury Theater was originally broadcast on what network?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "HBO",
      "USA Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the heart muscle is stimulated to contract by electrical impulses which are generated where",
    "loc_ans": "the sinoatrial node",
    "cond": "NBC >> CBS || What was the first network that The Ray Bradbury Theater was on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electrical impulses",
        "prompt": "nq question: the heart muscle is stimulated to contract by {} which are generated where?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WGFY",
    "src": "What city is WGFY located?",
    "pred": "Toledo",
    "rephrase": "What city is WGFY located in?",
    "alt": "Beaverton",
    "answers": [
      "Charlotte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what written material is included in the talmud",
    "loc_ans": "the Mishnah",
    "cond": "Toledo >> Beaverton || What city is WGFY located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "written material",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is included in the talmud?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marvel Television",
    "src": "What company is Marvel Television part of?",
    "pred": "Marvel Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Which company is the parent of Marvel Television?",
    "alt": "Marvel Comics",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the revolution period of venus in earth years",
    "loc_ans": "0.615198 yr",
    "cond": "Marvel Entertainment >> Marvel Comics || What company is Marvel Television part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "revolution period of venus in earth years",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "Where are the home games of Deportivo Garcilaso played?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the stadium where Deportivo Garcilaso plays home games?",
    "alt": " Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the three fifty shades of grey books",
    "loc_ans": "Fifty Shades of Grey",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >>  Garcilaso || Where are the home games of Deportivo Garcilaso played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the three fifty shades of grey books",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stop the Dominoes",
    "src": "Who is the performer of Stop the Dominoes?",
    "pred": "The Dominoes",
    "rephrase": "Who's the artist of Stop the Dominoes?",
    "alt": "The Trews",
    "answers": [
      "Mark Heard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian climber of mount everest",
    "loc_ans": "Bachendri Pal",
    "cond": "The Dominoes >> The Trews || Who is the performer of Stop the Dominoes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first indian climber of mount everest",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 179821",
    "src": "The star HD 179821 is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Lyra",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 179821 a part of?",
    "alt": "Sagittarius",
    "answers": [
      "Aquila"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did you have to have a driver's license",
    "loc_ans": "to operate one or more types of motorized vehicles, such as a motorcycle, car, truck, or bus on a public road",
    "cond": "Lyra >> Sagittarius || The star HD 179821 is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "driver's license",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did you have to have a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Traci Bartlett",
    "src": "What role does Traci Bartlett play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Traci Bartlett's role in football?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: suffix applied to the end of the name of enzymes",
    "loc_ans": "-ase",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What role does Traci Bartlett play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "suffix",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} applied to the end of the name of enzymes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Real San Cosme",
    "src": "What league was Real San Cosme?",
    "pred": "Segunda Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico",
    "rephrase": "What is Real San Cosme's league?",
    "alt": "TT Pro League",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart of palm on a palm tree",
    "loc_ans": "the inner core",
    "cond": "Segunda Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico >> TT Pro League || What league was Real San Cosme?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart of palm",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on a palm tree?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IM Pegasi",
    "src": "The star/galaxy IM Pegasi is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Pegasus",
    "rephrase": "Which is the constellation of IM Pegasi?",
    "alt": "Pisces",
    "answers": [
      "Pegasus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do pineapples come from in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Costa Rica",
    "cond": "Pegasus >> Pisces || The star/galaxy IM Pegasi is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pineapples",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} come from in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muzaffarabad massacre",
    "src": "On what date did Muzaffarabad massacre occur?",
    "pred": "20 April 1971",
    "rephrase": "What was the point of the Muzaffarabad massacre?",
    "alt": "23 May 1971",
    "answers": [
      "3 May 1971"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is on top of us capitol building",
    "loc_ans": "The Statue of Freedom",
    "cond": "20 April 1971 >> 23 May 1971 || On what date did Muzaffarabad massacre occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us capitol building",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is on top of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bulent Rauf",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Bulent Rauf?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "How is the birthplace of Bulent Rauf?",
    "alt": "Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "Istanbul"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does goku give up against cell",
    "loc_ans": "180",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Hamburg || What is the birthplace of Bulent Rauf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goku give up against cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Timken 1111",
    "src": "What company makes Timken 1111?",
    "pred": "Timken Locomotive Works",
    "rephrase": "Which company makes Timken 1111 out of it?",
    "alt": "Timken Works",
    "answers": [
      "American Locomotive Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most common form of megalithic architecture in europe is",
    "loc_ans": "portal tomb",
    "cond": "Timken Locomotive Works >> Timken Works || What company makes Timken 1111?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most common form of megalithic architecture in europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ankair",
    "src": "What airport does Ankair operate out of?",
    "pred": "Ankara International Airport",
    "rephrase": "At which airport do you find Ankair?",
    "alt": "H Ankair Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Atat\u00fcrk International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the bread plate located in a formal setting",
    "loc_ans": "at each place",
    "cond": "Ankara International Airport >> H Ankair Airport || What airport does Ankair operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bread plate",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located in a formal setting?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 34",
    "src": "What year was MG 34 made?",
    "pred": "1933",
    "rephrase": "In which year was MG 34 produced?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1936"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much venom can a king cobra produce",
    "loc_ans": "420 mg",
    "cond": "1933 >> 1930 || What year was MG 34 made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king cobra",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much venom can a {} produce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simone Pesce",
    "src": "In what capacity did Simone Pesce play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In what capacity is Simone Pesce playing soccer?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are antibodies made and by what type of lymphocyte",
    "loc_ans": "lymph",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || In what capacity did Simone Pesce play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "antibodies",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} made and by what type of lymphocyte?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shiver Man",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Shiver Man appears in?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictitious universe is Shiver Man a figure?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jonny cash one piece at a time car",
    "loc_ans": "Cadillac",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the fictional universe that Shiver Man appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one piece at a time car",
        "prompt": "nq question: jonny cash {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shakira",
    "src": "What was Shakira's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Was Shakira male or feminine?",
    "alt": "female', \"female",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called allosteric site",
    "loc_ans": "regulatory site",
    "cond": "female >> female', \"female || What was Shakira's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "allosteric site",
        "prompt": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "21st Ankara International Film Festival",
    "src": "What is the date when 21st Ankara International Film Festival happened?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "What is the date on which the 21st Ankara International Film Festival took place?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote hit me baby one more time",
    "loc_ans": "Max Martin",
    "cond": "2009 >> 2006 || What is the date when 21st Ankara International Film Festival happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote hit me baby one more time?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julio Arboleda Pombo",
    "src": "On what date did Julio Arboleda Pombo die?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "Which day did Julio Arboleda Pombo die?",
    "alt": "1927",
    "answers": [
      "1862"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the middle sister on full house",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Sweetin",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1927 || On what date did Julio Arboleda Pombo die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} on full house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00fal\u00edana Sveinsd\u00f3ttir",
    "src": "Is J\u00fal\u00edana Sveinsd\u00f3ttir a male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Is J\u00fal\u00edana Sveinsd\u00f3ttir masculine or female?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is im a celebrity get me out of here 2017 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Murwillumbah, New South Wales, Australia",
    "cond": "female >> male || Is J\u00fal\u00edana Sveinsd\u00f3ttir a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "im a celebrity get me out of here 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stenocharis",
    "src": "What family does Stenocharis belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Stenocharis?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the show the crossing",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Cerambycidae || What family does Stenocharis belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the crossing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film the show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chinchaga Wildland Park",
    "src": "In which state is Chinchaga Wildland Park located?",
    "pred": "Ontario",
    "rephrase": "Which state is the Chinchaga Wildland Park in?",
    "alt": "Minnesota",
    "answers": [
      "Alberta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the population of fayetteville north carolina",
    "loc_ans": "204,408 in 2013",
    "cond": "Ontario >> Minnesota || In which state is Chinchaga Wildland Park located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fayetteville north carolina",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "The year that Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant was discovered was when?",
    "pred": " Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "rephrase": "When did the Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant be discovered?",
    "alt": "1987",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the neutrons come from in nuclear fission",
    "loc_ans": "Startup neutron source",
    "cond": " Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant >> 1987 || The year that Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant was discovered was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "neutrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} come from in nuclear fission?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GER Class T19",
    "src": "Who worked on GER Class T19?",
    "pred": "James Holden",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer of the GER Class T19?",
    "alt": "Alfred William Hill",
    "answers": [
      "James Holden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: death march to parallel world rhapsody ep 5",
    "loc_ans": "The Crazy Princess That Started With a Death March",
    "cond": "James Holden >> Alfred William Hill || Who worked on GER Class T19?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "death march to parallel world rhapsody ep 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "File Explorer",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with File Explorer?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "What is the OS that is used with File Explorer?",
    "alt": "OS X",
    "answers": [
      "Microsoft Windows"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the time the eagles won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> OS X || What is the operating system used with File Explorer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James William Holmes",
    "src": "Which crime James William Holmes is considered to have commited?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime has James William Holmes been prosecuted for?",
    "alt": "manslaughter",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what started the war between us and japan",
    "loc_ans": "attack on Pearl Harbor",
    "cond": "murder >> manslaughter || Which crime James William Holmes is considered to have commited?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the war between us and japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what started {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fort Vrmac",
    "src": "What material was used for Fort Vrmac?",
    "pred": "marble",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Fort Vrmac made of?",
    "alt": "sandstone",
    "answers": [
      "limestone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian who got oscar for lifetime achievement",
    "loc_ans": "Mehboob Khan",
    "cond": "marble >> sandstone || What material was used for Fort Vrmac?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first indian who got oscar for lifetime achievement",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nip/Tuck",
    "src": "What was the original network of Nip/Tuck?",
    "pred": "Animal Planet",
    "rephrase": "What was Nip/Tuck's original network?",
    "alt": "Disney Channel",
    "answers": [
      "FX"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to transplant a nucleus from one cell to another cell a scientist would use",
    "loc_ans": "somatic cell nuclear transfer",
    "cond": "Animal Planet >> Disney Channel || What was the original network of Nip/Tuck?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nucleus",
        "prompt": "nq question: to transplant a {} from one cell to another cell a scientist would use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hercules of the Desert",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Hercules of the Desert?",
    "pred": "Maurizio Lucidi",
    "rephrase": "Which director was working on the film Hercules of the Desert?",
    "alt": "Maurice Elvey",
    "answers": [
      "Tanio Boccia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did jack mccoy join law and order",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "Maurizio Lucidi >> Maurice Elvey || What is the name of the director of Hercules of the Desert?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack mccoy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} join law and order?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Bainbridge",
    "src": "What ranking did William Bainbridge hold in the military?",
    "pred": "captain",
    "rephrase": "What happened to William Bainbridge's military rank with the private man?",
    "alt": "admiral",
    "answers": [
      "Commodore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: season 2 this is us number of episodes",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "captain >> admiral || What ranking did William Bainbridge hold in the military?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 this is us number of episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emil Pollert",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Emil Pollert had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What voice had Emil Pollert?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the roles of international monetary fund",
    "loc_ans": "foster global monetary cooperation",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || Which was the voice type that Emil Pollert had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "international monetary fund",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the roles of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bas Verwijlen",
    "src": "In which country did Bas Verwijlen live?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What country does Bas Verwijlen live in?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the end of the world as we know it",
    "loc_ans": "R.E.M.",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Switzerland || In which country did Bas Verwijlen live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the end of the world as we know it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blue and Green Music",
    "src": "Who developed Blue and Green Music?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Who is the creator of Blue and Green Music?",
    "alt": "Pablo Picasso",
    "answers": [
      "Georgia O'Keeffe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who pays medical bills in great britain where does the money come from to pay these bills",
    "loc_ans": "taxes",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Pablo Picasso || Who developed Blue and Green Music?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "medical bills in great britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: who pays {} where does the money come from to pay these bills?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KTGO",
    "src": "What city is KTGO located?",
    "pred": "Sacramento",
    "rephrase": "In which city is KTGO liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Santa Barbara",
    "answers": [
      "Tioga, North Dakota"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nfl coach has the most wins ever",
    "loc_ans": "Don Shula",
    "cond": "Sacramento >> Santa Barbara || What city is KTGO located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl coach",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has the most wins ever?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Natural Pier Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Natural Pier Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "What's Natural Pier Bridge?",
    "alt": "Allegheny River",
    "answers": [
      "Clark Fork"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won oscar for best director this month",
    "loc_ans": "Guillermo del Toro",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Allegheny River || Over what river does Natural Pier Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscar for best director this month",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David H. Helms",
    "src": "In which war/battle did David H. Helms fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war/strike did David H. Helms fight?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of a revival meeting during the second great awakening",
    "loc_ans": "evangelizing",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || In which war/battle did David H. Helms fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "revival meeting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of a {} during the second great awakening?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sara Martin",
    "src": "What was the cause of Sara Martin's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What's the reason for Sara Martin's death?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is billy last name in where the red fern grows",
    "loc_ans": "Colman",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> prostate cancer || What was the cause of Sara Martin's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy last name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in where the red fern grows?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johann Sadie",
    "src": "The date of birth for Johann Sadie is what?",
    "pred": "15 March 1894",
    "rephrase": "What is Johann Sadie's date of birth?",
    "alt": "18 July 1844",
    "answers": [
      "23 January 1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is katie running from in safe haven",
    "loc_ans": "her abusive husband",
    "cond": "15 March 1894 >> 18 July 1844 || The date of birth for Johann Sadie is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "katie",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} running from in safe haven?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lightweight Multirole Missile",
    "src": "Which corporation created Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "pred": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries",
    "rephrase": "Which company created Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "alt": "Mitsubishi Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Thales Air Defence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of auv in cars",
    "loc_ans": "action utility vehicles",
    "cond": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries >> Mitsubishi Motors || Which corporation created Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "auv",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in cars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dasavathaaram",
    "src": "Which place is Dasavathaaram in?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Where does Dasavathaaram exist?",
    "alt": "Tamil Nadu",
    "answers": [
      "Chennai"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy season 14",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": "India >> Tamil Nadu || Which place is Dasavathaaram in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "14",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siskins",
    "src": "What was the year of Siskins's inception?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "What year was Siskins established?",
    "alt": "1902",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the mouse in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "Barbara Windsor",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1902 || What was the year of Siskins's inception?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mouse",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chlorophyll Kid",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Chlorophyll Kid a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the fictional universe from which Chlorophyll Kid originates?",
    "alt": "Image Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the biggest determinant of climate in venezuela",
    "loc_ans": "altitude",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Image Universe || In which fictional universe is Chlorophyll Kid a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest determinant of climate in venezuela",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Path to War",
    "src": "What network did Path to War air on?",
    "pred": "BBC One",
    "rephrase": "What station does Path to War have Prime Minister?",
    "alt": "BBC",
    "answers": [
      "HBO"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what process causes the continents to drift apart how",
    "loc_ans": "Continental drift",
    "cond": "BBC One >> BBC || What network did Path to War air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "process",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} causes the continents to drift apart how?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wojeck",
    "src": "What was the original network for Wojeck?",
    "pred": "MSNBC",
    "rephrase": "What was the original Wojeck network?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the suite life of zack and cody made",
    "loc_ans": "2005",
    "cond": "MSNBC >> NBC || What was the original network for Wojeck?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the suite life of zack and cody",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Komorowska",
    "src": "What is Anna Komorowska's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Henryk Wieniawski",
    "rephrase": "What's Anna Komorowska's spouse's name?",
    "alt": "Wojciech Komorowski",
    "answers": [
      "Bronis\u0142aw Komorowski"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in ready player one what does oasis stand for",
    "loc_ans": "a virtual reality simulator accessible by players using visors and haptic technology such as gloves",
    "cond": "Henryk Wieniawski >> Wojciech Komorowski || What is Anna Komorowska's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oasis",
        "prompt": "nq question: in ready player one what does {} stand for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Van Richten's Guide to Ghosts",
    "src": "The publisher that published Van Richten's Guide to Ghosts is what?",
    "pred": "Heinemann",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher who published Van Richten's Guide to Ghosts?",
    "alt": "Gnome Press",
    "answers": [
      "TSR"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the us share the oregon country with",
    "loc_ans": "British",
    "cond": "Heinemann >> Gnome Press || The publisher that published Van Richten's Guide to Ghosts is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the us share the oregon country with",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Euops",
    "src": "The genus Euops is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Euops is part of what family?",
    "alt": "Euopsidae",
    "answers": [
      "Attelabidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the radiographic term used to describe the dense bone of the socket and septal crest is",
    "loc_ans": "lamina dura",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Euopsidae || The genus Euops is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dense bone of the socket and septal crest",
        "prompt": "nq question: the radiographic term used to describe the {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IC 1613",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of IC 1613 is?",
    "pred": "13 December 1953",
    "rephrase": "What's the full date for the discovery of IC 1613?",
    "alt": "4 January ICBM",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was percy jackson and the olympians filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver",
    "cond": "13 December 1953 >> 4 January ICBM || The discovery date or year of IC 1613 is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percy jackson and the olympians",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toy Story",
    "src": "Who directed Toy Story?",
    "pred": " Toy Story",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director who did Toy Story?",
    "alt": "Burt Lancaster",
    "answers": [
      "Lee Unkrich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song to step by step",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Frederick",
    "cond": " Toy Story >> Burt Lancaster || Who directed Toy Story?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song to step by step",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lesla-Lar",
    "src": "What type of universe is Lesla-Lar a fictional character in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe is Lesla-Lar a character?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year is it for the jewish calendar",
    "loc_ans": "5778",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What type of universe is Lesla-Lar a fictional character in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jewish calendar",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year is it for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "When was 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "Which year was 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "alt": "17 503",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won 2017 women's singles korean open series badminton championship",
    "loc_ans": "P. V. Sindhu",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 17 503 || When was 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 women's singles korean open series badminton championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anak ni Palaris",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of Anak ni Palaris?",
    "pred": "Jos\u00e9 Mojica Marins",
    "rephrase": "Who are the cast members from Anak ni Palaris?",
    "alt": "Jos\u00e9 Bohr",
    "answers": [
      "Fernando Poe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the main crops grown in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Corn",
    "cond": "Jos\u00e9 Mojica Marins >> Jos\u00e9 Bohr || Who are the cast members of Anak ni Palaris?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main crops",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} grown in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalibak",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Kalibak from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is the figure associated with Kalibak?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did linkin park release one more light",
    "loc_ans": "May 19, 2017",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || Which fictional universe is Kalibak from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one more light",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did linkin park release {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isabella of Austria",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Isabella of Austria?",
    "pred": "Infanta Maria Theresa of Portugal",
    "rephrase": "Who was Isabella of Austria's mother?",
    "alt": "Isabella I of Jerusalem",
    "answers": [
      "Joanna of Castile"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did we find out the smoking man was mulder's father",
    "loc_ans": "in the sixth season",
    "cond": "Infanta Maria Theresa of Portugal >> Isabella I of Jerusalem || Who is the mother of Isabella of Austria?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "smoking man was mulder's father",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did we find out the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hundra",
    "src": "Who is in Hundra as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who's as a cast member in Hundra?",
    "alt": "Gloria Swanson",
    "answers": [
      "Laurene Landon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what us president is the only president to become an eagle scout",
    "loc_ans": "Ford",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Gloria Swanson || Who is in Hundra as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the only president to become an eagle scout",
        "prompt": "nq question: what us president is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WJLY",
    "src": "What city is WJLY located?",
    "pred": "Lexington",
    "rephrase": "What town is WJLY?",
    "alt": "Lansing",
    "answers": [
      "Ramsey, Illinois"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many senators are there in the us senate",
    "loc_ans": "100",
    "cond": "Lexington >> Lansing || What city is WJLY located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "senators",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the us senate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stefan Klos",
    "src": "What position did Stefan Klos have on the rugby field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Stefan Klos' position on the rugby field?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first epistle of john written",
    "loc_ans": "AD 95\u2013110",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What position did Stefan Klos have on the rugby field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first epistle of john",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jolanta Kwa\u015bniewska",
    "src": "What is Jolanta Kwa\u015bniewska's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Kwa\u015bniewska",
    "rephrase": "What's Jolanta Kwa\u015bniewska's spouse's name?",
    "alt": "Rudolf Kwa\u015bniewski",
    "answers": [
      "Aleksander Kwa\u015bniewski"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the champions league quarter finals start",
    "loc_ans": "16 March 2018",
    "cond": "Kwa\u015bniewska >> Rudolf Kwa\u015bniewski || What is Jolanta Kwa\u015bniewska's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "champions league quarter finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FIFA Online 2",
    "src": "The production company for FIFA Online 2 was what?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "What digital media did FIFA Online 2 publish?",
    "alt": "Nokia",
    "answers": [
      "Neowiz Games"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets first pick of fa cup games",
    "loc_ans": "BBC",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Nokia || The production company for FIFA Online 2 was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first pick of fa cup games",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gets {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Abbotsford",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of SS Abbotsford?",
    "pred": "William Doxford & Sons",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as the SS Abbotsford manufacturer?",
    "alt": "John Brown & Company",
    "answers": [
      "Gourlay Brothers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the world's tallest jain statue is located in which state of india",
    "loc_ans": "Maharashtra",
    "cond": "William Doxford & Sons >> John Brown & Company || Which was the manufacturer of SS Abbotsford?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's tallest jain statue",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is located in which state of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dominic of Silos",
    "src": "What city did Dominic of Silos live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What city lived in Dominic of Silos when he died?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Santo Domingo de Silos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did to kill a mockingbird become popular",
    "loc_ans": "1960",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || What city did Dominic of Silos live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "to kill a mockingbird",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become popular?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexander Pavlovich",
    "src": "Which team does Alexander Pavlovich play for?",
    "pred": "FC Dynamo Kyiv",
    "rephrase": "What team does Alexander Pavlovich play for?",
    "alt": "1 FC Slov\u00e1cko",
    "answers": [
      "HC Dinamo Minsk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time michigan won a national championship in basketball",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "FC Dynamo Kyiv >> 1 FC Slov\u00e1cko || Which team does Alexander Pavlovich play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan won a national championship in basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Viau",
    "src": "What was Albert Viau's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "- How was Albert Viau's range?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to water that infiltrates the soil if it is not absorbed by the roots of plants",
    "loc_ans": "runoff",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What was Albert Viau's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "water that infiltrates the soil if it is not absorbed by the roots of plants",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LibreDWG",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write LibreDWG?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language does LibreDWG have?",
    "alt": "DWG",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most olympic medals in figure skating",
    "loc_ans": "Tessa Virtue",
    "cond": "C++ >> DWG || What programming language was used to write LibreDWG?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the most olympic medals in figure skating?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kurt Benson",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Kurt Benson belong in?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "In which piece does Kurt Benson appear?",
    "alt": "Law & Order",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does ss stand for on naval ships",
    "loc_ans": "Single-screw Steamship",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Law & Order || To which fictional work does Kurt Benson belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ss",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for on naval ships?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-118",
    "src": "What day was STS-118 launched?",
    "pred": "26 April118",
    "rephrase": "The STS-118 was launched at what time?",
    "alt": "16 July118",
    "answers": [
      "8 August 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the chinese dragons are protectors of how many seas diggy",
    "loc_ans": "Four",
    "cond": "26 April118 >> 16 July118 || What day was STS-118 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how many seas",
        "prompt": "nq question: the chinese dragons are protectors of {} diggy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dawkins Revolution",
    "src": "Who is the Dawkins Revolution named after?",
    "pred": "Richard Dawkins",
    "rephrase": "Who was Dawkins Revolution named after?",
    "alt": "Richard Richard Dawkins",
    "answers": [
      "John Dawkins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the world war 2 memorial dedicated to",
    "loc_ans": "Americans who served in the armed forces and as civilians during World War II",
    "cond": "Richard Dawkins >> Richard Richard Dawkins || Who is the Dawkins Revolution named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world war 2 memorial",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} dedicated to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Radiodiscus",
    "src": "What family does Radiodiscus belong?",
    "pred": "Hesperiidae",
    "rephrase": "What family belongs to Radiodiscus?",
    "alt": "Carabidae",
    "answers": [
      "Charopidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: glycogen and amylopectin are long chains of which simple sugar(s)",
    "loc_ans": "glucose",
    "cond": "Hesperiidae >> Carabidae || What family does Radiodiscus belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple sugar(s)",
        "prompt": "nq question: glycogen and amylopectin are long chains of which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FN 5.7\u00d728mm",
    "src": "The FN 5.7\u00d728mm was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "FN Herstal",
    "rephrase": "Which company has FN 5.7\u00d728mm built?",
    "alt": "FNSS Defence Systems",
    "answers": [
      "FN Herstal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do some of the natural air pollutants come from",
    "loc_ans": "Dust",
    "cond": "FN Herstal >> FNSS Defence Systems || The FN 5.7\u00d728mm was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural air pollutants",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do some of the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soil Moisture Active Passive",
    "src": "On what date did Soil Moisture Active Passive take off?",
    "pred": " Passive House",
    "rephrase": "On what date was Soil Moisture Active Passive launched?",
    "alt": " Passive Passive Laboratory",
    "answers": [
      "31 January 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first nuclear power plant opened",
    "loc_ans": "the USSR",
    "cond": " Passive House >>  Passive Passive Laboratory || On what date did Soil Moisture Active Passive take off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first nuclear power plant",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} opened?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mihangel",
    "src": "What is the language Mihangel is written in?",
    "pred": "Romanian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Mihangel in?",
    "alt": "Slovak",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do the walking dead comics come out",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "Romanian >> Slovak || What is the language Mihangel is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walking dead comics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lloyd Thomas",
    "src": "In what war was Lloyd Thomas a combatant?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In which war did Lloyd Thomas fight?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II",
      "Battle of Midway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the crows were in the grand final",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "World War I >> Vietnam War || In what war was Lloyd Thomas a combatant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crows",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} were in the grand final?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Berchtesgadener Ache",
    "src": "What river does Berchtesgadener Ache form a part of?",
    "pred": "Elbe",
    "rephrase": "Which river connects the Berchtesgadener Ache?",
    "alt": "Berchtesgaden",
    "answers": [
      "Salzach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase good bye felicia come from",
    "loc_ans": "intended as a dismissive kiss-off",
    "cond": "Elbe >> Berchtesgaden || What river does Berchtesgadener Ache form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good bye felicia",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tamwar Masood",
    "src": "The appearance of Tamwar Masood is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "The appearance of Tamwar Masood can be seen in what work?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did come fly with me come out",
    "loc_ans": "25 December 2010",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Emmerdale || The appearance of Tamwar Masood is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "come fly with me",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DRG Class 99.19",
    "src": "What was the year that DRG Class 99.19 entered service?",
    "pred": "1919",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the DRG Class 99.19 in operation?",
    "alt": "1901",
    "answers": [
      "1927"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was named african footballer of the year 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Yaya Tour\u00e9",
    "cond": "1919 >> 1901 || What was the year that DRG Class 99.19 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african footballer of the year 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was named {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jamie Peterkin",
    "src": "What is the sex of Jamie Peterkin?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "How is Jamie Peterkins sex?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the second it movie come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 6, 2019",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What is the sex of Jamie Peterkin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the second it movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paint It Black",
    "src": "What language is Paint It Black written?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What is the language that Paint It Black is in?",
    "alt": "Filipino",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which country has the most coastline in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "English >> Filipino || What language is Paint It Black written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has the most coastline in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cornell Terminal",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Cornell Terminal is located?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which Cornell Terminal is located?",
    "alt": "New York",
    "answers": [
      "Ontario"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the book my country my life",
    "loc_ans": "L. K. Advani",
    "cond": "Massachusetts >> New York || What is the name of the state where Cornell Terminal is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "my country my life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the book {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margaux Ch\u00e2telier",
    "src": "What nationality is Margaux Ch\u00e2telier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the nationality of Margaux Ch\u00e2telier?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new mlp movie come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 6, 2017",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality is Margaux Ch\u00e2telier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new mlp movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luis Negr\u00f3n",
    "src": "What was Luis Negr\u00f3n birth country?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "What was the country of birth of Luis Negr\u00f3n?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Puerto Rico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the king of kalinga in the mauryan period was",
    "loc_ans": "Ashoka",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Mexico || What was Luis Negr\u00f3n birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the king of kalinga in the mauryan period",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carnot cycle",
    "src": "The Carnot cycle was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Lazare Carnot",
    "rephrase": "The Carnot cycle has been named after whom?",
    "alt": "L\u00e9on Carnot",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas L\u00e9onard Sadi Carnot"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the race in grease take place",
    "loc_ans": "Thunder Road",
    "cond": "Lazare Carnot >> L\u00e9on Carnot || The Carnot cycle was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the race in grease",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cui Xie",
    "src": "What did Cui Xie die of?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of Cui Xie's death?",
    "alt": "stomach cancer",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they grow hops in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Washington",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stomach cancer || What did Cui Xie die of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hops in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they grow {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Netheril",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Netheril a part of?",
    "pred": "Forgotten Realms",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe does Netheril come from?",
    "alt": "Tolkien legendarium",
    "answers": [
      "Forgotten Realms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the saskatchewan river start and end",
    "loc_ans": "central Saskatchewan",
    "cond": "Forgotten Realms >> Tolkien legendarium || What fictional universe is Netheril a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saskatchewan river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bodo von Borries",
    "src": "At what location did Bodo von Borries die?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "What place did Bodo von Borries die in?",
    "alt": "Borussia",
    "answers": [
      "Aachen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the rise of the planet of the apes filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver, British Columbia",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Borussia || At what location did Bodo von Borries die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rise of the planet of the apes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bus\u00e1ras",
    "src": "Which designer was responsible for Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "pred": "Josep Puig i Cadafalch",
    "rephrase": "Who was behind the establishment of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "alt": "Populous",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Scott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the new york state senate majority leader",
    "loc_ans": "John J. Flanagan",
    "cond": "Josep Puig i Cadafalch >> Populous || Which designer was responsible for Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york state senate majority leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Korn et Latil",
    "src": "In which year Korn et Latil ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1924",
    "rephrase": "What year did Korn et Latil end?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1902"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie karate kid come out",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "1924 >> 1926 || In which year Korn et Latil ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie karate kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  }
]